<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Fleas on Pest Control &amp; Home Improvement Guides</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/categories/fleas/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Fleas on Pest Control &amp; Home Improvement Guides</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- 0.147.3</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 07 May 2025 12:21:29 +0300</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/categories/fleas/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Can You Use Dog Shampoo on Cats?</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/can-you-use-dog-shampoo-on-cats/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 23:51:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/can-you-use-dog-shampoo-on-cats/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We may earn a commission when you click and buy from Amazon.com.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This article will answer the question, &amp;ldquo;can you use dog shampoo on cats?&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Unlike dogs, cats don&amp;rsquo;t need to be bathed as often; they
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pestpolicy.com/what-can-i-wash-my-cat-with/&#34;&gt;keep their fur healthy and clean&lt;/a&gt;
using their tongue.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So, caring for a cat can be easy, but there are some instances where your feline friend needs a more intensive shampoo, maybe to remove bad smells or contamination.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wagner Spraytech 0282014 915e On-Demand Steam Cleaner</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/wagner-spraytech-0282014-915e-on-demand-steam-cleaner/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 23:48:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/wagner-spraytech-0282014-915e-on-demand-steam-cleaner/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We may earn a commission when you click and buy from Amazon.com.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The holiday season ushers in warmth, joy, and, inevitably, a surge in household messes. Amidst the festivities, maintaining a pristine home can pose a challenge.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thankfully, Wagner presents a game-changing solution with its
&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B003PGQI3Y?ref=t_ac_view_request_product_image&amp;amp;campaignId=amzn1.campaign.2MQKGZCT0CJXN&amp;amp;linkCode=tr1&amp;amp;tag=1563-20&amp;amp;linkId=amzn1.campaign.2MQKGZCT0CJXN_1701355115069&#34;&gt;915e On-Demand Steam Cleaner&lt;/a&gt;
. Here&amp;rsquo;s why this multipurpose powerhouse deserves a top spot on your holiday shopping list.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;chemical-free-cleaning-excellence&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Chemical-Free Cleaning Excellence:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Bid farewell to harsh chemicals and embrace the cleansing power of steam. The Wagner 915e ingeniously utilizes chemical-free steam to effortlessly banish grime, grease, and stubborn wallpaper residue.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Does Bug Spray Expire? Picaridin? Spectracide?</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/does-bug-spray-expire/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 23:43:17 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/does-bug-spray-expire/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We may earn a commission when you click and buy from Amazon.com.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;**Whether youre on a hiking trip or at the beach, a bug spray can be a lifesaver. But does bug spray expire? Well, the efficacy decreases over time. Since most products dont have an expiry date, you should use them within 18 to 36 months. **&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;what-happens-with-expired-bug-spray&#34;&gt;What happens with expired bug spray?&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When the spray passes the expiry date, it may not be useful as a self-defense weapon. Depending on the brand, you may not spray when the aerosol start leaking out.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Use a Flea Comb Effectively (with Steps)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/how-to-use-a-flea-comb/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 23:26:43 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/how-to-use-a-flea-comb/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We may earn a commission when you click and buy from Amazon.com.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;dl&gt;
&lt;dt&gt;Here&amp;rsquo;s how to use a flea comb. Hey, today I am here on my garage table with my dog Jake. I&amp;rsquo;ll demonstrate how to use a&lt;/dt&gt;
&lt;dt&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://pestpolicy.com/best-flea-comb-for-cats/&#34;&gt;flea comb&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/dt&gt;
&lt;dt&gt;on your cat or dog. You&amp;rsquo;ll not use chemicals, and thus it&amp;rsquo;s a non-toxic process.&lt;/dt&gt;
&lt;dt&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Note&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/dt&gt;
&lt;dd&gt;first, fleas live in the house (not on pets) - so, they&amp;rsquo;ll temporarily jump on pets or
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pestpolicy.com/can-humans-carry-fleas-from-one-home-to-another/&#34;&gt;pet owners&lt;/a&gt;
. I recommend inspecting your pets if you find the pet starts frequently scratching, losing hair, or restless than usual.
*If you need a short answer, place your cat/dog on a white or light-colored towel. Comb through your pet&amp;rsquo;s hair slowly - start at the nip of the neck and work your way down. Make sure to cover the base of the back and the neck area. Finally, clean and vacuum the spaces you&amp;rsquo;ve used for flea combing. *
[amazon bestseller=&amp;ldquo;Best Flea Comb&amp;rdquo; items=&amp;ldquo;2&amp;rdquo; template=&amp;ldquo;table&amp;rdquo;]&lt;/dd&gt;
&lt;/dl&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;how-to-use-a-flea-comb-step-by-step&#34;&gt;How to Use a Flea Comb (Step by Step)&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;step-1-take-a-half-full-bowl-or-bucket-with-hot-soapy-water&#34;&gt;Step 1: Take a Half-full Bowl or Bucket with Hot Soapy Water&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;First, you&amp;rsquo;ll need to put a half-filled bowl or bucket with hot soapy water. The
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pestpolicy.com/does-the-dryer-kill-fleas/&#34;&gt;hot-soapy water will drown or kill fleas&lt;/a&gt;
that you&amp;rsquo;ll remove from the cat or dog. The logic of having a hall-filled but equally deep bucket so that the fleas won&amp;rsquo;t jump out and escape.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Can Dog Fleas Transfer to Humans?</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/can-dog-fleas-transfer-to-humans/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 23:22:47 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/can-dog-fleas-transfer-to-humans/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We may earn a commission when you click and buy from Amazon.com.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Recently my friend, Jane, got a healthy-looking dog.
&lt;strong&gt;Sadly&lt;/strong&gt;
, the dog was flea-infested. Jane applied
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pestpolicy.com/best-flea-shampoo-for-dogs/&#34;&gt;flea shampoo&lt;/a&gt;
on the dog to save the situation.
But, she&amp;rsquo;s still worried whether &amp;ldquo;Dog Fleas Transfer to Humans?&amp;rdquo; Can the bugs jump/ bite him, his kids, or his wife? I seek to answer these questions in this short post.
&lt;strong&gt;The simple answer is Yes&lt;/strong&gt;
.
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pestpolicy.com/best-flea-combs-for-dogs/&#34;&gt;Dog fleas (Ctenocephalides canis&lt;/a&gt;
) will sometimes jump onto humans, bite them and suck blood - although they mainly suck blood from dogs and cats.
Scientific research
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pestpolicy.com/&#34;&gt;shows&lt;/a&gt;
that fleas will quickly move to another and
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pestpolicy.com/can-humans-carry-fleas-from-one-home-to-another/&#34;&gt;hitchhike people as they move to other houses&lt;/a&gt;
, just like the
&lt;a href=&#34;https://ohioline.osu.edu/factsheet/HYG-2081-11&#34;&gt;over 2,000 flea species&lt;/a&gt;
.
[amazon bestseller=&amp;ldquo;Best Fleas Killers&amp;rdquo; items=&amp;ldquo;2&amp;rdquo; template=&amp;ldquo;table&amp;rdquo;]&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Get Rid of Fleas (4 Steps and Tips)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/how-to-get-rid-of-fleas/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 23:08:41 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/how-to-get-rid-of-fleas/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We may earn a commission when you click and buy from Amazon.com.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The few
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pets.webmd.com/spot-fleas&#34;&gt;fleas&lt;/a&gt;
you see on your dog or cat only make up 5 percent of the total flea population in your home.
There is a whole bunch of them hiding on your pets bed, carpet, furniture, and even in your own bed. Here are some great methods on how to get rid of fleas fast.
Beneficial nematodes are highly effective in getting rid of fleas at home and in the yard. Unlike chemical treatments, the good news is that nematodes are completely safe for animals, pets, people, and plants.
[amazon bestseller=&amp;ldquo;Best Flea Killer&amp;rdquo; items=&amp;ldquo;2&amp;rdquo; template=&amp;ldquo;table&amp;rdquo;]
Read Also:
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pestpolicy.com/does-baking-soda-kill-fleas/&#34;&gt;Does Baking Soda Kill Fleas&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flea Eggs vs Dandruff - Tell Differences?</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/flea-eggs-vs-dandruff/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 22:51:47 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/flea-eggs-vs-dandruff/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We may earn a commission when you click and buy from Amazon.com.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Sometimes it is not easy to tell the difference between flea eggs vs. dandruff that appears on your pet&amp;rsquo;s skin - but
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pestpolicy.com/can-fleas-live-in-human-hair/&#34;&gt;fleas can&amp;rsquo;t live in human hair&lt;/a&gt;
.
***You are arming yourself with the knowledge to successfully determine which will significantly help you treat these conditions, including allergies. ***
***When you spot small white flakes on your pet&amp;rsquo;s skin, it might be easy to jump to conclusions without knowing the difference between dandruff and flea eggs - flea eggs can be killed by vacuuming while adults through flea bombs. ***
[amazon bestseller=&amp;ldquo;Best Flea Killers&amp;rdquo; items=&amp;ldquo;2&amp;rdquo; template=&amp;ldquo;table&amp;rdquo;]&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Does Rubbing Alcohol Kill Fleas?</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/does-rubbing-alcohol-kill-fleas/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 22:49:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/does-rubbing-alcohol-kill-fleas/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We may earn a commission when you click and buy from Amazon.com.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Having fleas around your home can be a real menace. They like to bite and cause itchiness on pets and humans. Does
&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.webmd.com/first-aid/ss/rubbing-alcohol-uses&#34;&gt;rubbing alcohol&lt;/a&gt;
kill fleas? Well, there are various methods to control them and alcohol is one of them.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;**So, does rubbing alcohol kill fleas? Well, Yes, rubbing alcohol is very effective in killing fleas. In fact, most disinfectants and some fleas spray at least contain some percentage of alcohol. Although it works, it is not a good idea to use it on your furry pet. **&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;What percent of alcohol kills fleas? Rubbing alcohol with 70% isopropyl alcohol offers excellent flea killing and disinfecting capability.
Though rubbing alcohol kills fleas, there is more that you need to know before you can get that spray can. Join me as we carefully analyze and understand more about what you can do and the various option available.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;details-does-rubbing-alcohol-kill-fleas-a-pet-safe-guide&#34;&gt;Details: Does Rubbing Alcohol Kill Fleas? A Pet-Safe Guide&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;can-i-use-rubbing-alcohol-on-my-pets&#34;&gt;Can I Use Rubbing Alcohol On My Pets?&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Rubbing alcohol kills fleas but if you want to it use on your pets, it poses a great risk to them. Rubbing alcohol has alcohol that is not carefully handled can bring serious problems in your home.
Alcohol is a highly flammable substance and you need to be extra cautious especially when using it indoors. As for pets, its a health risk factor that you cannot take lightly.
Though rubbing alcohol is effective in killing fleas, it is a bad idea to use it on pets. Health researchers have confirmed that apart from being toxic to your pet, it can also easily get absorbed into the pets skin.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Mix Cedar Oil for Pest Control</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/how-to-mix-cedar-oil-for-pest-control/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 22:42:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/how-to-mix-cedar-oil-for-pest-control/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We may earn a commission when you click and buy from Amazon.com.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Cedar oil (
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pestpolicy.com/essential-oils-for-bed-bugs/&#34;&gt;an essential oil&lt;/a&gt;
) is an effective pest repellent that works on a number of pests like mosquitoes, chiggers, gnats, chiggers, silverfish, fleas, ticks, and ants.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Cedar oil or cedarwood oil is extracted from cedar trees - i.e. from its needles, leaves, barks, and berries.
Besides the woody scent of the cedarwood oil is loved by many homeowners for keeping their houses smelling great. But it also has anti-inflammatory, antifungal, antiseptic, antispasmodic, and diuretic properties.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;In this article, Ive detailed how to mix cedar oil for pest control - it is safe to use around animals and garden trees but you must know the quantities to use.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;how-to-make-or-mix-cedar-oil-spray&#34;&gt;How to Make or Mix Cedar Oil Spray?&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Mix 120 ml (4 oz) of the cedar oil with 770 ml (26 Oz) of water.
First, pour the 120 mL of oil cedar oil into a sprayer that has a hose end.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Can I Use Baby Shampoo On My Cat?</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/can-i-use-baby-shampoo-on-my-cat/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 22:28:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/can-i-use-baby-shampoo-on-my-cat/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We may earn a commission when you click and buy from Amazon.com.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Well, it takes a well-trained cat to make it have a bath, otherwise, cats hate water. To bath or
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pestpolicy.com/what-do-flea-eggs-look-like-on-a-cat/&#34;&gt;remove fleas&lt;/a&gt;
, can I use baby shampoo on my cat? The whole process of
&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.wikihow.pet/Train-a-Cat-to-Take-a-Bath&#34;&gt;getting the cat to bathe&lt;/a&gt;
is difficult and you may find yourself using unskilful ways to get it into water.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Can I use baby shampoo on my cat? No, its not a good idea to use baby shampoo on cats. Baby shampoo is not designed for cat pets and may contain some chemicals that may harm the furry pet.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Some shampoos may also affect the cats skin by causing irritation and dry skin too. Instead, its a good idea to use the cat shampoos that are available in the market.&lt;/strong&gt;
In this detailed article, I have gathered all the necessary information about these shampoos. Also, get to learn more about the alternative shampoos that you can use on the cat.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;details-can-i-use-baby-shampoo-in-my-cat-a-healthy-pet&#34;&gt;Details: Can I Use Baby Shampoo In My Cat? A Healthy Pet&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;No, because baby shampoo is made for human skin which is very different from cat skin. Though cats are not good with water using shampoo is going to affect their skin by causing dryness and also irritation.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Is Borax Safe for Cats? Borax for Fleas</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/is-borax-safe-for-cats/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 22:21:53 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/is-borax-safe-for-cats/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We may earn a commission when you click and buy from Amazon.com.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hey Pet Lovers &amp;amp; Pet Parents,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Maybe you know that borax (sodium borate) is as a cleaner and antiseptic. Also, it&amp;rsquo;s used in toothpastes, water softener, pesticide, and mouthwashes.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Well, recently, we discussed how borax can be used
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pestpolicy.com/borax-flea-killer/&#34;&gt;as a flea killer&lt;/a&gt;
around the house. But how safe is it around
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pestpolicy.com/is-borax-safe-for-dogs/&#34;&gt;dogs&lt;/a&gt;
and cats.
**Is borax safe for cats? **
**Yes and No. **
**Cats, and kittens are more sensitive to the toxicity of borax than humans are - and if your cat ingests a large amount (5 grams and above), it damages their internal organs and skin which can cause poisoning, breathlessness, allergies, and death. **&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Did My Dog Get Fleas?</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/how-did-my-dog-get-fleas/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 22:20:51 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/how-did-my-dog-get-fleas/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We may earn a commission when you click and buy from Amazon.com.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Recently, I noticed my neighbor&amp;rsquo;s dog scratching and upon further inspection, I have served simply that on them.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;So my neighbor&amp;rsquo;s biggest question was how did my dog get fleas this is a question. Has it become a flea magnet? This is a question I&amp;rsquo;ll be answering in this article.
**But in brief, dogs can get fleas from other animals such as foxes, raccoons, and rodents, or from the house (from flea-infested blankets, rugs, and bedding), or even in outdoor spaces such as the neighbor&amp;rsquo;s yard, or flea-infested kennels. **&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;details-how-did-my-dog-get-fleas&#34;&gt;Details: How Did My Dog Get Fleas?&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;1-can-dogs-get-fleas-from-other-animals-wildlife-hotspot-1&#34;&gt;1. Can Dogs Get Fleas From Other Animals? Wildlife? Hotspot #1&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Yes, dogs can get fleas from other animals including wildlife, and household pets like cats.
Notably, cat fleas will not discriminate against their hosts and thus will bite even the dogs.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rentokil Pest Control Review in 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/rentokil-pest-control-review/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 21:52:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/rentokil-pest-control-review/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We may earn a commission when you click and buy from Amazon.com.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Rentokil provided various services for controlling and preventing pests like termites, roaches, and ants.
In this article, I will review Rentokil pest control on its
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pestpolicy.com/pest-control-near-me/&#34;&gt;suitability for bug control&lt;/a&gt;
.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;This company is among other pest control companies that are in the United States.
Let&amp;rsquo;s get into the review!
I will consider the reputation, pricing, and quality of services provided by the Rentokil pest control company.
Related:
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pestpolicy.com/orkin-pest-control-review/&#34;&gt;Orkin Pest Control Review&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;details-rentokil-pest-control-review&#34;&gt;Details: Rentokil Pest Control Review&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For starters, Rentokil company has many branches all over the world and it boasts off hundred plus years of experience in pest control.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Avoid Pests in Apartments</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/how-to-avoid-pests-in-apartments/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 21:46:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/how-to-avoid-pests-in-apartments/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We may earn a commission when you click and buy from Amazon.com.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Avoiding pests in apartments requires a combination of good hygiene, preventive measures, and prompt action if pests are spotted. Here are some effective strategies to keep your apartment pest-free:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;1-maintain-cleanliness&#34;&gt;1. Maintain Cleanliness&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Regular Cleaning&lt;/strong&gt;: Clean your apartment regularly, focusing on areas like the kitchen and bathroom where pests are more likely to be attracted.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Food Storage&lt;/strong&gt;: Store food in&lt;a href=&#34;https://pestpolicy.com/how-to-get-rid-of-cockroaches-in-apartments/&#34;&gt;airtight containers&lt;/a&gt;and keep countertops, floors, and tables free of crumbs and spills.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Proper Waste Management&lt;/strong&gt;: Dispose of garbage regularly and use trash cans with tight-fitting lids. Recycle and compost properly to minimize waste.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;2-seal-entry-points&#34;&gt;2. Seal Entry Points&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Seal Cracks and Gaps&lt;/strong&gt;: Inspect your apartment for cracks, holes, or gaps around windows, doors, and pipes, and seal them with caulk or weather stripping. This prevents pests from finding their way inside.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Screens&lt;/strong&gt;: Ensure that window and door screens are in good condition and fit tightly to keep pests out.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;3-control-moisture&#34;&gt;3. Control Moisture&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Fix Leaks&lt;/strong&gt;: Repair any leaks in plumbing to prevent damp areas that can attract pests like cockroaches and ants.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Proper Ventilation&lt;/strong&gt;: Use exhaust fans in the bathroom and kitchen to reduce humidity levels.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;4-eliminate-clutter&#34;&gt;4. Eliminate Clutter&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Declutter&lt;/strong&gt;: Reduce clutter in your apartment, as it provides hiding places for pests.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Storage&lt;/strong&gt;: Store items in plastic bins rather than cardboard boxes, which can attract pests.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;5-natural-repellents&#34;&gt;5. Natural Repellents&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Essential Oils&lt;/strong&gt;: Use essential oils like peppermint,&lt;a href=&#34;https://pestpolicy.com/how-to-use-eucalyptus-oil-for-bed-bugs/&#34;&gt;eucalyptus&lt;/a&gt;, or tea tree oil as natural repellents. Mix with water and spray around entry points and other areas where pests may enter.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Herbs&lt;/strong&gt;: Plant herbs such as basil, mint, or bay leaves in pots around your apartment to repel pests.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;6-regular-inspections&#34;&gt;6. Regular Inspections&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Routine Checks&lt;/strong&gt;: Regularly inspect your apartment for signs of pests, such as droppings, nests, or damage to food packaging - including&lt;a href=&#34;https://pestpolicy.com/best-steam-cleaner-for-fleas/&#34;&gt;steam cleaning&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Professional Help&lt;/strong&gt;: If you notice any signs of infestation, contact a professional pest control service promptly.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;7-collaborate-with-neighbors&#34;&gt;7. Collaborate with Neighbors&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Awareness&lt;/strong&gt;: Stay informed about common pests in your area and their habits.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Communication&lt;/strong&gt;: Work with your neighbors to ensure the entire building is taking preventive measures. Pests can easily move from one apartment to another, so a coordinated effort is more effective.
By following these steps and collaborating with your neighbors, you can create an environment that is less attractive to pests and quickly address any issues that arise.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Get Rid of Fleas in the House Fast</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/how-to-get-rid-of-fleas-in-the-house-fast/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 21:42:23 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/how-to-get-rid-of-fleas-in-the-house-fast/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We may earn a commission when you click and buy from Amazon.com.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Fleas are a major problem for many people in houses and offices. They can infest your carpet, furniture, and even your pets.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Some fleas fall off
&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.extension.colostate.edu/docs/pubs/insect/05600.pdf&#34;&gt;these wild animals&lt;/a&gt;
onto furniture, carpets, and bedding. So, on how to get rid of fleas in the house fast, you&amp;rsquo;ll want to:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Vacuum your carpets, furniture, and hard floors thoroughly. Be sure to change the bag in your vacuum cleaner often.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Wash all bedding, curtains, and clothes that have come into contact with fleas or their droppings using a temperature of at least 60C (140F) for all items.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Kill fleas on your pet by bathing them with a medicated shampoo, or using other methods, such as brushing their fur and giving them an oral medication&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Treat your yard to prevent the infestation from coming back.
[amazon bestseller=&amp;ldquo;Best Fleas Killer for Apartment&amp;rdquo; items=&amp;ldquo;2&amp;rdquo; template=&amp;ldquo;table&amp;rdquo;]&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;step-by-step---how-to-get-rid-of-fleas-in-the-house-fast&#34;&gt;Step by Step - How to Get Rid Of Fleas in the House Fast&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;step-1-use-flea-traps&#34;&gt;Step 1: Use Flea traps&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Flea traps offer an easy method to remove fleas from your home. They contain a chemical that attracts insects, which then die on their sticky surface.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Can You Use Dawn Dish Soap for Fleas?</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/dawn-dish-soap-for-fleas/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 21:39:43 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/dawn-dish-soap-for-fleas/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We may earn a commission when you click and buy from Amazon.com.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Witnessing my pets scratching, or even falling ill from flea bites is distressing. So, you&amp;rsquo;re wondering, can Dawn dish soap (the household detergent)
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pestpolicy.com/best-flea-treatment-for-puppies/&#34;&gt;really kill fleas&lt;/a&gt;
on your dogs or cats?
**Certainly! Dawn dish soap can kill fleas on your cats and dogs, but it&amp;rsquo;s a less effective flea control method compared to IGR sprays. Although it can easily remove grease and oil from wild birds, the flea-killing process is different. **&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Does Salt Kill Fleas? Remove Fleas with Salt!</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/does-salt-kill-fleas/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 21:33:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/does-salt-kill-fleas/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We may earn a commission when you click and buy from Amazon.com.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Does salt kill fleas? When looking to eradicate fleas, you are often confronted by a wealth of information, but what is correct and what is not? If you have fleas in the lawn - check this
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pestpolicy.com/best-flea-spray-for-yard/&#34;&gt;flea spray for the yard&lt;/a&gt;
.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In this article, we will be focusing on the truth behind whether salt kills fleas. Check these images of fleas and their larvae - here&amp;rsquo;s
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pestpolicy.com/what-do-fleas-look-like/&#34;&gt;what fleas look like&lt;/a&gt;
.
One of the significant points of concern when trying to
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pestpolicy.com/does-the-dryer-kill-fleas/&#34;&gt;rid your home of fleas are their eggs&lt;/a&gt;
. These are notoriously difficult to get rid of and can often be a source of the infestation returning.
[amazon bestseller=&amp;ldquo;Best Flea Killers&amp;rdquo; items=&amp;ldquo;2&amp;rdquo; template=&amp;ldquo;table&amp;rdquo;]&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Does Baking Soda Kill Fleas? Natural</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/does-baking-soda-kill-fleas/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 21:18:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/does-baking-soda-kill-fleas/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We may earn a commission when you click and buy from Amazon.com.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Does baking soda kill
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pestpolicy.com/what-do-fleas-look-like/&#34;&gt;fleas&lt;/a&gt;
? You may have heard that baking soda can be used to kill fleas, but is there any truth to this statement? Previously, I outlined how to use
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pestpolicy.com/best-flea-spray-for-yard/&#34;&gt;spray against yard fleas&lt;/a&gt;
.
In this article, we will delve a little deeper into this topic and find out once and for all. Ensure that you ensure that you know the
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pestpolicy.com/how-to-tell-if-you-have-fleas/&#34;&gt;signs of fleas&lt;/a&gt;
.
Following this simple method will bring you the best results and ensure that the fleas are eradicated from your home for gooda technique
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pestpolicy.com/how-to-kill-flea-eggs/&#34;&gt;for killing fleas&lt;/a&gt;
around the house with baking soda.
[amazon bestseller=&amp;ldquo;Best Flea Killers&amp;rdquo; items=&amp;ldquo;2&amp;rdquo; template=&amp;ldquo;table&amp;rdquo;]&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Kill Fleas on Dogs Naturally</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/how-to-kill-fleas-on-dogs-naturally-safe-and-fast/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 20:50:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/how-to-kill-fleas-on-dogs-naturally-safe-and-fast/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We may earn a commission when you click and buy from Amazon.com.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Natural flea control methods will not leave
&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.nrdc.org/sites/default/files/poisonsonpets.pdf&#34;&gt;dangerous chemical residues&lt;/a&gt;
on your dogs fur.
But, I know you might have used flea control chemicals such as NexGard, Advantage, flea collars,
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pestpolicy.com/best-fogger-for-fleas/&#34;&gt;flea bombs&lt;/a&gt;
, Frontline,
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pestpolicy.com/best-puppy-shampoo-for-fleas/&#34;&gt;dog flea shampoo&lt;/a&gt;
, etc.
Chemicals aside, today we discuss step by step process to control fleas on your dog naturally.
[amazon bestseller=&amp;ldquo;Best Fleas Killers on Dogs&amp;rdquo; items=&amp;ldquo;2&amp;rdquo; template=&amp;ldquo;table&amp;rdquo;]&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Get Rid of Silverfish</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/how-to-get-rid-of-silverfish/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 20:46:41 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/how-to-get-rid-of-silverfish/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We may earn a commission when you click and buy from Amazon.com.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Silverfish are small, wingless insects known for their silvery-grey appearance and fish-like movements. Though generally harmless, these pests can become a nuisance due to their tendency to damage books, wallpaper, and clothing, while feeding on starches and sugars.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you&amp;rsquo;ve noticed silverfish lurking in your home, it&amp;rsquo;s essential to address the issue promptly. In this blog, we&amp;rsquo;ll explore how to identify silverfish, what attracts them, and effective methods to
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pestpolicy.com/best-silverfish-killer/&#34;&gt;eliminate them&lt;/a&gt;
.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Long Does It Take To Break the Flea Life Cycle?</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/how-long-does-it-take-to-break-the-flea-life-cycle/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 20:39:52 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/how-long-does-it-take-to-break-the-flea-life-cycle/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We may earn a commission when you click and buy from Amazon.com.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;By breaking the flea life cycle, you will not only prevent further growth but also terminate breeding progress from that particular stage;
i.e. eggs, larvae, pupae, and adults.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;**On how long does it take to break the flea life cycle; the simple answer is about 1 to 6 months; for the different stages, this is how long it&amp;rsquo;ll take to break the flea cycle; egg stage break period (10-18 days), larvae stage break period (2 to 3 months), pupae stage break period (4 months.), adult stage break (5 months). **
[amazon bestseller=&amp;ldquo;Best Fleas Killers&amp;rdquo; items=&amp;ldquo;2&amp;rdquo; template=&amp;ldquo;table&amp;rdquo;]
Each stage may be broken independently though the elimination time varies from one stage to another.
When breaking the flea life cycle, it is important to identify the size of the infestation,
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pestpolicy.com/where-do-fleas-come-from/&#34;&gt;type of infested items&lt;/a&gt;
(is it pets, humans, or furniture), prevailing weather conditions, and possible source of infestation.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;how-long-does-it-take-to-break-the-flea-life-cycle&#34;&gt;How Long Does It Take To Break the Flea Life Cycle?&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Select a flea termination method that is environmentally friendly and safe for both pets &amp;amp; human beings. Remember, if you are new to the flea-breaking process; contract a professional exterminator for help.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why Do Flea Bites Itch? How Do I stop it?</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/why-do-flea-bites-itch/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 20:39:37 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/why-do-flea-bites-itch/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We may earn a commission when you click and buy from Amazon.com.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The legs of fleas have strong claws and proboscis (tiny needles) that&amp;rsquo;ll help the pest bite the skin of the hosts such as cats,
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pestpolicy.com/how-do-dogs-get-fleas/&#34;&gt;dogs&lt;/a&gt;
, and even humans.
**Why do flea bites itch? Well, fleas will bite humans and pets where they&amp;rsquo;ll secrete some saliva into the blood - which the host&amp;rsquo;s body and blood take as an allergen. **
**The immune system will send histamine to counter the allergen (flea saliva) and thus the chemical triggers itching and swelling. **&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Best Flea Collar for Dogs - Protect Your Pet</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/best-flea-collar-for-dogs/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 20:33:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/best-flea-collar-for-dogs/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We may earn a commission when you click and buy from Amazon.com.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Are you searching for the best flea collar to keep your dog free from pesky fleas and ticks?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Look no further! We&amp;rsquo;ve reviewed some of the top-rated flea collars on the market to help you make an informed decision for your furry friend&amp;rsquo;s well-being.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Related:
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pestpolicy.com/best-flea-shampoo-for-dogs/&#34;&gt;Flea shampoo for adult dogs&lt;/a&gt;
and
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pestpolicy.com/best-puppy-shampoo-for-fleas/&#34;&gt;puppies&lt;/a&gt;
.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;7-best-flea-collar-for-dogs---protect-your-pet&#34;&gt;7 Best Flea Collar for Dogs - Protect Your Pet&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;1-bayer-seresto-flea-collar-for-large-dogs&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B00B8CG602/?tag=p-policy-20&#34;&gt;1. Bayer Seresto Flea Collar for Large Dogs&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Bayer Seresto Flea Collar is a standout choice known for its long-lasting efficacy and convenience.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>7 Best Dog Brush for Short Hair Shedding 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/best-dog-brush-for-short-hair-shedding/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 20:32:49 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/best-dog-brush-for-short-hair-shedding/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We may earn a commission when you click and buy from Amazon.com.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Sometimes
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pestpolicy.com/best-vacuum-for-dog-hair/&#34;&gt;vacuuming&lt;/a&gt;
your carpets, floors, or sofas off any dog hair is never enough. It can get tiring and time-consuming, significantly when your dog is shedding excessive hair.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;But a good with a hairbrush, you can remove the excess hair thats on your dogs coat. Also, if your dog has short and smooth hair, it requires regular grooming.
But, finding the best dog brush for short hair shedding is a challenging task.
**See the top hair combs. **
[amazon bestseller=&amp;ldquo;Best Dog Brush for Short Hair Shedding&amp;rdquo; items=&amp;ldquo;2&amp;rdquo; template=&amp;ldquo;table&amp;rdquo;]&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;1-1-top-pick-chirpy-pets-grooming-brush-for-short--long-hair&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B0178VW3PS/?tag=p-policy-20&#34;&gt;1. #1 Top Pick: Chirpy-Pets Grooming Brush for Short &amp;amp; Long Hair&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;[amazon box=&amp;ldquo;B0178VW3PS&amp;rdquo; template=&amp;ldquo;horizontal&amp;rdquo;]
&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=16q683HLMXU&#34;&gt;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=16q683HLMXU&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What Attracts Fleas?</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/what-attracts-fleas/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 20:27:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/what-attracts-fleas/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We may earn a commission when you click and buy from Amazon.com.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Fleas will pose a hazard (health) to both pets and humans. So, ensure to
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pestpolicy.com/best-flea-treatment-for-cats/&#34;&gt;flea-treat your cats&lt;/a&gt;
&amp;amp; dogs -  to avoid that massive infestation.
**But what attracts fleas? As they find a host, cat fleas are mainly attracted by thermal and visual stimuli (heat &amp;amp; light). Others include C02 &amp;amp; exhaled breath from humans, movement, darkness, food, and warmth. **
&lt;strong&gt;Attraction Cues:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>7 Best Flea Carpet Powders - Flea-Free Home 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/best-flea-carpet-powder/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 20:11:30 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/best-flea-carpet-powder/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We may earn a commission when you click and buy from Amazon.com.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you have pets like cats or dogs, fleas are an inevitable problem. While treating your pets is essential, its not enough to fully eliminate fleas. These pests often find their way into your carpets, floors, furniture, and even bedding.
To tackle this issue,
&lt;strong&gt;flea carpet powders&lt;/strong&gt;
are a highly effective solution. They not only kill adult fleas but also target eggs, larvae, and pupae, breaking the flea lifecycle.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Get Rid of Flea Eggs on Cats?</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/how-to-get-rid-of-flea-eggs-on-cats/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 19:52:37 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/how-to-get-rid-of-flea-eggs-on-cats/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We may earn a commission when you click and buy from Amazon.com.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;dl&gt;
&lt;dt&gt;Previously, I discussed the&lt;/dt&gt;
&lt;dt&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://pestpolicy.com/best-fogger-for-fleas/&#34;&gt;top flea foggers&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/dt&gt;
&lt;dt&gt;, but we&amp;rsquo;ll cover how you can get rid of cat flea eggs in this post.&lt;/dt&gt;
&lt;dt&gt;In short, to get rid of flea eggs on cats, Bathe the&lt;/dt&gt;
&lt;dt&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://pestpolicy.com/best-flea-shampoo-for-cats/&#34;&gt;cat with a flea shampoo&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/dt&gt;
&lt;dt&gt;, flea comb the cat&amp;rsquo;s fur (with tightly-spaced tines), give oral&lt;/dt&gt;
&lt;dt&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://pestpolicy.com/best-flea-treatment-for-cats/&#34;&gt;cat flea medicine&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/dt&gt;
&lt;dt&gt;such as lufenuron, and kill adult fleas using cat medication such as nitenpyram twice per week.&lt;/dt&gt;
&lt;dt&gt;&lt;strong&gt;First off&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/dt&gt;
&lt;dd&gt;Whats the negative effect of having
&lt;a href=&#34;https://entnemdept.ufl.edu/creatures/urban/occas/catflea.htm&#34;&gt;fleas on your cat&lt;/a&gt;
or kittens? Notably, fleas will not just cause itching on your feline friends but will also trigger anemia, hair loss and could introduce tapeworms.
[amazon bestseller=&amp;ldquo;Best Fleas Killer for Cats&amp;rdquo; items=&amp;ldquo;2&amp;rdquo; template=&amp;ldquo;table&amp;rdquo;]&lt;/dd&gt;
&lt;/dl&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;how-to-get-rid-of-flea-eggs-on-cats-step-by-step&#34;&gt;**How to Get Rid of Flea Eggs on Cats Step By Step **&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;But, what color are flea eggs on a cat? Well, flea eggs have a rounded oval shape. If freshly deposited,
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pestpolicy.com/does-the-dryer-kill-fleas/&#34;&gt;flea eggs&lt;/a&gt;
will look translucent white but change to pearl-like and opaque with time. Experts consider
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pestpolicy.com/flea-eggs-vs-dandruff/&#34;&gt;flea eggs as dandruff&lt;/a&gt;
flakes, salt grains, and tiny pearls shaped.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Does Capstar Work? Flea Treatment</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/how-does-capstar-work-flea-treatment/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 19:51:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/how-does-capstar-work-flea-treatment/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We may earn a commission when you click and buy from Amazon.com.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you need to keep fleas off your cats and dogs, then the Capstar Flea Tablets is highly recommended by pet owners and vets - even when you
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pestpolicy.com/dog-has-fleas-and-sleeps-in-my-bed/&#34;&gt;sleep with flea-infested dogs in your bed&lt;/a&gt;
.
Capstar is manufactured by a company known as Novartis which is a DIY flea killer that targets adult fleas in cats and dogs.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What Do Baby Fleas Look Like? 9 Key Tips</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/what-do-baby-fleas-look-like/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 19:12:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/what-do-baby-fleas-look-like/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We may earn a commission when you click and buy from Amazon.com.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;What do baby fleas look like? Check these baby flea (larvae) videos, images, and pictures - check their color and size.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Flea larvae are worm-like, leg-less, off-white in color, and measure about  inches with a tiny head. You&amp;rsquo;ll mainly find them during a&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.canr.msu.edu/ipm/uploads/files/Fleas.pdf&#34;&gt;flea infestation&lt;/a&gt;on second-hand furniture and pet sleeping.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;*The short answer on &amp;ldquo;What do baby fleas look like?&amp;rdquo; has four distinct phases - pupal, larvae, eggs, and adults all look differentFlea larval stage measures between 2.8 mm to 4.9 mm. The larvae are worm-like, white, or semi-transparent in color. *&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;*Fleas in the pupal stage look lumpy and crusty with an irregular shape plus have a silky cocoon. *
*Flea eggs measure about anywhere from 0.04 millimeters plus have dry and smooth skin that is off-white. *
[amazon bestseller=&amp;ldquo;Best Flea Killer&amp;rdquo; items=&amp;ldquo;2&amp;rdquo; template=&amp;ldquo;table&amp;rdquo;]
Read Also:
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pestpolicy.com/best-flea-spray-for-yard/&#34;&gt;What&amp;rsquo;s the best flea spray for your yard&lt;/a&gt;
.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What Do Flea Larvae Look Like?</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/what-do-flea-larvae-look-like/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 19:04:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/what-do-flea-larvae-look-like/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We may earn a commission when you click and buy from Amazon.com.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;What do flea larvae look like? If you are concerned that you may have a flea problem, you are likely looking out for various signs.
This article will look at what you might see when spotting flea larvae and what action to take. Read also;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pestpolicy.com/what-do-flea-larvae-eat/&#34;&gt;what do flea larvae eat&lt;/a&gt;
.
Fleas go through four different stages during their life cycle, the second of these stages being the
&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.petmd.com/dog/parasites/6-facts-about-flea-larvae-you-need-know&#34;&gt;larvae stage&lt;/a&gt;
.
[amazon bestseller=&amp;ldquo;Best Flea Killers&amp;rdquo; items=&amp;ldquo;2&amp;rdquo; template=&amp;ldquo;table&amp;rdquo;]&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Top 7 Best Dog Backpack Carrier for Hiking</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/best-dog-backpack-carrier-for-hiking/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 19:00:39 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/best-dog-backpack-carrier-for-hiking/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We may earn a commission when you click and buy from Amazon.com.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When choosing the best dog backpack carrier for hiking, you can consider things like comfort, durability, size, and safety. These factors ensure that both you and your canine companion have an enjoyable and safe experience on the trail.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;key-factors-to-consider&#34;&gt;Key Factors to Consider&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;**1. Comfort **
Some products, like the
&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B0CSG5YRZF/?tag=p-policy-20&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;K9 Sport Sack AIR Plus&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;
, prioritize comfort for both the dog and the owner. This carrier has padded shoulder straps and back panels, reducing strain during long hikes.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Does Heat Kill Fleas?</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/does-heat-kill-fleas/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 18:52:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/does-heat-kill-fleas/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We may earn a commission when you click and buy from Amazon.com.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Fleas are tiny
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pestpolicy.com/what-do-baby-fleas-look-like/&#34;&gt;flat-bodied external parasites&lt;/a&gt;
thatll feed on blood from mammals and birds.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Fleas will mainly hide floor cracks, beddings and furniture  and thus it is challenging to control them. But,
*does heat kill fleas? *
**In summary, YES, heat will kill fleas, their eggs, and larvae  particularly heat from steaming, laundering, dryers, professional heat treatment (Entotherm), and flea heaters. So, lets get into the details! **&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Top 5 Best Flea Collars For Your Cat</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/best-flea-collar-for-cats/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 18:51:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/best-flea-collar-for-cats/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We may earn a commission when you click and buy from Amazon.com.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When choosing the best flea collar for cats, you can consider things like effectiveness, safety, duration of protection, and ease of use.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;These factors play a crucial role in ensuring your cat remains flea-free and comfortable while wearing the collar. Related:
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pestpolicy.com/best-flea-treatment-for-cats/&#34;&gt;Spot-on flea treatments&lt;/a&gt;
.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;key-factors-to-consider&#34;&gt;Key Factors to Consider&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;1-effectiveness&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;1. Effectiveness&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The primary function of a flea collar is to repel and kill fleas. Some products, like the
&lt;strong&gt;Seresto Flea and Tick Collar&lt;/strong&gt;
, offer nearly instant protection by starting to kill fleas within 24 hours of application.
Others, like the
&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B00B8CG5NK/?tag=p-policy-20&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Hartz UltraGuard Plus&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;
, may take a few days to reach full effectiveness but can still provide long-lasting relief. When considering effectiveness, its essential to look at
how quickly the collar starts working and how long it continues to protect your cat.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flea Life Cycle &amp; Lifespan Stages: 7 Facts</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/flea-life-cycle/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 17:40:43 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/flea-life-cycle/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We may earn a commission when you click and buy from Amazon.com.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The flea life cycle consists of four stages: egg, flea larva, pupa, and the adult. Fleas will live from a few weeks to several months given optimal humidity and temperature (70 percent and 7085F).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fleas feed on blood, and the cycle of a flea&amp;rsquo;s life is closely aligned with that need.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Flea eggs hatch into larvae, which then turn into pupae before emerging as adults. The adults lay eggs as they feed to continue the cycle.
Understanding
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pestpolicy.com/how-long-does-it-take-to-break-the-flea-life-cycle/&#34;&gt;the flea life cycle&lt;/a&gt;
functions can help you better protect your pet and home from these parasites!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In this article, we&amp;rsquo;ll take a look at the cycle of their life. Also, check this
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pestpolicy.com/can-humans-carry-fleas-from-one-home-to-another/&#34;&gt;fleas movement guide&lt;/a&gt;
.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>7 Best Flea Spray for Yard 2025 Reviewed</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/best-flea-spray-for-yard/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 17:31:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/best-flea-spray-for-yard/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We may earn a commission when you click and buy from Amazon.com.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Fleas can be annoying to both humans and pets. Worse still, they could cause severe health complications if not controlled - try the best flea spray for the yard.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;There are different types of sprays that can be used to kill and keep fleas off your yard.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Home improvement entails many things, and pest control is one of them.
However, with many products on the market, knowing what would work best might be a considerable challenge.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;reviews-top-7-best-flea-spray-for-yard-in-2025&#34;&gt;Reviews: Top 7 Best Flea Spray For Yard in 2025&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;1-wondercide-yard-and-garden-flea-and-tick-control&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B00V7C37F0/?tag=p-policy-20&#34;&gt;1. Wondercide Yard and Garden Flea and Tick Control&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This easy-to-use flea and tick spray uses natural ingredients to protect your home and garden from infestation.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Does Chlorine Safely Kill Fleas on Cats?</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/does-chlorine-safely-kill-fleas-on-cats/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 17:23:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/does-chlorine-safely-kill-fleas-on-cats/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We may earn a commission when you click and buy from Amazon.com.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Fleas got your cat down? Forget the pool chlorine  it&amp;rsquo;s a recipe for disaster, and it can be downright dangerous for your precious kitty.
Even small amounts of chlorine can be harmful to cats. Here why:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;**Skin and eye irritation:**Chlorine can cause painful burns and itchy rashes on your cat&amp;rsquo;s delicate skin and eyes.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;**Digestive distress:**Ingesting chlorine can lead to vomiting, diarrhea, and even internal damage.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;**Respiratory problems:**Inhaling chlorine fumes can cause coughing, wheezing, and difficulty breathing.
Let&amp;rsquo;s explore why chlorine is a no-go and discover safe, effective ways to keep your feline free of these pesky parasites.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;why-chlorine-is-a-no-go-for-feline-flea-solutions&#34;&gt;Why Chlorine is a No-Go for Feline Flea Solutions&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;1. Chlorine&amp;rsquo;s Toxic Touch:&lt;/strong&gt;
Even small amounts of chlorine can be harmful to cats. It can irritate their skin and eyes, cause digestive upset, and even lead to respiratory problems.
Remember, your cat&amp;rsquo;s health is always a top priority, so choose solutions designed specifically for their well-being.
&lt;strong&gt;2. Fleas Slip Through the Chlorine Slipstream:&lt;/strong&gt;
While chlorine might knock out some adult fleas on contact, it won&amp;rsquo;t reach the eggs and pupae  the real culprits behind the flea fiesta. These resilient stages stay hidden, ready to hatch a new generation of itchy invaders.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>7 Best Flea Combs for Cats in 2025 Reviewed</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/best-flea-comb-for-cats/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 17:17:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/best-flea-comb-for-cats/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We may earn a commission when you click and buy from Amazon.com.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In this post, Ive reviewed the
best flea combs
for cats.
Flea Combs are safer and simple flea control solutions when liked to
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pestpolicy.com/best-flea-spray-for-yard/&#34;&gt;flea spray&lt;/a&gt;
, boric acid, or flea shampoo.
With these combs, you can easily
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pestpolicy.com/how-to-use-a-flea-comb/&#34;&gt;find and remove fleas&lt;/a&gt;
, flea dirt, and eggs.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Luckily, the combs are non-chemical flea control methods and suitable for kittens and puppies with sensitive or damaged skin.
**Summary: **
To stop scratching and itching in your cats &amp;amp; dogs due to fleas, check these flea combs.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;1-safari-flea-comb--double-row-tines-metal-flea-comb&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B0002RJMAK/?tag=p-policy-20&#34;&gt;1. Safari Flea Comb  Double Row Tines (Metal) Flea Comb&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Top on the list of the best flea combs for cats and dogs is the safari flea comb. Initially, I noted that my cat was
dandruffy and scabby in addition to having fleas. In addition to pre-brushing the cats fur, I recommend the Safari
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pestpolicy.com/does-salt-kill-fleas/&#34;&gt;Flea Comb to search and remove&lt;/a&gt;
fleas.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What is blep in pets Cats and dogs</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/what-is-blep-in-pets-cats-and-dogs/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 16:51:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/what-is-blep-in-pets-cats-and-dogs/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We may earn a commission when you click and buy from Amazon.com.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Cats never cease to amaze with their adorable but sometimes bizarre behaviors. One such behavior is
&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.reddit.com/r/Blep/&#34;&gt;blep&lt;/a&gt;
(as described on the inter-webs), particularly among cats and dogs. So, we asked our pet behavior expert: What is blep in pets (cats and dogs), you ask?
Well, no one really knows the origin of this blep word, but you might already know how it looks like. It&amp;rsquo;s when your cat or dog unconsciously sticks out its tongue, particularly when they forget to take it back. Most time, cats blep while they are resting.
So, blep, it&amp;rsquo;s usually not anything to worry about. But, blep can also significant damage to the face, teeth, or jaw. Read Also:
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pestpolicy.com/best-flea-treatment-for-dogs/&#34;&gt;Flea Treatment for Dogs&lt;/a&gt;
.
[amazon bestseller=&amp;ldquo;Best Cat Food&amp;rdquo; items=&amp;ldquo;2&amp;rdquo; template=&amp;ldquo;table&amp;rdquo;]
&lt;a href=&#34;https://twitter.com/MeowMoeDotCom/status/1030926427850452993&#34;&gt;https://twitter.com/MeowMoeDotCom/status/1030926427850452993&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Where Do Fleas Live? 7 Common Hiding Places?</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/where-do-fleas-live/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 16:46:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/where-do-fleas-live/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We may earn a commission when you click and buy from Amazon.com.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;code&gt;We may earn a commission when you click and buy from Amazon.com&lt;/code&gt;.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Where do fleas live? Often-times,
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pestpolicy.com/what-do-fleas-look-like/&#34;&gt;fleas&lt;/a&gt;
will cause a scare in your home and
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pestpolicy.com/best-flea-spray-for-yard/&#34;&gt;yard - but you can control these bugs&lt;/a&gt;
. Equally important is that fleas will be challenging to track them down and maintain too.
*In Summary, fleas are mainly ectoparasites &amp;amp; live on pet hosts where they&amp;rsquo;ll suck blood, fleas mate, and ultimately lay eggs. They&amp;rsquo;ll live on the pet hosts and wildlife up-to when they&amp;rsquo;re brushed off, fall off or die. *
&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=g6vMqrhltxQ&#34;&gt;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=g6vMqrhltxQ&lt;/a&gt;
See top quality flea sprays.
[amazon bestseller=&amp;ldquo;Best Flea Spray&amp;rdquo; items=&amp;ldquo;2&amp;rdquo; template=&amp;ldquo;table&amp;rdquo;]&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Capstar Flea Treatment Reviews - Oral Flea Treatment</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/capstar-flea-treatment-reviews/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 16:45:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/capstar-flea-treatment-reviews/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We may earn a commission when you click and buy from Amazon.com.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Capstar tablets are formulated to kill the various adult flea species and they&amp;rsquo;re meant for use on large dogs, cats, puppies, and kittens that are over 2 pounds in weight.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;For most of these pests, one dose of the Capstar tablets will kill most of the fleas - but you must use other techniques to&lt;a href=&#34;https://pestpolicy.com/how-long-does-it-take-to-break-the-flea-life-cycle/&#34;&gt;break the flea lifecycle&lt;/a&gt;.
In this article, I will online and discuss some of the Capstar flea treatment reviews that are accessible to me.
Let&amp;rsquo;s dig in!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;details-capstar-flea-treatment-reviews&#34;&gt;Details: Capstar Flea Treatment Reviews&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;review-1-highly-effective-oral-flea-treatment&#34;&gt;Review #1: Highly Effective Oral Flea Treatment&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I can say that I finally landed on an effective and still
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pestpolicy.com/capstar-flea-tablets-for-small-dogs&#34;&gt;safe flea killer - for small dogs&lt;/a&gt;
and large dogs plus cats.
Compared to other over-the-counter pesticides and repellents that I had used trying to control the fleas on my pets, Capstar tablets proved much better.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Does Lambda Cyhalothrin Kill Fleas?</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/does-lambda-cyhalothrin-kill-fleas/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 16:43:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/does-lambda-cyhalothrin-kill-fleas/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We may earn a commission when you click and buy from Amazon.com.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://npic.orst.edu/factsheets/l_cyhalogen.pdf&#34;&gt;Lambda Cyhalothrin&lt;/a&gt;
is a synthetic Pyrethroid chemical that is popular for pest control.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The ingredient is employed in a number of lawn and pest solutions that have been certified for controlling different problematic insects.
&lt;strong&gt;But does lambda-cyhalothrin kill fleas? YES, the synthetic pyrethroid is packaged in liquids, pellets, powders forms and it kills a range of outdoor and indoor pests such as fleas, bees, wasps, bed bugs, earwigs, scorpions, silverfish, ticks, flies, termites, spiders, cockroaches, and ants.&lt;/strong&gt;
In this article, I&amp;rsquo;ll get deeper into the products that have Lambda-cyhalothrin for your
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pestpolicy.com/borax-flea-killer/&#34;&gt;DIY pest control&lt;/a&gt;
. Let&amp;rsquo;s get into it.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;details-how-lambda-cyhalothrin-is-used-for-pest-control&#34;&gt;Details: How Lambda-Cyhalothrin Is Used For Pest Control&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As described earlier lambda-cyhalothrin is classified as a pyrethroid (synthetic one) meaning that it is a replica of pyrethrum (natural) that comes from a chrysanthemum flower.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Top 7 Best IGR for Fleas Reviewed</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/best-igr-for-fleas/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 16:42:44 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/best-igr-for-fleas/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We may earn a commission when you click and buy from Amazon.com.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When choosing the best IGR (Insect Growth Regulator) for fleas, you can consider things like effectiveness, safety, ease of use, and the specific environment where it will be applied.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;These factors help ensure that you pick a product that meets your needs while providing long-lasting protection against
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pestpolicy.com/flea-life-cycle/&#34;&gt;flea infestation&lt;/a&gt;
.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;key-factors-to-consider&#34;&gt;Key Factors to Consider&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;1. Effectiveness Against Different Flea Life Stages&lt;/strong&gt;
Some products, like
&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B00C2R54QY/?tag=p-policy-20&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;MKG NyGuard IGR&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;
, are highly effective against various flea life stages, including eggs, larvae, and pupae.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>7 Best Flea Drops for Cats 2025 Reviewed</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/best-flea-drops-for-cats/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 16:35:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/best-flea-drops-for-cats/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We may earn a commission when you click and buy from Amazon.com.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Searching for the best flea drops for cats can be an overwhelming task due to the many options available for sale online and at your local pet stores.
You may have read many
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pestpolicy.com/best-flea-treatment-for-cats/&#34;&gt;cat flea treatment&lt;/a&gt;
reviews, which have been confusing for a person who&amp;rsquo;s not a professional exterminator.
We want to simplify the process for you by sharing with you five of the best flea drops for cats based on our research and experience.
**Check the top flea drops.  **
[amazon bestseller=&amp;ldquo;Best Flea Drops for Cats&amp;rdquo; items=&amp;ldquo;2&amp;rdquo; template=&amp;ldquo;table&amp;rdquo;]&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Top 9 Best Spray for Sand Fleas Reviewed</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/best-spray-for-sand-fleas/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 16:15:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/best-spray-for-sand-fleas/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We may earn a commission when you click and buy from Amazon.com.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When choosing the best spray for sand fleas, you can consider factors like effectiveness, safety, ease of use, and duration of protection.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;These key factors will help ensure you select a product that not only eliminates sand fleas but also provides long-lasting protection for you and your loved ones.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;key-factors-to-consider&#34;&gt;Key Factors to Consider&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;1-effectiveness-against-sand-fleas-&#34;&gt;**1. Effectiveness Against Sand Fleas **&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Some products, like
&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B01M8GFPXG/?tag=p-policy-20&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Wondercide Flea &amp;amp; Tick Spray&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;
, are known for their powerful, plant-based formula that kills and repels sand fleas on contact. For those looking for a chemical-based alternative,
&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B004H89KFC/?tag=p-policy-20&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Repel 100 Insect Repellent&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;
contains DEET and is incredibly effective against sand fleas and
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pestpolicy.com/best-no-see-ums-repellent/&#34;&gt;other parasites&lt;/a&gt;
, providing long-lasting protection.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Get Rid of Sand Fleas - 7 Tips</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/how-to-get-rid-of-sand-fleas/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 15:51:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/how-to-get-rid-of-sand-fleas/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We may earn a commission when you click and buy from Amazon.com.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Spring is here and with it,
&lt;a href=&#34;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Tunga_penetrans&#34;&gt;sand fleas&lt;/a&gt;
. In this article, I&amp;rsquo;ll provide tips on how to get rid of sand fleas.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;These tiny parasitic bugs inhabit humid beaches or coastal climates and they&amp;rsquo;re known for their bite, itchiness, and difficulty to get rid of.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Sand fleas can bite both dogs and cats, as well as birds and humans. These itch-inducing bites can cause fatal infections or recurring skin conditions.
So, inspect your pets, luggage, and home for sand fleas and undertake appropriate steps to prevent re-infestation. Related:
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pestpolicy.com/best-flea-spray-for-yard/&#34;&gt;Flea Spray for Garden&lt;/a&gt;
.
[amazon bestseller=&amp;ldquo;Sand Fleas Killers&amp;rdquo; items=&amp;ldquo;2&amp;rdquo; template=&amp;ldquo;table&amp;rdquo;]&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;approach-1-identify-the-sand-fleas---how-to-get-rid-of-sand-fleas&#34;&gt;Approach 1: Identify the Sand Fleas - How to Get Rid of Sand Fleas&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;step-1-how-do-you-identify-the-sand-fleas&#34;&gt;Step 1: How do you identify the sand fleas?&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A sand flea looks like a sand particle and is the size of a grain of rice or a speck of salt. - you&amp;rsquo;ll find it near the sand-water interface or in moist areas.
While sand fleas are tiny insects that you may not be able to spot with your naked eye, it is still possible to see with a closer look.
When you&amp;rsquo;re walking on sand, sand fleas are most likely to climb onto your legs and feet. If you&amp;rsquo;re wearing shoes, they&amp;rsquo;ll crawl up to your ankles.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What Do Flea Eggs Look Like on a Cat?</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/what-do-flea-eggs-look-like-on-a-cat/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 15:44:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/what-do-flea-eggs-look-like-on-a-cat/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We may earn a commission when you click and buy from Amazon.com.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you are a pet lover, you have to be very keen on identifying fleas from them. What do flea eggs look like on a cat?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fleas eggs are&lt;a href=&#34;https://entnemdept.ufl.edu/creatures/urban/occas/catflea.htm&#34;&gt;very tiny in size&lt;/a&gt;. They are also shiny and visible with human eyes. They are approximately 0.019 by 0.011 inches which is nearly the size of the salt grain.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;As for their color - Are flea eggs Black or white? - fleas vary from being translucent to white -&lt;a href=&#34;https://pestpolicy.com/what-do-fleas-look-like/&#34;&gt;see these pictures of fleas&lt;/a&gt;. If you started suspecting your cat or dog is having fleas, there are so many ways to confirm your doubts.
Some cats and dogs also have light furs which may make it difficult to trace these flea eggs but you can use the methods listed below to help makes things easier. Related:
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pestpolicy.com/does-flea-treatment-burn-cats-skin/&#34;&gt;Will Flea Treatment Burn Cats Skin&lt;/a&gt;
?
[amazon bestseller=&amp;ldquo;Best Flea Killers&amp;rdquo; items=&amp;ldquo;2&amp;rdquo; template=&amp;ldquo;table&amp;rdquo;]&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;what-do-flea-eggs-look-like-on-a-cat&#34;&gt;What Do Flea Eggs Look Like On A Cat?&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;What do flea eggs look like to the human eye? Because cats are furry pets, you need to be keen when it comes to identifying fleas and their eggs. This is also applicable to dogs too.
These pets are the biggest carriers and breeders of fleas in our homes and any effort to control fleas is a big win for eliminating fleas in your home.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Get Rid of Fleas on Humans</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/how-to-get-rid-of-fleas-on-humans/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 15:20:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/how-to-get-rid-of-fleas-on-humans/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We may earn a commission when you click and buy from Amazon.com.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Fleas are common pests with hairy pets like cats and dogs but they can also attack humans. There are over 2000 species and some species also attack humans. This guide on how to get rid of fleas on humans has all you need to know.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;**Unlike fury pets, fleas attacking humans like to hide either on the clothing or hair. To get rid of them, you need to wash your hair with anti-fleas products. **&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Taking a bath with a flea shampoo will also help. Ultimately, knowing their source and other infested areas will do much good when eliminating them.&lt;/strong&gt;
Fleas are tiny parasites that will attack and suck human and pet blood. Even before you get hold of these tiny pests,
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pestpolicy.com/how-to-get-rid-of-fleas-on-clothes-and-bedding/&#34;&gt;it jumps into hiding&lt;/a&gt;
.
[amazon bestseller=&amp;ldquo;Best Fleas Killer&amp;rdquo; items=&amp;ldquo;2&amp;rdquo; template=&amp;ldquo;table&amp;rdquo;]&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;details-how-to-get-rid-of-fleas-on-humans&#34;&gt;Details: How to Get Rid Of Fleas on Humans&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Fleas are tiny and very fast to jump off when they have been exposed. Because they are parasites, they like to suck blood from their host.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>7 Best Cordless Vacuum for Pet Hair 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/best-cordless-vacuum-for-pet-hair/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 15:18:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/best-cordless-vacuum-for-pet-hair/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We may earn a commission when you click and buy from Amazon.com.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Sharing a house with pets comes at a cost. Pets such as dogs and cats shed hair on bare floors, upholstery, carpet, crevices, and so on.
A
&lt;a href=&#34;https://patents.google.com/patent/US10238250B2/en&#34;&gt;cordless vacuum&lt;/a&gt;
will enable you to
&lt;a href=&#34;https://hisense.co.uk/blog/do-you-know-the-benefits-of-cordless-vacuum-cleaner/&#34;&gt;reach every corner&lt;/a&gt;
of the house and remove pet hair and other debris. But which is the best cordless vacuum for pet hair?
After going through several
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pestpolicy.com/best-vacuum-for-dog-hair/&#34;&gt;vacuum cleaners for dog hair&lt;/a&gt;
in the market, I have narrowed it down to
&lt;strong&gt;7 products ideal for vacuuming pet hair&lt;/strong&gt;
.
[amazon bestseller=&amp;ldquo;Best Cordless Vacuum for Pet Hair&amp;rdquo; items=&amp;ldquo;2&amp;rdquo; template=&amp;ldquo;table&amp;rdquo;]&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Can Fleas Live in Human Hair? (7 Quick Tips)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/can-fleas-live-in-human-hair/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 15:16:44 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/can-fleas-live-in-human-hair/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We may earn a commission when you click and buy from Amazon.com.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://pestpolicy.com/do-fleas-bite-humans/&#34;&gt;Flea bites on humans&lt;/a&gt;
from cat fleas, dog fleas, rat fleas cause irritation, itching, pain, and distress - they&amp;rsquo;ll bite calves, ankles, lower legs, and feet.
But are flea bites on the human scalp common? Can these pests create a permanent residence in your hair? So,
*can fleas live in human hair? *&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;*In summary, when you sleep with a pet, fleas can temporarily hide in dense or full frizzy human hair (like Remy human hair). This is common when they can&amp;rsquo;t find their preferred hosts like cats or dogs. *&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;*While female fleas have lower fertility inside the human hair, human blood is not preferred by fleas. Thus you won&amp;rsquo;t find flea eggs laid or developing to other stages in the flea cycle. *
*However, chigoe or human fleas (found in tropical areas) will prefer human hosts. Human fleas will burrow into the human skin, suck blood, and lay eggs in their numbers. See the flea spray. *
[amazon bestseller=&amp;ldquo;Best Flea Spray&amp;rdquo; items=&amp;ldquo;2&amp;rdquo; template=&amp;ldquo;table&amp;rdquo;]&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;details-can-fleas-live-in-human-hair-7-quick-tips&#34;&gt;Details: Can Fleas Live in Human Hair? (7 Quick Tips)&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Usually,
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pestpolicy.com/how-long-do-fleas-live-on-humans/&#34;&gt;fleas won&amp;rsquo;t stay or live in human&lt;/a&gt;
hair. But when humans sleep with pets (including cats and dogs), the fleas may jump off, at night, onto the human hair and
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pestpolicy.com/can-fleas-live-on-clothes/&#34;&gt;clothes&lt;/a&gt;
.
The
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pestpolicy.com/flea-repellent-for-humans/&#34;&gt;fleas jump onto the human&lt;/a&gt;
scalp, where they&amp;rsquo;ll feed on your blood - a good blood meal despite not being like the pet&amp;rsquo;s blood meal.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Big are Fleas? Size in Flea Life Cycle</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/how-big-are-fleas/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 15:06:45 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/how-big-are-fleas/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We may earn a commission when you click and buy from Amazon.com.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Fleas are
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pestpolicy.com/what-do-fleas-look-like/&#34;&gt;tiny insects (order Siphonaptera)&lt;/a&gt;
that exist parasitically (sucking blood) on hosts birds, mammals, and pets like dogs &amp;amp; cats.
Key identifies of the fleas include their color which can vary from black, reddish-brown, or brown; visible with naked eyes but may
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pestpolicy.com/does-vacuuming-kill-flea-larvae/&#34;&gt;hide in&lt;/a&gt;
*furniture &amp;amp; carpet fibers, and animals coats or fur. *
**But how big are fleas? Adult fleas are dark brown and will measure about 1.4 - 3.3 millimeters in body length. **
**But male fleas have a shorter body (average 1 millimeter) compared to females (average 2.5 millimeters). Despite being tiny, fleas can be seen through naked eyes. **
Related:
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pestpolicy.com/best-flea-spray-for-yard/&#34;&gt;Commercial Grade Flea Killer for Yard&lt;/a&gt;
.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Top 7 Best Silverfish Repellent for 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/best-silverfish-repellent/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 15:05:17 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/best-silverfish-repellent/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We may earn a commission when you click and buy from Amazon.com.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;On the best silverfish repellent, you will not only acquire a quality product but also reduce the hassles of searching for the top choice solution.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The current market is flooded with spray brands, which if you&amp;rsquo;re not careful, you may end up acquiring ineffective repellents or&lt;a href=&#34;https://pestpolicy.com/best-silverfish-traps/&#34;&gt;traps.&lt;/a&gt;
During selection, consider factors like quantity, action time, residue effects (if any), user mechanism, packaging form (powder, liquid, or compressed gas?), and the environmental impact upon use.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;reviews-top-7-best-silverfish-repellent-in-2025&#34;&gt;Reviews: Top 7 Best Silverfish Repellent in 2025&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;[amazon bestseller=&amp;ldquo;Best Silverfish Repellent&amp;rdquo; items=&amp;ldquo;2&amp;rdquo; template=&amp;ldquo;table&amp;rdquo;]&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Is Borax Safe for Dogs?</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/is-borax-safe-for-dogs/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 15:04:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/is-borax-safe-for-dogs/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We may earn a commission when you click and buy from Amazon.com.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The first question is, is borax safe for dogs? The answer to this question is that it depends on the amount and how often they are exposed.
Borax is a chemical compound (Na2B4O7(OH)410H2O) that has multiple uses in industry, but many people use it as a laundry booster or as an insecticide because of its low toxicity to mammals and birds.
&lt;strong&gt;But, just how toxic is borax to dogs?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Top 7 Best Puppy Shampoo for Fleas Reviewed</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/best-puppy-shampoo-for-fleas/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 14:53:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/best-puppy-shampoo-for-fleas/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We may earn a commission when you click and buy from Amazon.com.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In this guide, we review the best puppy shampoos for combating fleas. Puppies, like newborns, need gentle care, especially regarding grooming.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Weve assessed top-rated shampoos to help you choose the right one for your puppys flea issues. Check out our picks to find the perfect solution for keeping your furry friend clean and comfortable.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Related:
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pestpolicy.com/best-flea-shampoo-for-dogs/&#34;&gt;Flea Shampoo for Adult Dogs&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Are fleas Nocturnal? Do fleas Sleep at Night?</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/are-fleas-nocturnal/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 14:38:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/are-fleas-nocturnal/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We may earn a commission when you click and buy from Amazon.com.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As a home or pet owner, you&amp;rsquo;d be worried if your lovely dog or cat
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pestpolicy.com/flea-life-cycle/&#34;&gt;caught fleas&lt;/a&gt;
. These bugs will bite and suck blood from these animals, causing your furry friends pain, anemia, or death.
So, it&amp;rsquo;s logical to pursue techniques to help control fleas both in the day and night times. But are fleas nocturnal? do fleas sleep at night?
**In summary, fleas do not sleep but these bugs use the circadian (activity &amp;amp; rest) rhythms. **
**But fleas, like bedbugs, are very active during the night-time or dusk than in the day (maybe they&amp;rsquo;re nocturnal or vespertine?). **
**However, fleas won&amp;rsquo;t be fully inactive during the day and hence they may still jump into humans, between houses, and on pets. **&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How High Can Fleas Jump?</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/how-high-can-fleas-jump/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 14:33:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/how-high-can-fleas-jump/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We may earn a commission when you click and buy from Amazon.com.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Fact:
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pestpolicy.com/do-fleas-have-wings/&#34;&gt;Fleas (Ctenocephalides felis) don&amp;rsquo;t have wings&lt;/a&gt;
and will move by jumping using their powerful legs.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://pestpolicy.com/how-long-can-fleas-live-without-a-host/&#34;&gt;Fleas can only live up to 4 days&lt;/a&gt;
when removed from their hosts.
So, fleas jump around looking for a blood meal or move from
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pestpolicy.com/does-heat-kill-fleas/&#34;&gt;heat&lt;/a&gt;
.
So,
*how high can fleas jump? *
**Fleas can jump a maximum of **
**7 inches (18 cm) vertically and 13 inches (33 cm) horizontally (an average 40 - 99 times of the flea&amp;rsquo;s body length) - it&amp;rsquo;s only second to **
**froghopper. Its hind-most pair of legs are significantly adapted in jumping. Here&amp;rsquo;s how to tell if you have a flea problem. **&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>7 Best Flea Shampoo for Dogs - Buying Guide</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/best-flea-shampoo-for-dogs/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 14:23:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/best-flea-shampoo-for-dogs/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We may earn a commission when you click and buy from Amazon.com.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Dealing with fleas can feel like a never-ending battle, but the right flea shampoo can make all the difference. If you&amp;rsquo;re tired of watching your dog scratch and squirm, it&amp;rsquo;s time to take action.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The best flea shampoos not only eliminate fleas but also soothe your dog&amp;rsquo;s skin and provide long-lasting relief. With countless products on the market, choosing the right one can be overwhelming.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Does the Dryer Kill Fleas?</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/does-the-dryer-kill-fleas/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 14:17:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/does-the-dryer-kill-fleas/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We may earn a commission when you click and buy from Amazon.com.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Drying fabric or clothes at high temperatures is often prescribed to homeowners
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pestpolicy.com/what-temperature-kills-bed-bugs/&#34;&gt;killing bugs such as bed bugs&lt;/a&gt;
. But does the dryer kill fleas?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;**Well, in summary, YES, the high temperatures in a dryer do kill fleas plus all their babies including eggs and flea larvae on your clothes, curtains, and bedding. **&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;**So, launder the clothing and other fabrics 10 minutes at temperatures of ~ 95F (35C). Finally, undertake the garment drying (at the highest temperature) to kill the fleas and other bugs. **&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;details-does-the-dryer-kill-fleas&#34;&gt;Details: Does The Dryer Kill Fleas?&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Besides killing the adult fleas,
dryers will also exterminate flea eggs (on your fabric, clothes, stuffed animals, and bedding) prior to the hatching.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Diatomaceous Earth for Fleas - Flea Control</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/diatomaceous-earth-for-fleas/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 14:12:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/diatomaceous-earth-for-fleas/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We may earn a commission when you click and buy from Amazon.com.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://pestpolicy.com/diatomaceous-earth/&#34;&gt;Diatomaceous Earth (DE)&lt;/a&gt;
is an effective and equally safe way to kill various pests and insects, including fleas and bed bugs.
DE is made up of tiny fossilized remains of diatoms (a form of algae). DE won&amp;rsquo;t kill fleas immediately, like the contact killers, but its benefits far outweigh the expected wait time.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When crushed, Diatomaceous Earth powder has sharp edges (microscopic) safe for you and your pets but is fatal on pests like fleas. The razor-sharp edges in DE will break the
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pestpolicy.com/does-the-dryer-kill-fleas/&#34;&gt;fleas&amp;rsquo; exoskeletons and kill&lt;/a&gt;
them through dehydration.
In this post, you&amp;rsquo;ll learn how to use
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pestpolicy.com/does-diatomaceous-earth-kill-bed-bugs/&#34;&gt;Diatomaceous Earth&lt;/a&gt;
for fleas&amp;rsquo; extermination safely. But you can click here to check out how to use
DE.
[amazon bestseller=&amp;ldquo;Best Fleas Killer&amp;rdquo; items=&amp;ldquo;2&amp;rdquo; template=&amp;ldquo;table&amp;rdquo;]&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Where Do Flea Larvae Live?</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/where-do-flea-larvae-live/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 14:05:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/where-do-flea-larvae-live/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We may earn a commission when you click and buy from Amazon.com.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Flea larvae are concentrated in places that pets sleep or relax like carpet fibers. Also, the carpet fibers may hinder
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pestpolicy.com/best-fogger-for-fleas/&#34;&gt;insecticides like foggers&lt;/a&gt;
from easily penetrating and killing the larvae.
**On where do flea larvae live? Fleas larvae will live in those micro-habitats that are dark, with moderate temperature, and high humidity with enough flea food. **&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;**So, in your home, you&amp;rsquo;ll find flea larvae (and over **80% of the fleas) growing incarpet fibers.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;**You&amp;rsquo;ll also get fleas larvae around the pet&amp;rsquo;s resting areas - including around dog houses, holstered furniture, floorboard cracks, and pet bedding. **
You may try
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pestpolicy.com/best-steam-cleaner-for-fleas/&#34;&gt;these steam cleaners&lt;/a&gt;
.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;[amazon bestseller=&amp;ldquo;Best steam cleaner for fleas&amp;rdquo; items=&amp;ldquo;2&amp;rdquo; template=&amp;ldquo;table&amp;rdquo;]&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Where Do Fleas Hide? 7 Fleas&#39; Hiding Spots</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/where-do-fleas-hide/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 13:40:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/where-do-fleas-hide/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We may earn a commission when you click and buy from Amazon.com.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Where do fleas hide? - this article presents my quick and detailed response. The information will assist homeowners to
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pestpolicy.com/best-fogger-for-fleas/&#34;&gt;track down the fleas and exterminate them&lt;/a&gt;
.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;**In brief; fleas hide on clothes, in the yard (around pet&amp;rsquo;s feeding places), on furniture, under leaf piles, in beds &amp;amp; mattresses, cracks &amp;amp; crevices, on the carpet, and on pets. **
But how will fleas get to jump *(up to 33 cm) onto pets and humans? Well, the bugs detect movement, vibrations, and breath to know when humans and pets are around.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;where-do-fleas-hide-top-7-fleas-hiding-spots&#34;&gt;Where Do Fleas Hide? Top 7 Fleas&amp;rsquo; Hiding Spots&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As those flea eggs begin to hatch and their larvae emerging, this flea stage will be about 35% of that
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pestpolicy.com/best-flea-spray-for-home/&#34;&gt;flea population in your household&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Diatomaceous Earth for Fleas on Cats</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/diatomaceous-earth-for-fleas-on-cats/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 13:27:08 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/diatomaceous-earth-for-fleas-on-cats/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We may earn a commission when you click and buy from Amazon.com.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You might have noticed that your cat is scratching its fur more than usual, and some small creatures are falling off its skin.
Your cat is most probably infected by fleas, a nightmare to your cat, and you as well.
There are many ways to get rid of fleas from cats.
They include methods where you use chemicals and others where no chemicals are involved. The latter method is the use of
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pestpolicy.com/diatomaceous-earth-for-fleas/&#34;&gt;Diatomaceous Earth for Fleas&lt;/a&gt;
.
[amazon bestseller=&amp;ldquo;Diatomaceous Earth for Fleas&amp;rdquo; items=&amp;ldquo;2&amp;rdquo; template=&amp;ldquo;table&amp;rdquo;]&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>7 Best Flea Shampoo for Cats 2025 Reviewed</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/best-flea-shampoo-for-cats/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 13:25:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/best-flea-shampoo-for-cats/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We may earn a commission when you click and buy from Amazon.com.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Whats the best flea shampoo for cats? It can take up to three months to stop a flea outbreak, and you can attack your home all through the year.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Protect your cat with one of these flea shampoos - keep them scratch-free all year round!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Unfortunately, fleas can multiply by one thousand within the first twenty-one days of a singular flea hatching.
Dont be fooled into thinking these blood-suckers dont attack during winter; they can attack in every season and can attack every type of breed. No cat is immune.
[amazon bestseller=&amp;ldquo;Best Flea Shampoo for Cats&amp;rdquo; items=&amp;ldquo;2&amp;rdquo; template=&amp;ldquo;table&amp;rdquo;]&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;1-our-1-pick-adams-plus-flea-and-tick-shampoo-with-precor&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B004KDRGD2/?tag=p-policy-20&#34;&gt;1. Our #1 Pick: Adams Plus Flea and Tick Shampoo with Precor&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;[amazon box=&amp;ldquo;B004KDRGD2&amp;rdquo; template=&amp;ldquo;horizontal&amp;rdquo;]
This reasonably priced formula is trusted and heavily relied on in the industry with Pet owners worldwide.
It offers twenty-eight days of protection for your precious feline friend and can
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pestpolicy.com/does-the-dryer-kill-fleas/&#34;&gt;kill the Fleas in all stages of life - larvae&lt;/a&gt;
, eggs, and adult fleas.
This means youll prevent the eggs from re-hatching. It can also
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pestpolicy.com/does-ammonia-kill-bed-bugs/&#34;&gt;kill off the egg&lt;/a&gt;
to stop them from hatching in warm places such as mattresses, carpets, and furniture.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flea Bites vs. Bed Bug Bites- Differentiate?</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/flea-bites-vs-bed-bug-bites/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 13:24:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/flea-bites-vs-bed-bug-bites/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We may earn a commission when you click and buy from Amazon.com.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The small red bumps appearing in specific areas of your skin can be hard to tell apart. Well tell you how to figure out whether theyre flea bites or
&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pmc/articles/PMC3255965/&#34;&gt;bedbug&lt;/a&gt;
bites.
&lt;strong&gt;Both these bites swell up and can be itchy, so here are some tips thatll help you tell the difference between them:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Fleas prefer animal blood but can drink human blood as well. Whereas bedbugs only drink human blood.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Flea bites appear to be red, swollen, and hard. Bedbug bites, on the other hand, seem to have a dark red spot in the center of the bitten and raised area of the skin.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Fleas tend to bite randomly over the body, and you might notice clusters of three dots together. Bedbugs, however, tend to bite their hosts strategically in a pattern of a linear row, you can find a group of 10 or more together.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Flea bites can be found on the lower half of the body, in places like ankles, calves, or moist areas such as elbows and knees bends. Whereas, bedbug bites are found in the upper half of the body in areas such as the neck, arms, shoulders, and back.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Cat ScratchingLets go into detail about all the things that make the two bites different, as well as how to deal with them.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Diatomaceous Earth for Fleas on Dogs</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/diatomaceous-earth-for-fleas-on-dogs/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 13:19:21 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/diatomaceous-earth-for-fleas-on-dogs/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We may earn a commission when you click and buy from Amazon.com.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Fleas are not only irritating and a nuisance to your dog, but they also cause painful wounds and internal infections.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;**Many methods to get rid of fleas on dogs have been advanced. Below I review the Diatomaceous Earth for Fleas on Dogs. **&lt;strong&gt;Among the numerous methods, many dog owners are opting for ways that dont involve chemicals.&lt;/strong&gt;
Methods that do not harm the environment, such as the use of
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pestpolicy.com/diatomaceous-earth-for-fleas/&#34;&gt;Diatomaceous Earth for Fleas&lt;/a&gt;
.
[amazon bestseller=&amp;ldquo;Diatomaceous Earth for Fleas&amp;rdquo; items=&amp;ldquo;2&amp;rdquo; template=&amp;ldquo;table&amp;rdquo;]&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;details-diatomaceous-earth-for-fleas-on-dogs&#34;&gt;**Details: Diatomaceous Earth for Fleas on Dogs **&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Studies have found that
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pestpolicy.com/diatomaceous-earth/&#34;&gt;diatomaceous earth&lt;/a&gt;
has sharp edges that resemble bits of broken glass. The mode of action of DE is mechanical.
The diatoms
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pestpolicy.com/does-salt-kill-fleas/&#34;&gt;kill insects and parasites&lt;/a&gt;
by removing the protective outer shell that helps them conserve moisture; they then dehydrate and subsequently die.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Diatomaceous Earth - Uses &amp; Side Effects</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/diatomaceous-earth/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 13:14:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/diatomaceous-earth/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We may earn a commission when you click and buy from Amazon.com.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Diatomaceous earth, anyone? You probably were searching for remedies to the roach infestation in your home or a solution to fleas that have become a nuisance to your pet and stumbled on
&lt;a href=&#34;http://npic.orst.edu/factsheets/degen.html&#34;&gt;Diatomaceous earth&lt;/a&gt;
.
And now you are wondering what this Diatomaceous earth is. This article is going to lay down all the facts about Diatomaceous earth and its benefits.
&lt;strong&gt;Definition:&lt;/strong&gt;
Diatomaceous earth is a naturally occurring siliceous sedimentary rock made from fossilized tiny aquatic organisms. These tiny organisms are called diatoms, and they contain shells of single-cell hard-shelled algae-like water plants. Diatomaceous easily crumbles to form a white to an off-white fine powder.
[amazon bestseller=&amp;ldquo;Diatomaceous Earth&amp;rdquo; items=&amp;ldquo;2&amp;rdquo; template=&amp;ldquo;table&amp;rdquo;]&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Treat Fleas in the Yard - 11 Tips</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/how-to-treat-fleas-in-the-yard/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 12:57:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/how-to-treat-fleas-in-the-yard/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We may earn a commission when you click and buy from Amazon.com.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you&amp;rsquo;re tired of fleas in your yard, this blog post is for you. We&amp;rsquo;ll discuss how to treat fleas in the yard.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Fleas in your yard can be a nuisance, as they breed fast and thrive there; thanks to the
&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.canr.msu.edu/ipm/uploads/files/Fleas.pdf&#34;&gt;humid or warm environments&lt;/a&gt;
. They may hitchhike your pets (
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pestpolicy.com/can-humans-carry-fleas-from-one-home-to-another/&#34;&gt;or rarely humans&lt;/a&gt;
) to get into your home.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Long Can Fleas Live Without a Host?</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/how-long-can-fleas-live-without-a-host/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 12:51:45 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/how-long-can-fleas-live-without-a-host/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We may earn a commission when you click and buy from Amazon.com.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Fleas are generally parasites that
&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pmc/articles/PMC5734377/&#34;&gt;need a host to survive&lt;/a&gt;
. But how long can fleas live without a host? Well, because of their thirst for blood and parasitic nature, they depend on the host most of their time.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;**Fleas can survive for a period of 4-7 days without a host. But if you subject them to any longer than this, they will die. **&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Fleas have different stages of a life cycle but it is the adults that need the host more especially when laying eggs. Fleas can attach to many hosts, but their preferred hosts are the furry homes pets- cats and dogs.&lt;/strong&gt;
If you study the life cycle of a flea, you shall get the opportunity to learn and understand about the fleas and their host.
[amazon bestseller=&amp;ldquo;Best Flea Killers&amp;rdquo; items=&amp;ldquo;2&amp;rdquo; template=&amp;ldquo;table&amp;rdquo;]&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;details-how-long-can-fleas-live-without-a-host&#34;&gt;Details: How Long Can Fleas Live Without A Host?&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Because fleas are parasites, it is difficult to live without a host. They get their food from the host to survive and reproduce.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Does Flea Treatment Burn Cats Skin?</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/does-flea-treatment-burn-cats-skin/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 12:51:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/does-flea-treatment-burn-cats-skin/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We may earn a commission when you click and buy from Amazon.com.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;On how to flea treat kittens with sensitive skin? Kittens/cats with sensitive skin are delicate animals to handle, even with
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pestpolicy.com/best-flea-treatment-for-kittens/&#34;&gt;kittens&amp;rsquo; best flea treatment&lt;/a&gt;
. These skin sensations are triggered by some causes such as:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Allergens  cause irritation and itching.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://pestpolicy.com/can-fleas-live-on-clothes/&#34;&gt;Flea infestations  Flea bites&lt;/a&gt;my case diseases like Bartonella, Anemia, or Flea Allergy Dermatitis on your kittens.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;details-does-flea-treatment-burn-cats-skin&#34;&gt;Details: Does Flea Treatment Burn Cats Skin?&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You can use some of the ways highlighted while treating your skin sensitive kitten/cat:&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Borax Flea Killer for Infestations at Home?</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/borax-flea-killer/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 12:46:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/borax-flea-killer/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We may earn a commission when you click and buy from Amazon.com.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Below
I&amp;rsquo;ve described how you can use a borax flea killer (an
&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.google.com/patents/US4617188&#34;&gt;old-time flea control&lt;/a&gt;
). But why, Borax?
Well, it&amp;rsquo;s
budget-friendly, effective, all-natural treatment, and safe around kids, cats, and dogs.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The Borax in your laundry room provides a safer way to control fleas - without using harsh chemicals.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Borax can help homeowners control flea problems in and around our homes - including&lt;a href=&#34;https://pestpolicy.com/what-do-flea-eggs-look-like/&#34;&gt;flea eggs?&lt;/a&gt;. Let&amp;rsquo;s find out!
*In summary, Borax will kill both adult fleas plus other insects that feed on plant juices and animal and human blood. But Borax won&amp;rsquo;t kill immature insects, including. Though, you must note that are differences between boric acid and Borax. *&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;in-a-hurry-view-top-borax-flea-killers&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;In a Hurry? View Top Borax Flea Killers&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;[amazon bestseller=&amp;ldquo;Borax Flea Killer&amp;rdquo; items=&amp;ldquo;2&amp;rdquo; template=&amp;ldquo;table&amp;rdquo;]&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What Soap Can I Use to Wash My Dog?</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/what-soap-can-i-use-to-wash-my-dog/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 12:27:37 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/what-soap-can-i-use-to-wash-my-dog/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We may earn a commission when you click and buy from Amazon.com.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Dogs love playing and making themselves dirty. Washing them also becomes very tricky because not every soap can work on them.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;**What soap I can use to wash my dog?  A good soap/shampoo will not trigger an allergic reaction in your dog.  You can get a good allergic report from your vet so that you may know what to avoid. **
Another thing is that there are some dogs that are smelly when they get dirty. In this case, you need to know what is the best shampoo/ soap to get rid of that smell.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;what-soap-can-i-use-to-wash-my-dog--the-best-choice&#34;&gt;What Soap Can I Use to Wash My Dog?  The Best Choice&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When you want to clean your dog, you surely want the best for him. There are dog specialist dog soaps with precise pH requirements for the dog.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Can Fleas Bite Through Clothes?</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/can-fleas-bite-through-clothes/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 12:15:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/can-fleas-bite-through-clothes/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We may earn a commission when you click and buy from Amazon.com.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Fleas are
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pestpolicy.com/how-to-get-rid-of-fleas-in-the-house-fast/&#34;&gt;very stubborn parasites&lt;/a&gt;
. They like to suck blood from both humans and animals-more so our pets at home. When its cold outside, they find their way into our houses for survival. When on human, can fleas bite through clothes?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;**Yes, and No, fleas cant bite through thick clothing or layers of clothes such as denim, jeans, and sneakers. **&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;**But, fleas can bite through thin clothes such as silk or lace - thin and tight fabric-like skin tights. Fleas cannot bite through clothes but like to find their way under the clothes and enjoy biting and sucking blood. **
[amazon bestseller=&amp;ldquo;Best Killer for Fleas&amp;rdquo; items=&amp;ldquo;2&amp;rdquo; template=&amp;ldquo;table&amp;rdquo;]
*But, fleas will move under the clothes to feed on your exposed skin. *
*Thus, you can stop flea bites by wearing closed-toe shoes, long trousers, and socks - and tuck the pant legs into your socks. *
For additional flea bite protection, use sprays some Sawyer Products Permethrin on your garments.
Related:
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pestpolicy.com/dawn-dish-soap-for-fleas/&#34;&gt;Can You Use Dawn Dish Soap&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;can-fleas-bite-through-clothes&#34;&gt;Can Fleas Bite Through Clothes?&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Fleas cant bite through clothes. But if the clothes are thin or tight they can. In most cases, fleas like to penetrate under the clothes and hide before they can bite into your skin.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Do Dogs Get Fleas? 7 Key Places!</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/how-do-dogs-get-fleas/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 11:46:45 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/how-do-dogs-get-fleas/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We may earn a commission when you click and buy from Amazon.com.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Fleas are a harsh pest when they attack your pets including dogs and cats. The bloodsuckers (fleas) will bite the dogs, causing irritation, scratching, pain, and even diseases. But how do dogs get fleas?
**In brief, dogs may get fleas from places such as the backyard, the park, **
**Pet facilities, **
**or when they come into contact with animals such as wildlife and pets. Outdoor animals that may bring fleas to dogs include foxes, raccoons, deer, rabbits, opossum, skunks, squirrels, ferrets, birds, and rodents. **&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Do Fleas Mate? How Fleas Breed</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/how-do-fleas-mate/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 11:44:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/how-do-fleas-mate/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We may earn a commission when you click and buy from Amazon.com.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;How do fleas mate? If you are unfortunate enough to be suffering a flea outbreak, you may be wondering how the mate and therefore spread - to
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pestpolicy.com/how-to-get-rid-of-fleas/&#34;&gt;control the fleas effectively&lt;/a&gt;
.
In this article, we will take a detailed look at how these pests reproduce - there are clear signs to show if fleas infest your house or yard.
[amazon bestseller=&amp;ldquo;Best Flea Killers&amp;rdquo; items=&amp;ldquo;2&amp;rdquo; template=&amp;ldquo;table&amp;rdquo;]&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What Does Leopard Gecko Eat?</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/what-does-leopard-gecko-eat/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 11:39:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/what-does-leopard-gecko-eat/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We may earn a commission when you click and buy from Amazon.com.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A proper diet will make your
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pestpolicy.com/are-leopard-geckos-nocturnal/&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt;crepuscular&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;
Leopard Gecko
&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.rspca.org.uk/adviceandwelfare/pets/other/leopardgecko&#34;&gt;healthy and happy every day&lt;/a&gt;
. But, really, what does leopard gecko eat?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Leopard Gecko is a small and attractive insectivorous reptile that is easier to take care of. Improper food administration may adversely affect their health.
**In summary, Leopard Gecko mainly eats insects such as cockroaches, super worms (such as Zilla Reptile Food), mealworms, or crickets. Leopard Geckos can also feed on silkworms, tomato hornworms, waxworms, beetles, sowbugs, and butter worms. Leopard Gecko does not feed on any vegetables or plant extracts. **
[amazon bestseller=&amp;ldquo;Best Food for Leopard&amp;rdquo; items=&amp;ldquo;2&amp;rdquo; template=&amp;ldquo;table&amp;rdquo;]&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What Do Flea Eggs Look Like?</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/what-do-flea-eggs-look-like/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 11:34:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/what-do-flea-eggs-look-like/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We may earn a commission when you click and buy from Amazon.com.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Really, what do flea eggs look like? Well, for anyone whos been
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pestpolicy.com/pictures-of-bed-bug-bites/&#34;&gt;bitten by a bed bug&lt;/a&gt;
, you can be sure some tiny flea eggs are lurking around to hatch  either from your cat or dogs.
*But to control flea eggs, you must effectively know their physical appearance and places where theyre hidden  including differences between flea eggs and flea dirt. *
*In summary, fleas eggs are tiny specs (0.5 lengths by 0.25 mm width), rounded-oval shape, with a flexible-chorion and softshell. *
*Adult females fleas produce eggs 1 to 2 days after taking a full blood meal and mating. Flea eggs will be laid on a host like cats or dogs, but they&amp;rsquo;ll fall off shortly (within hours). *
[amazon bestseller=&amp;ldquo;Best Flea Killers&amp;rdquo; items=&amp;ldquo;2&amp;rdquo; template=&amp;ldquo;table&amp;rdquo;]&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>My Guide to 7 Best Flea Treatment for Cats</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/best-flea-treatment-for-cats/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 11:27:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/best-flea-treatment-for-cats/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We may earn a commission when you click and buy from Amazon.com.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Flea prevention is crucial, especially in warmer climates like Arizona or Florida. Fleas not only cause discomfort but can also carry diseases such as Bartonellosis and cause allergic reactions in cats.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Below, we review the best cat flea treatments, highlighting their benefits, ease of use, and effectiveness. Related:
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pestpolicy.com/best-flea-drops-for-cats/&#34;&gt;Cat flea drops&lt;/a&gt;
.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;top-flea-treatments-for-cats&#34;&gt;Top Flea Treatments for Cats&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;1-cutter-backyard-flea-concentrate-ready-to-spray&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B000PGE032?th=1&amp;amp;linkCode=ll1&amp;amp;tag=p-policy-20&amp;amp;linkId=c7b45578922a0b55f3134d065ae6e212&amp;amp;language=en_US&amp;amp;ref_=as_li_ss_tl&#34;&gt;1. Cutter-Backyard Flea Concentrate Ready-to-Spray&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Cutter Backyard Flea Concentrate Ready-to-Spray is a highly effective product for long-term flea prevention. This treatment ensures that any infestation stays far away from your pet and home.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What Do Flea Eggs Look Like on a Dog?</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/what-do-flea-eggs-look-like-on-a-dog/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 11:26:43 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/what-do-flea-eggs-look-like-on-a-dog/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We may earn a commission when you click and buy from Amazon.com.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Flea eggs are generally oval-shaped and off-white in color with their chorion soft shell - they will appear like some salt grain, sand, or dry skin. However, what do flea eggs look like on a dog?
**In summary, Yes and NO - flea eggs are light in color and tiny and may thus prove difficult to see while on your dog with a naked eye. However, flea eggs are smooth and oval with a white color, which may hinder their visibility on the dog&amp;rsquo;s fur just like while on some light-colored fabric. **&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Where Do Bed Bugs Hide? - Identify Bugs</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/where-do-bed-bugs-hide/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 11:21:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/where-do-bed-bugs-hide/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We may earn a commission when you click and buy from Amazon.com.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Bed bugs are tiny insects (1/4 inch in body length) and are a nuisance to humans  their bites are painful and may cause anemia.
You will mainly find these bloodsuckers in residential or public premises and public places. Nevertheless, its challenging to
&lt;a href=&#34;https://extension.psu.edu/biology-habitat-and-management-of-bed-bugs&#34;&gt;locate their hideouts&lt;/a&gt;
. So, where do bed bugs hide?
*Simply put, bed bugs hide in mattress seams, wall or floor cracks, bed frames, chair joints, second-hand furniture joints, couches, bedding, clothes seams, ceiling, and clothe shelves.  Often, bed bugs hide during the day and appear at night when you are asleep. *
[amazon bestseller=&amp;ldquo;Best Bed Bug Killers&amp;rdquo; items=&amp;ldquo;2&amp;rdquo; template=&amp;ldquo;table&amp;rdquo;]&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Can Fleas Live on Clothes? Fleas and Flea Bites</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/can-fleas-live-on-clothes/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 11:19:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/can-fleas-live-on-clothes/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We may earn a commission when you click and buy from Amazon.com.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Flea eggs and pupae can remain dormant for a prolonged lying under carpets, pet fur, or clothes lying on the floor. But, cats &amp;amp; dogs - which are warm-blooded are their preferred hosts.
Also, fleas may host tapeworms and spread diseases like Lyme diseases. But
*, can fleas live on clothes? *
&lt;strong&gt;The short answer is, No!&lt;/strong&gt;
Cat
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pestpolicy.com/can-fleas-live-in-human-hair/&#34;&gt;fleas can&amp;rsquo;t live on hair&lt;/a&gt;
and clothes.
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pestpolicy.com/can-humans-carry-fleas-from-one-home-to-another/&#34;&gt;Fleas stay on humans&lt;/a&gt;
for only about 7.5 minutes as they suck blood.
If you disrupt them while sucking blood, the fleas will hide in the seams of your clothes -
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pestpolicy.com/&#34;&gt;for better flea control&lt;/a&gt;
. But, sometimes, the
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pestpolicy.com/how-to-get-rid-of-fleas-on-clothes-and-bedding/&#34;&gt;fleas can hide in clothes&lt;/a&gt;
for about 24 hours if they can&amp;rsquo;t figure their way out - as they continue sucking human blood.
[amazon bestseller=&amp;ldquo;Best Fleas Killers&amp;rdquo; items=&amp;ldquo;2&amp;rdquo; template=&amp;ldquo;table&amp;rdquo;]&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>7 Best Electronic Flea Combs for Cats &amp;amp; Dogs</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/best-electronic-flea-comb/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 11:17:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/best-electronic-flea-comb/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We may earn a commission when you click and buy from Amazon.com.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Fleas can be a
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pestpolicy.com/where-do-fleas-come-from/&#34;&gt;persistent nuisance&lt;/a&gt;
for pets and their owners alike. Traditional
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pestpolicy.com/best-flea-treatment-for-cats/&#34;&gt;flea treatments&lt;/a&gt;
often involve chemical solutions that can be harmful to both pets and the environment.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Fortunately, electronic flea combs offer a clean, effective, and chemical-free alternative. These innovative devices use a mild electric current to kill fleas on your cat or dog, providing a safe and environmentally friendly solution for flea control.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Get Rid Of Fleas in the House Forever</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/how-to-get-rid-of-fleas-in-the-house-forever/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 11:14:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/how-to-get-rid-of-fleas-in-the-house-forever/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We may earn a commission when you click and buy from Amazon.com.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Fleas are a
&lt;a href=&#34;https://entnemdept.ufl.edu/creatures/urban/occas/catflea.htm&#34;&gt;common pest&lt;/a&gt;
in the house; They&amp;rsquo;re small, they jump high, they&amp;rsquo;ll multiply so fast, and can be incredibly difficult to get rid of.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The fleas may have used your dog or cat as carriers to get into the house, or
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pestpolicy.com/can-humans-carry-fleas-from-one-home-to-another/&#34;&gt;they hitchhiked onto humans&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;sometimes.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This article will detail all of the steps on how to get rid of fleas in the house forever.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Top 9 Best Vacuums for Fleas in 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/best-vacuums-for-fleas/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 11:12:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/best-vacuums-for-fleas/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We may earn a commission when you click and buy from Amazon.com.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The most effective flea vacuums combine several key features: powerful suction to pull pests from deep fibers, HEPA filtration to trap microscopic eggs, sealed containment systems to prevent escape, and specialized brush rolls that agitate surfaces to dislodge
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pestpolicy.com/can-cats-get-fleas-in-the-winter/&#34;&gt;embedded pests&lt;/a&gt;
.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Regular vacuuming with the right machine can remove up to 30% of larvae and 60% of flea eggs from carpets, significantly disrupting their life cycle. We&amp;rsquo;ve evaluated dozens of models based on these criteria to bring you the top 5 vacuums specifically designed to
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pestpolicy.com/does-vacuuming-kill-flea-larvae/&#34;&gt;combat flea infestations&lt;/a&gt;
.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Top 7 Best Dog Beds 2025 Reviewed</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/best-dog-beds/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 10:53:30 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/best-dog-beds/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We may earn a commission when you click and buy from Amazon.com.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A dog that has comfortable bedding (best dog beds) is always a happily living pet, and it will definitely bond with the owner and other households amazingly well.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Selecting the beds is the most crucial process for any dog owner who wishes to transforms its entire lifestyle and boost its daily activeness.
Notably, Dogs Bed Orthopedic comes in varieties of colors such as grey, blue, red, orange, etc. for your optional selection. Check these
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pestpolicy.com/best-flea-treatment-for-dogs/&#34;&gt;flea treatments for dogs&lt;/a&gt;
.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;in-a-hurry-see-these-best-dog-beds&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;In a Hurry? See these Best Dog Beds&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;[amazon bestseller=&amp;ldquo;Best Dog Beds&amp;rdquo; items=&amp;ldquo;2&amp;rdquo; template=&amp;ldquo;table&amp;rdquo;]&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Does Apple Cider Vinegar Kill Fleas??</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/does-apple-cider-vinegar-kill-fleas/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 08:52:52 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/does-apple-cider-vinegar-kill-fleas/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We may earn a commission when you click and buy from Amazon.com.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Does apple cider vinegar kill fleas? To make your life and that of your pets as stress-free as possible, proper flea extermination is necessary.
Summer is here, and unfortunately, it brings along a lot of flea activity plus the hatching of
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pestpolicy.com/what-do-flea-eggs-look-like/&#34;&gt;flea eggs&lt;/a&gt;
.
There is one tested method employed by many pet owners to get rid of fleas:
&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.pacificcollege.edu/news/blog/2015/04/25/what-does-apple-cider-vinegar-not-do&#34;&gt;Vinegar&lt;/a&gt;
solution for fleas. I take a closer look at how you can get rid of fleas with vinegar and Dawn dish soap.
[amazon bestseller=&amp;ldquo;Best Flea Killer&amp;rdquo; items=&amp;ldquo;2&amp;rdquo; template=&amp;ldquo;table&amp;rdquo;]&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Permethrin Insect Repellent - Interactions, Side Effects</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/permethrin/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 08:48:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/permethrin/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We may earn a commission when you click and buy from Amazon.com.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Permethrin is one of the synthetic chemicals that are classified under the
&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.epa.gov/ingredients-used-pesticide-products/registration-review-pyrethrins-and-pyrethroids&#34;&gt;pyrethroids family&lt;/a&gt;
and come from a chrysanthemum flower.
Permethrin has been in use as an insecticide (as approved by EPA) since 1979 but its use has been adopted in 2006.
This broad insecticide can be used in a number of techniques in controlling insects.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Controlling mosquitoes, especially in programs meant for the general public.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Spraying on clothes, structures, pets,&lt;a href=&#34;https://pestpolicy.com/best-flea-spray-for-yard/&#34;&gt;yard or gardens&lt;/a&gt;, livestock, ornamental lawns, seed, and food crops.
You may also spray around food-handling areas.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;which-products-have-permethrin&#34;&gt;Which Products Have Permethrin?&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Permethrin can be found in a number of products including pest-treated clothes, sprays, aerosol or bombs, powders, and liquids.
Further, you can find permethrin in various pest treatment products like spot-on medication, flea collars, and ear tags.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>9 Best Flea Spray for Home 2025 Reviewed</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/best-flea-spray-for-home/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 08:37:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/best-flea-spray-for-home/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We may earn a commission when you click and buy from Amazon.com.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Looking for the best flea spray for your home? Say no more! In this post, Ill discuss that and other related questions.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://pestpolicy.com/can-fleas-live-on-clothes/&#34;&gt;Flea bites and flea infestations&lt;/a&gt;are everyday problems for most pet owners. The bugs will jump from one pet to another or the&lt;a href=&#34;https://pestpolicy.com/best-flea-spray-for-yard/&#34;&gt;yard&lt;/a&gt;while spreading diseases.
A suitable flea spray will exterminate the adult
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pestpolicy.com/combat-max-12-month-roach-killing-bait-review/&#34;&gt;roaches while killing&lt;/a&gt;
other flea stages; the eggs and larvae.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;in-a-hurry-view-our-flea-spray-for-home-&#34;&gt;**In a Hurry? View Our Flea Spray for Home **&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;[amazon bestseller=&amp;ldquo;Best Flea Spray for Home&amp;rdquo; items=&amp;ldquo;2&amp;rdquo; template=&amp;ldquo;table&amp;rdquo;]&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Where do Fleas Come From? 7 Places</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/where-do-fleas-come-from/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 08:32:47 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/where-do-fleas-come-from/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We may earn a commission when you click and buy from Amazon.com.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Fleas are remarkably adaptable parasites that can survive in numerous environments beyond their preferred animal hosts. While they commonly live and feed on warm-blooded animals like dogs and cats, these persistent pests have evolved to thrive in various household settings. Understanding where fleas live is the first step toward effective control.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Within homes, fleas frequently establish populations in carpets where the dense fibers provide ideal protection for eggs and developing larvae. The warm, humid environment created by foot traffic and indoor heating creates perfect breeding conditions.
Bedding and mattresses also serve as prime flea habitats, offering both warmth from
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pestpolicy.com/best-fogger-for-fleas/&#34;&gt;sleeping humans and pets&lt;/a&gt;
along with easy access to blood meals. Upholstered furniture similarly provides shelter and proximity to hosts, while clothing and shoes can transport fleas throughout the home. Even tiny cracks in flooring can harbor fleas between feedings.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;where-do-fleas-come-from&#34;&gt;Where do Fleas Come From?&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Fleas require very specific environmental conditions to survive and reproduce successfully. They thrive in humid, shaded locations and cannot tolerate direct sunlight, which quickly dehydrates and kills them.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Do Fleas Have Wings? 9 FAQs for Fleas</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/do-fleas-have-wings/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 08:08:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/do-fleas-have-wings/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We may earn a commission when you click and buy from Amazon.com.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;*So, how do fleas move? Do fleas have wings?  *
Wondering if
&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.canr.msu.edu/ipm/uploads/files/Fleas.pdf&#34;&gt;fleas&lt;/a&gt;
have wings, can they fly like
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pestpolicy.com/how-to-get-rid-of-gnats/&#34;&gt;gnats?&lt;/a&gt;
or do these clitters jump like frogs?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Fleas are tiny insects of the Siphonaptera order that&amp;rsquo;ll feed off human or animal blood.
Fleas move quickly and it may seem like they fly. Most of their over 2,000 types, like human fleas or cat fleas have strong legs, flat bodies and a length of ~ 0.1 inches.
&lt;strong&gt;Well, the short answer is, No, fleas don&amp;rsquo;t have wings. The suffix &amp;ldquo;&lt;/strong&gt;
*aptera&amp;rdquo; in *
**Siphonaptera **
*order *
**denote that fleas are **
&lt;a href=&#34;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Aptera&#34;&gt;wingless arthropods&lt;/a&gt;
** - like most ectoparasites such as **
&lt;strong&gt;ticks&lt;/strong&gt;
**. **
**Fleas use their powerful and tiny legs to jump (about 8 inches vertically) or move between hairs of host animal. Fleas, besides froghoppers, have the highest jump-body size ratio. **&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What Can I Wash My Cat with - 7 Tips</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/what-can-i-wash-my-cat-with/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 08:06:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/what-can-i-wash-my-cat-with/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We may earn a commission when you click and buy from Amazon.com.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You&amp;rsquo;re ready to give your fluffy, adorable cat a bath -
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pestpolicy.com/how-to-tell-if-your-cat-has-fleas/&#34;&gt;or it has fleas&lt;/a&gt;
. You&amp;rsquo;re considering using shampoo, maybe dish soap, or probably laundry detergent?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Really, what can I wash my cat with?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;What should I use to wash my cat with so he doesn&amp;rsquo;t get irritated skin or an allergic reaction?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;**In summary: to wash your cat, use a ****deodorizing shampoo made from natural ingredients. Or use a conditioning and dry skin shampoo, for a cat having dry skin. But overall, avoid human shampoo to wash the cat as it&amp;rsquo;ll dry out its hair. **
Let us find out!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;details-what-can-i-wash-my-cat-with&#34;&gt;Details: What Can I Wash My Cat with&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There are a number of benefits associated with using authentic cat shampoo compared to
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pestpolicy.com/can-you-use-human-shampoo-on-cats/&#34;&gt;human shampoo&lt;/a&gt;
, including; less dryness and itching, more natural pH balances, and fuller hair.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How To Tell If Your dog Has Fleas - 5 Signs</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tell-if-your-dog-has-fleas/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 07:50:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tell-if-your-dog-has-fleas/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We may earn a commission when you click and buy from Amazon.com.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;How do I know if my dog has fleas?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Well, the vet says it&amp;rsquo;s if you notice your dog scratching, shaking their head, biting themselves, and then scratching some more. But how do you know for sure?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In this article, I&amp;rsquo;ll tackle this question: how to tell if your dog has fleas?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;**Dogs with fleas will usually have at least one of the following: excessive scratching or licking; black specks around the base of their tail, head, ears, or paws; an irritated red skin rash. **
If your dog is exhibiting any of these symptoms then it may very well have fleas.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;[amazon bestseller=&amp;ldquo;Best Flea Killers&amp;rdquo; items=&amp;ldquo;2&amp;rdquo; template=&amp;ldquo;table&amp;rdquo;]&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Should You Spray Your Yard for Fleas?</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/should-you-spray-your-yard-for-fleas/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 07:32:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/should-you-spray-your-yard-for-fleas/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We may earn a commission when you click and buy from Amazon.com.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If used around the house (beyond just the Yard),
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pestpolicy.com/best-flea-spray-for-yard/&#34;&gt;Vet&amp;rsquo;s Best Flea Spray&lt;/a&gt;
will leave no stains even in places that the pets eat, play, sleep or live.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;However, you&amp;rsquo;ll need to test a small area like on pant legs or shoes before you undertake full-blown spraying.
Now, point the spray nozzle in any direction in your Yard or lawn to spray. However, ensure that you flea-spray the yard area evenly and avoid forming a puddle.
[amazon bestseller=&amp;ldquo;Best Flea Spray for Yard&amp;rdquo; items=&amp;ldquo;2&amp;rdquo; template=&amp;ldquo;table&amp;rdquo;]
&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=t4mJPb_z0fo&#34;&gt;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=t4mJPb_z0fo&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;considerations-in-yard-flea-spray&#34;&gt;Considerations in Yard Flea Spray&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;1-ease-of-use-and-duration&#34;&gt;1. Ease-of-use and Duration:&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The flea sprays for yards we&amp;rsquo;ve reviewed can be used with a garden sprayer. Some even come with a very handy hose applicator. Most of the products we&amp;rsquo;ve reviewed last 3-4 weeks.
&lt;em&gt;How long does the spray last?&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Long Do Flea Eggs Take To Hatch</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/how-long-do-flea-eggs-take-to-hatch/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 07:22:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/how-long-do-flea-eggs-take-to-hatch/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We may earn a commission when you click and buy from Amazon.com.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Using
monthly flea control products such as
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pestpolicy.com/best-fogger-for-fleas/&#34;&gt;flea foggers&lt;/a&gt;
will
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pestpolicy.com/how-long-does-it-take-to-break-the-flea-life-cycle/&#34;&gt;break the&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pestpolicy.com/how-long-does-it-take-to-break-the-flea-life-cycle/&#34;&gt;flea cycle in 3 months&lt;/a&gt;
while adult fleas have a lifespan of ~ 12 days (up to 110+ days).
Fleas will lay about 22 - 51 eggs a day, but this could vary with the prevailing temperature or if there are pesticides around and the fleas&amp;rsquo; food - may be
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pestpolicy.com/what-is-flea-dirt/&#34;&gt;flea dirt&lt;/a&gt;
?
*But how long do flea eggs take to hatch? Fleas eggs hatch within 1 (36 hours) to 10 days into larvae but this may vary with environmental conditions like humidity (over 50 %) &amp;amp; temperature (75 to 85 degrees). *&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What do fleas look like? (30&#43; Images of Fleas)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/what-do-fleas-look-like/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 07:05:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/what-do-fleas-look-like/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We may earn a commission when you click and buy from Amazon.com.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Fleas are small wingless insects that can be classified as parasites that are difficult to control. These insects predominantly live on small animals kept at home as pets, such as cats and dogs.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fleas are also common among birds and various other wild animals. Being parasitic, fleas survive almost exclusively on a diet of blood.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;They belong in the order Siphonaptera, which encompasses over 2,500 different species.
The focus of this post shall be on what fleas look like, but first things firstrelated:
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pestpolicy.com/pictures-of-bed-bugs/&#34;&gt;Bed Bug Pictures&lt;/a&gt;
.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;what-do-fleas-look-like-30-images-of-fleas--eggs&#34;&gt;What do fleas look like? (30+ Images of Fleas &amp;amp; Eggs)&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=mjjGoiGhIUM&#34;&gt;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=mjjGoiGhIUM&lt;/a&gt;
First and foremost, fleas are transmitters of a wide spectrum of diseases to both humans and animals. Some of these include the following;
1.
&lt;strong&gt;Murine Typhus&lt;/strong&gt;
This disease is mainly transmitted from rats and cats through
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pestpolicy.com/do-fleas-bite-humans/&#34;&gt;flea bites&lt;/a&gt;
. It is important to remember that when
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pestpolicy.com/flea-bites-vs-bed-bug-bites/&#34;&gt;fleas bite&lt;/a&gt;
, they also defecate simultaneously.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dog Has Fleas and Sleeps in My Bed</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/dog-has-fleas-and-sleeps-in-my-bed/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 07:03:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/dog-has-fleas-and-sleeps-in-my-bed/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We may earn a commission when you click and buy from Amazon.com.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Sleeping with you are cat or dog on the bed is quite cozy and soothing but this may turn out different if the pet has fleas.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Psychological snuggling or sleeping next to your pet has been documented to&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.sleepassociation.org/sleep-news/pets-may-help-you-sleep-better/&#34;&gt;reduce anxiety and stress&lt;/a&gt;from work or school.
So, youre wondering; your dog has fleas and sleeps in my bed, what should you do? Is it safe?
Well, fleas don&amp;rsquo;t generally jump onto humans and bite them but they do occasionally. Therefore if the dog has fleas and it sleeps on your bed, you could end up with a massive flea problem, or (at the minimum) the fleas might just bite you while you&amp;rsquo;re sleeping and leave you with itchy or painful skin.
Fleas will bite pets such as cats and dogs
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pestpolicy.com/can-dog-fleas-transfer-to-humans/&#34;&gt;but will also bite humans&lt;/a&gt;
if they share a bed or if you go near there betting that is not flea-treated.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;So if youve risen from your bed and you notice that your pet and yourself are scratching continuously, I encourage you to continue reading this article to know the science to check out to know whether you have fleas in the bed.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;details-dog-has-fleas-and-sleeps-in-my-bed&#34;&gt;Details: Dog Has Fleas and Sleeps in My Bed&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So if your cat or dog sleeps with you on the bed and they&amp;rsquo;re not
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pestpolicy.com/best-flea-shampoo-for-dogs/&#34;&gt;flea-treated&lt;/a&gt;
you could be attracting a flea problem around yourself.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Revolution for Cats without Vet Prescription</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/revolution-for-cats-without-vet-prescription/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 07:02:43 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/revolution-for-cats-without-vet-prescription/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We may earn a commission when you click and buy from Amazon.com.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I, like many other pet owners, prefer getting effective and
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pestpolicy.com/is-borax-safe-for-cats/&#34;&gt;safe flea medication&lt;/a&gt;
s for my cat without having to visit the vet office or giving them a call.
In this article, I will discuss how you can get your Cat&amp;rsquo;s revolution flea killer for cheap and without a vet&amp;rsquo;s prescription.
NB: Other
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pestpolicy.com/how-to-get-rid-of-flea-eggs-on-cats/&#34;&gt;common flea medications&lt;/a&gt;
for your cat such as interceptor,
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pestpolicy.com/capstar-flea-treatment-reviews/&#34;&gt;Capstar&lt;/a&gt;
, and frontline plus will require a vet&amp;rsquo;s prescription.
So, let&amp;rsquo;s get started with Revolution flea killer for cats!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Do I Keep Fleas From Biting Me?</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/how-do-i-keep-fleas-from-biting-me/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 07:02:39 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/how-do-i-keep-fleas-from-biting-me/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We may earn a commission when you click and buy from Amazon.com.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Flea bites are a common concern, especially in households with pets or in areas where pets frequently visit. These tiny pests can cause significant discomfort, itching, and even allergic reactions.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Preventing flea bites requires a proactive approach to ensure your
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pestpolicy.com/can-humans-carry-fleas-from-one-home-to-another/&#34;&gt;home and surroundings remain flea-free&lt;/a&gt;
. In this guide, we will explore effective strategies to avoid flea bites, including what to wear, how to use flea repellents, proper laundering techniques, and essential cleaning practices.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Get Rid Of Fleas in Carpet</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/how-to-get-rid-of-fleas-in-carpet/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 06:52:45 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/how-to-get-rid-of-fleas-in-carpet/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We may earn a commission when you click and buy from Amazon.com.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If youve got a furry pet at home, its likely that your carpet is
&lt;a href=&#34;https://entomology.ca.uky.edu/ef602&#34;&gt;infected with fleas&lt;/a&gt;
. Well tell you how to get rid of the fleas in your carpet.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Weve carried out the research so that you dont have to, and well share with you the most effective tips and techniques that you can use to ensure that your carpets are flea-free.
&lt;strong&gt;Its best for both you and your pet that you eliminate fleas from your carpet as soon as possible. To get rid of fleas, you just need to follow any of these three simple methods:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What Do Flea Larvae Eat?</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/what-do-flea-larvae-eat/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 06:43:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/what-do-flea-larvae-eat/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We may earn a commission when you click and buy from Amazon.com.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;What do flea larvae eat?
&lt;a href=&#34;http://npic.orst.edu/pest/flea.html&#34;&gt;Flea larvae&lt;/a&gt;
(35% of the flea population) are the second phase of the fleas&amp;rsquo; life cycle.
&lt;strong&gt;The short answer is&lt;/strong&gt;
*flea larvae feed primarily on flea dirt, which is (1) adult fleas&amp;rsquo; feces (or undigested blood) &amp;amp; (2) conspecific (or nonviable) eggs - this is unlike other holometabolous larvae. *&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;what-do-flea-larvae-eat&#34;&gt;What Do Flea Larvae Eat?&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;These tiny
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pestpolicy.com/what-do-baby-fleas-look-like/&#34;&gt;baby fleas&lt;/a&gt;
will quickly feel running vacuum, footsteps, and vibrations, after which they&amp;rsquo;ll act dead.
As hematophagous obligate epiphytes, flea larva doesnt require a host to survive or grow.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>9 Best Indoor Flea Killer 2025 Reviewed</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/best-indoor-flea-killer/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 06:39:08 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/best-indoor-flea-killer/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We may earn a commission when you click and buy from Amazon.com.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Its not only pet owners who have to deal with flea infestations. Each household is prone to flea attack, which means that even you might require the best indoor flea killer or
&lt;a href=&#34;https://citybugs.tamu.edu/factsheets/biting-stinging/others/ent-3001/&#34;&gt;flea control treatment&lt;/a&gt;
.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Look out for signs of a flea infestation, and take measures to control them. Flea sprays are a good option to deal with such pests.
Well provide you a list of flea sprays that are the top picks for homeowners. If youve just discovered that your home is infested with fleas, you must take action before its too late. Related:
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pestpolicy.com/best-flea-treatment-for-cats/&#34;&gt;Flea Treatment for Cats&lt;/a&gt;
.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Does Garlic Kill Fleas On Cats?</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/does-garlic-kill-fleas-on-cats/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 06:24:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/does-garlic-kill-fleas-on-cats/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We may earn a commission when you click and buy from Amazon.com.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Cats bring joy and purrs to our lives, and keeping them healthy and pest-free is a top priority. Fleas, however, can be pesky nuisances that cause discomfort and potential health problems for our furry companions.
While seeking natural remedies is understandable, using garlic as a flea remedy for cats is
&lt;strong&gt;strongly discouraged&lt;/strong&gt;
due to its toxicity and lack of scientific backing.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Top 7 Best Silverfish Killer Reviewed</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/best-silverfish-killer/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 06:22:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/best-silverfish-killer/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We may earn a commission when you click and buy from Amazon.com.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When choosing the
&lt;strong&gt;best silverfish killer&lt;/strong&gt;
, you can consider things like effectiveness, safety for pets and children, ease of use, and the speed at which it delivers results. Silverfish infestations can be tricky, but with the right product, you can quickly eliminate these pests and prevent them from returning.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;key-factors-to-consider&#34;&gt;Key Factors to Consider&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;1effectiveness&#34;&gt;1.&lt;strong&gt;Effectiveness&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Some products, like
&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B002Y2OW6A/?tag=p-policy-20&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Dekko Silverfish Paks&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;
, are specifically designed for targeting silverfish infestations. The active ingredients in these products kill silverfish by luring them in with a bait, ensuring you eliminate the pests without much effort.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Do Fleas Bite Humans? Where? Flea Remedies</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/do-fleas-bite-humans/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 06:17:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/do-fleas-bite-humans/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We may earn a commission when you click and buy from Amazon.com.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.petmd.com/dog/parasites/flea-bites-dogs-what-do-they-look&#34;&gt;Flea bites&lt;/a&gt;
trigger irritation and discomfort in dogs and cats. But do fleas bite humans and possibly
&lt;a href=&#34;http://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/pii/S1198743X1461377X&#34;&gt;transmit diseases like the bubonic plague&lt;/a&gt;
?
*In summary, the flea will bite humans to suck blood, leaving 3-4 clusters of small-reddish spots - particularly on the ankles, feet, lower legs, calves. *&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;*Flea bites trigger irritation, pain, scratching, and allergic reactions, plus a rash or white-top blisters. Fleas have a mouth with 3 stylet that is needle-like adapted for biting their hosts and sucking blood. *&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;*The 2 styles on the outer side will bite (pierce) the human skin, and the remaining (middle) stylet will enter the blood capillary of the host and draw blood. **Also, the middle stylet injects some anticoagulant saliva to prevent blood clotting. *
[amazon bestseller=&amp;ldquo;Best Flea Killers&amp;rdquo; items=&amp;ldquo;2&amp;rdquo; template=&amp;ldquo;table&amp;rdquo;]&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;do-fleas-bite-humans-where-home-flea-remedies&#34;&gt;Do Fleas Bite Humans? Where? Home Flea Remedies&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Flea bites trigger inflammation, itching, and anemia due to blood loss to the parasitic insect in petshowever, it&amp;rsquo;s
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pestpolicy.com/how-to-tell-if-you-have-fleas/&#34;&gt;clear that fleas&lt;/a&gt;
also bite humans.
An adult flea can jump about 150x its height, but they&amp;rsquo;ll also easily move around by
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pestpolicy.com/can-humans-carry-fleas-from-one-home-to-another/&#34;&gt;hitchhiking on humans&lt;/a&gt;
and pets - mainly cats and dogs while moving around the house or yard.
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pestpolicy.com/flea-bites-vs-bed-bug-bites/&#34;&gt;Fleas will bite&lt;/a&gt;
humans on their lower extremities - ankles, feet, lower legs, calves. Therefore, the yard or lawn bugs will target camping blankets, pant legs, stockings, and shoes.
With 3 months (their whole lifespan), adult fleas will bring forth
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pestpolicy.com/what-do-baby-fleas-look-like/&#34;&gt;400 to 500 baby fleas&lt;/a&gt;
. However, fleas are mainly left in your yard by wild animals like skunks, raccoons, and moles - check these
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pestpolicy.com/best-mole-traps/&#34;&gt;durable moles traps&lt;/a&gt;
.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Do I Get Rid of Fleas in My House Without Bombing?</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/how-do-i-get-rid-of-fleas-in-my-house-without-bombing/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 06:11:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/how-do-i-get-rid-of-fleas-in-my-house-without-bombing/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We may earn a commission when you click and buy from Amazon.com.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Pyrethrins in the flea spray kill the adult fleas targeting the fleas nervous system and thus kill or paralyze them - with IGR - 0.1% pyriproxyfen.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;An IGR in Ultracide-flea, the pyriproxyfen, will stop various biological triggers, making the flea evolve to its next life cycle stage.
On how do I get rid of fleas in my house without
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pestpolicy.com/best-fogger-for-fleas/&#34;&gt;bombing&lt;/a&gt;
; check the detailed explanation below. These are the flea fogger or flea bomb alternatives.
[amazon bestseller=&amp;ldquo;Best Flea Sprays&amp;rdquo; items=&amp;ldquo;2&amp;rdquo; template=&amp;ldquo;table&amp;rdquo;]&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;1-pesticide-sprays&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;1. Pesticide Sprays&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Pesticide sprays kill fleas and are suitable for home use. Watch out for ingredients like resmethrin &amp;amp; permethrin - unsuitable for
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pestpolicy.com/best-flea-treatment-for-cats/&#34;&gt;cat flea treatment&lt;/a&gt;
. Ensure that any spray you use will
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pestpolicy.com/how-to-get-rid-of-flea-eggs-on-cats/&#34;&gt;kill the flea eggs on cats&lt;/a&gt;
.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Top 7 Best Silverfish Traps Reviewed</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/best-silverfish-traps/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 06:05:17 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/best-silverfish-traps/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We may earn a commission when you click and buy from Amazon.com.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When choosing the
&lt;em&gt;best silverfish traps&lt;/em&gt;
, you can consider things like
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pestpolicy.com/how-to-get-rid-of-silverfish/&#34;&gt;efficiency&lt;/a&gt;
, safety, ease of use, and environmental impact.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Whether youre dealing with a minor infestation or looking to prevent one, picking the right trap can make all the difference. Here&amp;rsquo;s how to choose wisely and some top recommendations to help keep your home silverfish-free.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;key-factors-to-consider&#34;&gt;Key Factors to Consider&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;1effectiveness&#34;&gt;1.&lt;strong&gt;Effectiveness&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Some products, like the
&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B007E83LUM/?tag=p-policy-20&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Catchmaster 72MAX&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Pest Trap&lt;/em&gt;
, are known for their high effectiveness due to the strength of the adhesive used. Effectiveness in silverfish traps usually refers to how quickly and thoroughly they catch these pests.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Get Rid Of Fleas on Clothes and Bedding</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/how-to-get-rid-of-fleas-on-clothes-and-bedding/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 05:59:31 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/how-to-get-rid-of-fleas-on-clothes-and-bedding/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We may earn a commission when you click and buy from Amazon.com.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Fleas hiding in clothes and bedding cause disastrous effects - like intense and annoying itching and may transmit diseases like
&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.mayoclinic.org/diseases-conditions/plague/symptoms-causes/syc-20351291&#34;&gt;Bubonic plague&lt;/a&gt;
and
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pestpolicy.com&#34;&gt;Rickettsia prowazekii&lt;/a&gt;
.
Fleas
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pestpolicy.com/can-fleas-live-on-clothes/&#34;&gt;may live on&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pestpolicy.com/can-fleas-live-on-clothes/&#34;&gt;clothing&lt;/a&gt;
(dirty areas) for ~ 24 hours. But the critters cause flea bites, which many people are allergic to, and cause
skin infections or blisters (pus-filled).
**The short answer on how to kill fleas in clothes and bedding -  detergent-launder the fabrics, heat-treatment, and turbulence produced by your washing machine will exterminate fleas, flea eggs, pupae, and larvae. **
See these flea sprays.
[amazon bestseller=&amp;ldquo;Best Flea Spray&amp;rdquo; items=&amp;ldquo;2&amp;rdquo; template=&amp;ldquo;table&amp;rdquo;]&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Top 7 Best Flea Spray for House Carpets Reviewed</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/best-flea-spray-for-house-carpets/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 05:58:37 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/best-flea-spray-for-house-carpets/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We may earn a commission when you click and buy from Amazon.com.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When choosing the best flea spray for house carpets, you can consider things like effectiveness,
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pestpolicy.com/where-do-fleas-come-from/&#34;&gt;ease of use&lt;/a&gt;
, safety for pets and children, and residual effect.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;By evaluating these key factors, you can ensure you select the best product to effectively eliminate fleas and keep your home safe.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;key-factors-to-consider&#34;&gt;Key Factors to Consider&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;1effectiveness&#34;&gt;1.&lt;strong&gt;Effectiveness&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Some products, like
&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B003PRI6OC/?tag=p-policy-20&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Vet&amp;rsquo;s Best Flea&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;
, are known for their fast-acting flea-killing abilities.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Does Vacuuming Kill Flea Larvae?</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/does-vacuuming-kill-flea-larvae/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 05:43:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/does-vacuuming-kill-flea-larvae/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We may earn a commission when you click and buy from Amazon.com.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As a homeowner, I&amp;rsquo;ve at one time been disturbed by household fleas and I was required to take quick and effective steps to control them - including vacuuming and heat treatment?
But does vacuuming kill flea larvae? Well, Yes, researchers have concluded that vacuuming will indeed kill 96% or more of the fleas that in
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pestpolicy.com/flea-life-cycle/&#34;&gt;various life stages&lt;/a&gt;
.
So, I advise you to vacuum your home and yard to exterminate or kill the developing flea pupae, larvae, adults, and flea eggs.
Further, the vacuuming process will trigger the cocoons-surrounded fleas to emerge faster - and thus enhances better
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pestpolicy.com/best-flea-spray-for-yard/&#34;&gt;exposure to insecticides&lt;/a&gt;
.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>7 Best Flea Treatment for Puppies 2025 Reviewed</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/best-flea-treatment-for-puppies/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 05:42:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/best-flea-treatment-for-puppies/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We may earn a commission when you click and buy from Amazon.com.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Flea Treatment is vital for your puppies healthy life. Flea may cause skin allergies, typhus, or even transmit parasites such as tapeworms.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Your top daily care for puppies is essential. So, could you be looking for the&lt;a href=&#34;https://pestpolicy.com/best-flea-treatment-for-dogs/&#34;&gt;best flea treatment&lt;/a&gt;for your puppies?
So, let&amp;rsquo;s get started!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;7-best-flea-treatment-for-puppies-2025-reviewed&#34;&gt;7 Best Flea Treatment for Puppies 2025 Reviewed&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;1-natural-care-flea-spray-for-puppies-12-weeks-dogs&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B01BWKMV2Q/?tag=p-policy-20&#34;&gt;1. Natural-Care Flea Spray for Puppies (12+ weeks), Dogs&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A solid choice for pet owners seeking a
&lt;strong&gt;natural, multi-purpose flea and tick spray&lt;/strong&gt;
for home and pet use. Ideal for routine prevention, but may need consistent reapplication for heavy infestations. Confirm shipping availability before ordering.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Get Rid of Fleas in Bed</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/how-to-get-rid-of-fleas-in-bed/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 05:42:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/how-to-get-rid-of-fleas-in-bed/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We may earn a commission when you click and buy from Amazon.com.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Fun fact: Over 95% of the
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pestpolicy.com/flea-life-cycle/&#34;&gt;flea population&lt;/a&gt;
will be scattered all over your house (including in the bed) with the pets hosting just 5% of the pests.
So, if you think bed bugs are the only disturbing pest you can have in your bed, then think again.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fleas will hide, reproduce, and bite you or your kids as you sleep.
In this article, Ive outlined how to get rid of fleas in bed.
In summary, you can remove fleas from the bed by Washing and drying the bed fabrics at high temperatures.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Wash the bed covers, pillow covers, and bed sheets using hot water to kill the fleas. Next, put the fabrics into your dryer to kill any living fleas.
Related:
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pestpolicy.com/how-big-are-fleas/&#34;&gt;How Big are Fleas?&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;details-how-to-get-rid-of-fleas-in-bed&#34;&gt;Details: How to Get Rid of Fleas in Bed&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Fleas will reproduce at a quick rate and after laying eggs the growth of the population will be very fast.
But you can remove fleas from your bed without hiring an exterminator -
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pestpolicy.com/can-cats-get-fleas-in-the-winter/&#34;&gt;even during winter&lt;/a&gt;
. Here are the steps you must take.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>7 Best Vacuum for Dog Hair 2025 Reviewed</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/best-vacuum-for-dog-hair/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 05:40:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/best-vacuum-for-dog-hair/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We may earn a commission when you click and buy from Amazon.com.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Even when healthy, your dog will always shed some hair - use the best vacuum for dog hair. So, the hair that&amp;rsquo;s dropped on carpets, floors, or sofa may irritate homeowners or
&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.aaaai.org/conditions-treatments/allergies/pet-allergy&#34;&gt;cause allergies&lt;/a&gt;
.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;So, in this post, I&amp;rsquo;ve reviewed the quality vacuums for dog hair - (either all-around vacuums, canister vacuums, and upright vacuums).
But most pet owners will first try to regularly
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pestpolicy.com/best-dog-brush-for-short-hair-shedding/&#34;&gt;brush&lt;/a&gt;
or
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pestpolicy.com/best-flea-shampoo-for-dogs/&#34;&gt;shampoo their dog&amp;rsquo;s hair&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;which might not be effective in some dog coats.
**Check these Vacuum for Dog Hair. **
[amazon bestseller=&amp;ldquo;Best Vacuum for Dog Hair&amp;rdquo; items=&amp;ldquo;2&amp;rdquo; template=&amp;ldquo;table&amp;rdquo;]&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;1-our-1-pick-bissell-pet-hair-eraser-handheld-vacuum-corded-33a1&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B001EYFQ28/?tag=p-policy-20&#34;&gt;1. Our #1 Pick: Bissell Pet Hair Eraser Handheld Vacuum, Corded, 33A1&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;[amazon box=&amp;ldquo;B001EYFQ28&amp;rdquo; template=&amp;ldquo;horizontal&amp;rdquo;]
Bissell Pet Hair Eraser is excellent in cleaning dog hair, little dirt mess, dog beds, and sofas due to its high suction power.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Are Male or Female Bernedoodles Better?</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/are-male-or-female-bernedoodles-better/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 05:35:51 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/are-male-or-female-bernedoodles-better/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We may earn a commission when you click and buy from Amazon.com.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Bernedoodles make
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pestpolicy.com/what-soap-can-i-use-to-wash-my-dog/&#34;&gt;adorable pets&lt;/a&gt;
. You may be wondering if there are any major differences between male and female ones.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Understanding what separates them is important for both you and your pet.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Whether you already have one or are looking to adopt, there are certain underlying factors to be aware of.
It is natural to wonder if you made the right decision. Do not worry, as we have done extensive research on this matter to make things easier for you. Read on to find out more.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;[amazon bestseller=&amp;ldquo;Bernedoodles&amp;rdquo; items=&amp;ldquo;2&amp;rdquo; template=&amp;ldquo;table&amp;rdquo;]&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Does Coconut Oil Kill Fleas? 7 Secrets</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/does-coconut-oil-kill-fleas/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 05:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/does-coconut-oil-kill-fleas/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We may earn a commission when you click and buy from Amazon.com.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;*So, &lt;strong&gt;does coconut oil kill fleas&lt;/strong&gt;? Well, the simple answer is, YES! coconut oil has lauric acid that&amp;rsquo;ll kill fleas through suffocation and restricting their movement. It covers the *
*flea&amp;rsquo;s exoskeleton restricting its movement and breathing - leading to and death.  *
*In addition, coconut oil has anti-fungal and anti-microbial properties. Thus, I&amp;rsquo;ll heal various skin conditions on your pet - cats or dogs. Just like on pets, coconut oil has many health benefits for humans. *
*Coconut oil with myristic acid (C14:0) and lauric (C12:0) is better than DEET in killing fleas. Externally, coconut oil nourishes the pet&amp;rsquo;s coat or skin, controls itchiness, dry skin, and allergies. *&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Can Fleas Live in Carpets Fiber? or Rugs?</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/can-fleas-live-in-carpets/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 05:34:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/can-fleas-live-in-carpets/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We may earn a commission when you click and buy from Amazon.com.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So, can fleas live in carpets? For pet owners, fleas are an unfortunate part of having animals in the home, and from time to time, you may notice an infestation on your pet - maybe you&amp;rsquo;ve tried
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pestpolicy.com/best-fogger-for-fleas/&#34;&gt;flea foggers&lt;/a&gt;
?
But treating your animal for fleas may not be enough; you need to consider your home too! For the yard, you can try these
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pestpolicy.com/best-flea-spray-for-yard/&#34;&gt;quality flea sprays for lawns&lt;/a&gt;
.
[amazon bestseller=&amp;ldquo;Best Flea Killer for Carpet&amp;rdquo; items=&amp;ldquo;2&amp;rdquo; template=&amp;ldquo;table&amp;rdquo;]&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What Is Flea Dirt? Color, Shape, and Size</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/what-is-flea-dirt/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 05:08:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/what-is-flea-dirt/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We may earn a commission when you click and buy from Amazon.com.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;**What is flea dirt? **
Flea dirt (flea poop or flea frass) is the round black pepper or dandruff-looking specs made up of undigested and dried blood (dropped by fleas) after sucking blood from cats, dogs, or
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pestpolicy.com/flea-repellent-for-humans/&#34;&gt;humans&lt;/a&gt;
.
You can find flea dirt when
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pestpolicy.com/best-electronic-flea-comb/&#34;&gt;combing&lt;/a&gt;
or running fingers against the grain of your cat&amp;rsquo;s or dog&amp;rsquo;s hair. Flea dirt is mainly found around your cat&amp;rsquo;s or dog&amp;rsquo;s
groin
area, the tails, or between their hind legs.
Ultimately, flea larvae will feed on the flea dirt -
&lt;em&gt;remember its blood anyway&lt;/em&gt;
. But most fleas must be controlled from their hiding places in the
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pestpolicy.com/best-fogger-for-fleas/&#34;&gt;house&lt;/a&gt;
or the
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pestpolicy.com/best-flea-spray-for-yard/&#34;&gt;yard&lt;/a&gt;
.
[amazon bestseller=&amp;ldquo;Best Fleas Killer&amp;rdquo; items=&amp;ldquo;2&amp;rdquo; template=&amp;ldquo;table&amp;rdquo;]&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Capstar Flea Tablets for Large Dogs</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/capstar-flea-tablets-for-large-dogs/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 05:05:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/capstar-flea-tablets-for-large-dogs/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We may earn a commission when you click and buy from Amazon.com.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Capstar flea tablets for large dogs contain 57 mg of nitenpyram as its active ingredient and it&amp;rsquo;s effective for
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pestpolicy.com/how-to-kill-fleas-on-dogs-naturally-safe-and-fast/&#34;&gt;killing adult fleas&lt;/a&gt;
.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The nitenpyram ingredient falls under the group of neonicotinoids.
The oral tablet is effective and safe for killing fleas in large dogs.
However, the manufacturers caution that these oral tablets must not be used for humans.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;So, keep the tablets away from the reach of kids.
Luckily, Capstar is safe for use on so you can give a second dose to the dog if it has a fleas&amp;rsquo; re-infestation.
Administering the Capstar flea trap tablets will require that you conceal the medication in the pet&amp;rsquo;s food or drop it into the dog&amp;rsquo;s mouth directly.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Inspect the dog thoroughly to ensure it has swallowed the flea tablet or re-administer the medication if you are not sure if it has swallowed.
NB: Remember that the fleas can multiply and reproduce while on another pet in your household even when you flea-treated your dog.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;So, it is good to adopt a comprehensive flea treatment approach for the house and on other pets. Related:&lt;a href=&#34;https://pestpolicy.com/capstar-flea-tablets-for-small-dogs/&#34;&gt;Capstar Flea Tablets for Small Dogs&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;dosage-and-reaction&#34;&gt;Dosage and Reaction&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Capstar flea tablets must be administered separately to the dog or other pets.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Where Do Fleas Lay Eggs? 7 Hiding Places</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/where-do-fleas-lay-eggs/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 05:05:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/where-do-fleas-lay-eggs/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We may earn a commission when you click and buy from Amazon.com.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As a home- and pet owner, flea infestations are a real nuisance to
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pestpolicy.com/how-long-do-fleas-live-on-humans/&#34;&gt;humans&lt;/a&gt;
, cats, and dogs - including
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pestpolicy.com/what-do-baby-fleas-look-like/&#34;&gt;baby fleas&lt;/a&gt;
. But where do fleas lay eggs? Knowing the hideouts will help us to easily break the flea&amp;rsquo;s life cycle.
Definitely, of the 2,000 flea species,
&lt;a href=&#34;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Dog_flea&#34;&gt;dog fleas&lt;/a&gt;
and
&lt;a href=&#34;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Cat_flea&#34;&gt;cat flea&lt;/a&gt;
(Ctenocephalides felis) are the most common on furry mammals, birds, dogs, and cats.
**Fleas lay their eggs on hosts such as cats (around the neck) or dogs (around their hips). The flea eggs are non-stick and thus will fall off from the pet&amp;rsquo;s fur. They&amp;rsquo;ll accumulate on the upholstery, between floorboards, carpets, and on the pet&amp;rsquo;s bedding and will hatch into larvae. But to break the flea cycle, you should use spot-on or oral treatments. **&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>7 Best Steam Cleaner for Fleas in 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/best-steam-cleaner-for-fleas/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 05:05:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/best-steam-cleaner-for-fleas/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We may earn a commission when you click and buy from Amazon.com.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When choosing the
&lt;strong&gt;best steam cleaner for fleas&lt;/strong&gt;
, you need to consider factors like heat output, tank size, pressure, and versatility.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fleas are resilient pests, and a good steam cleaner will help eliminate them at every stage of their lifecyclefrom adult fleas to their eggs and larvae.
Below, well break down the most important factors to consider when choosing a steam cleaner and provide recommendations to help you make an informed buying decision.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;key-factors-to-consider&#34;&gt;Key Factors to Consider&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;1-temperature-and-heat-output&#34;&gt;1. Temperature and Heat Output&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The effectiveness of a steam cleaner in eliminating fleas is closely tied to its temperature.
&lt;strong&gt;High heat&lt;/strong&gt;
is crucial because fleas, especially their eggs and larvae, are resistant to lower temperatures. A steam cleaner that produces steam at over 200F is ideal.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Tell If You Have Fleas in Your House</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tell-if-you-have-fleas/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 05:03:45 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tell-if-you-have-fleas/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We may earn a commission when you click and buy from Amazon.com.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It is pretty obvious and common for pets to catch fleas and eventually show up at home with a full load of them.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Our houses get infested too from pets, which bring them indoors, which means that human beings eventually get plagued.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;To human beings, they cause diseases like bubonic plague and typhus fever, and to pets, they cause anemia and introduce tapeworms to them.
In this post, Ive discussed how to
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pestpolicy.com/flea-eggs-vs-dandruff/&#34;&gt;tell if you have fleas&lt;/a&gt;
. Related:
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pestpolicy.com/best-flea-spray-for-home/&#34;&gt;Home Flea Control Sprays&lt;/a&gt;
.
[amazon bestseller=&amp;ldquo;Best Flea Killers&amp;rdquo; items=&amp;ldquo;2&amp;rdquo; template=&amp;ldquo;table&amp;rdquo;]&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;how-to-tell-if-you-have-fleas-in-your-house&#34;&gt;How to Tell If You Have Fleas in Your House&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;step-1---inspect-your-pets&#34;&gt;**Step 1 - Inspect Your Pets **&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The following are signs that you should watch out for if fleas have infested your pets.
**1. Scratching **
The undeniable sign that fleas have infested your pet is prolonged and repeated scratching your pets are doing. The primary source of food for
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pestpolicy.com/flea-bites-vs-bed-bug-bites/&#34;&gt;fleas is blood, and it is only&lt;/a&gt;
obtained by biting.
Pets, in turn, retaliate by scratching themselves and repeated grooming (for cats) to
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pestpolicy.com/does-salt-kill-fleas/&#34;&gt;remove the fleas&lt;/a&gt;
off their bodies.
The discomfort caused by the fleas makes the animal have abnormal scratching of the body, licking and biting the affected parts.
**2. Restlessness **
Due to the increased scratching and itching, the pets are always at bay due to the irritable little assailants. Behavioral changes are easily noticeable. For cats, they tend to be moody, low energy, and excessive grooming.
**3. Welts and bumps **
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pestpolicy.com/can-fleas-live-on-clothes/&#34;&gt;Flea bites&lt;/a&gt;
are irritable.  These bites appear as small red bumps with a red halo at the center. They mostly appear around the waist, armpits, breasts, groin, elbows, or knees for humans. These small red bumps are called welts and bumps.
**4. Hair loss **
When your pet is infested with fleas, it resorts to scratching and rubbing against the ground, carpet, and other surfaces to ease the itching.
Excessive scratching caused by the nagging
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pestpolicy.com/do-fleas-stay-on-humans/&#34;&gt;bites of fleas&lt;/a&gt;
leads to loss of hair. Animals may pull out some of their hair due to continuous biting and licking of fleabites.
In dogs, Alopecia is
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pestpolicy.com/can-fleas-live-in-human-hair/&#34;&gt;hair loss caused by some strains of the flea&lt;/a&gt;
. It affects the dogs immune, lymphatic, and endocrine systems.
**5. Anemia or pale gums **
The diet of fleas is mainly blood. Fleas can consume up to 15 times their body weight. This results in reduced numbers of red blood cells.
Pale gums mean reduced red blood cells. Reduced red blood cells indicate that your pet is not producing sufficient blood to compensate for blood loss to fleas.
**6. Dodgy colored dandruff **
In human beings, fleas cause welts and bumps. In pets, you are likely to spot breaking skin with sores on their bodies that are black/red in color.
To check the dodgy colored dandruff,
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pestpolicy.com/how-to-use-a-flea-comb/&#34;&gt;run a flea comb&lt;/a&gt;
through the animals coat. A flea comb has a close set of teeth specifically designed to trap fleas.
Run it on the animal several times. An infested coat will leave small black spots or brown spots on the teeth of the comb.
Related:
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pestpolicy.com/best-flea-spray-for-yard/&#34;&gt;Yard Flea Sprays&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Do Fleas Stay on Humans and Bite Us?</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/do-fleas-stay-on-humans/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 04:54:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/do-fleas-stay-on-humans/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We may earn a commission when you click and buy from Amazon.com.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So, do fleas stay on humans? If you&amp;rsquo;re like most humans, you&amp;rsquo;ll start scratching just with the mention of bed bugs. However, fleas bites on humans are only
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pestpolicy.com/can-dog-fleas-transfer-to-humans/&#34;&gt;incidental&lt;/a&gt;
.
But adult fleas will bite and suck blood from humans, cats, dogs, and outdoor animals like opossums, foxes, and rodents both for survival and reproduction purposes.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;*So, in this post, I&amp;rsquo;ve answered this question &amp;ldquo;do fleas stay on humans?&amp;rdquo; **The short answer is YES and NO! **Cat fleas can survive and breed by feeding exclusively on human blood. Female fleas must suck human blood for many hours to reproduce effectively. This is only possible in laboratory settings. Most fleas species can&amp;rsquo;t live in humans because we lack hair. *&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;*But human fleas have elongated hind legs and measure about 1.5-3mm, which allows them to hide under the human skin for a bit longer. Overall, fleas will stay on humans for a maximum of 24 hours before jumping onto their preferred host like cats and dogs. *
[amazon bestseller=&amp;ldquo;Best Flea Killers&amp;rdquo; items=&amp;ldquo;2&amp;rdquo; template=&amp;ldquo;table&amp;rdquo;]&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;details-do-fleas-stay-on-humans-and-bite-us-treatment&#34;&gt;Details: Do Fleas Stay on Humans and Bite Us? Treatment?&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Cat, dog, or human fleas have
&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.petmd.com/flea/infographic/flea-habitats-home&#34;&gt;different preferred hosts&lt;/a&gt;
. Despite that all of them can feed on a non-preferred host, their fertility is significantly reduced.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How To Tell If Your Cat Has Fleas</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tell-if-your-cat-has-fleas/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 04:53:37 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tell-if-your-cat-has-fleas/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We may earn a commission when you click and buy from Amazon.com.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As a pet parent, maybe sometimes you wonder how to tell if your cat has fleas.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Well, not anymore!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In this article, I am going to show you how best to tell if your cat has fleas (these size-sized bugs) so that they can start feeling their fur again!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Cats can be prone to fleas, a common pest that if left untreated could inflict furry cats and
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pestpolicy.com/how-to-tell-if-your-dog-has-fleas/&#34;&gt;dogs&lt;/a&gt;
with severe problems.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Top 7 Best Flea Treatment for Dogs</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/best-flea-treatment-for-dogs/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 04:42:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/best-flea-treatment-for-dogs/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We may earn a commission when you click and buy from Amazon.com.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When choosing the best flea treatment for dogs, you can consider things like the product&amp;rsquo;s effectiveness, safety, ease of use, and your dog&amp;rsquo;s specific needs. Selecting the right flea treatment can keep your dog comfortable and protect them from harmful parasites.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;key-factors-to-consider&#34;&gt;Key Factors to Consider&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;1-effectiveness-against-fleas-and-ticks&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;1. Effectiveness Against Fleas and Ticks&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Some products, like
&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B0002J1FOO/?tag=p-policy-20&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Frontline Plus&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;
, are renowned for their ability to eliminate both fleas and ticks at various life stages.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>7 Best Flea Shampoos for Dogs 2025 Reviewed</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/best-flea-shampoos-for-dogs/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 04:36:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/best-flea-shampoos-for-dogs/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We may earn a commission when you click and buy from Amazon.com.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Fleas are more than just a nuisance - they can cause severe itching, skin infections, and even transmit diseases to your dog. Choosing the right flea shampoo is essential for
&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.vet.cornell.edu/departments-centers-and-institutes/riney-canine-health-center/canine-health-information/flea-and-tick-prevention&#34;&gt;effective pest control&lt;/a&gt;
while keeping your dog&amp;rsquo;s skin and coat healthy.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;With so many options available, it&amp;rsquo;s important to weigh the pros and cons of each product. In this guide, we&amp;rsquo;ll review the top flea shampoos for dogs, highlighting their benefits, drawbacks, and key features to help you make an informed decision.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Does Steam Cleaning Kill Fleas?</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/does-steam-cleaning-kill-fleas/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 04:31:30 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/does-steam-cleaning-kill-fleas/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We may earn a commission when you click and buy from Amazon.com.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Fleas will reproduce rapidly and may soon become a challenge to pets, pet owners, and households. But is steam cleaning a suitable method to eradicate fleas?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;**To control the flea problem effectively, steam cleaning alone will kill some flea eggs and adult fleas, but it won&amp;rsquo;t solve the flea problem entirely. **&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;**So, combine steam cleaning with other methods for better outcomes. R****egularly vacuum your spaces frequently, wash the pet bedding, and use suitable flea treatment in combination with steam cleaning.  **
In this article, I&amp;rsquo;ll outline other tools you can use in combination with
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pestpolicy.com/best-steam-cleaner-for-fleas/&#34;&gt;steam cleaners&lt;/a&gt;
to eliminate fleas.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;does-steam-cleaning-carpets-remove-fleas-or-killfleas&#34;&gt;Does Steam Cleaning Carpets Remove Fleas Or KillFleas?&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Yes, steam cleaning can eliminate adult fleas and some flea eggs lodged in upholstery and carpets. However, it won&amp;rsquo;t entirely stop the flea infestation.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Capstar Flea Tablets for Small Dogs</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/capstar-flea-tablets-for-small-dogs/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 04:20:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/capstar-flea-tablets-for-small-dogs/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We may earn a commission when you click and buy from Amazon.com.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Capstar tablets are
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pestpolicy.com/how-to-get-rid-of-fleas/&#34;&gt;effective remedies for controlling fleas&lt;/a&gt;
in dogs, puppies, kittens, and cats. In the Star article, I will discuss Capstar flea tablets for small dogs (up to 11kg).
Notably, capital will begin killing the fleas on your dog in around half an hour and its effectiveness will last for one day.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;So I advise that you start the journey of controlling that flea infestation on your car or the dog by administering Capstar - it is an effective flea killer and it&amp;rsquo;s also fast-acting.
Let&amp;rsquo;s dig in!
Related:
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pestpolicy.com/dog-has-fleas-and-sleeps-in-my-bed/&#34;&gt;Dog Has Fleas and Sleeps in My Bed&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;details-capstar-flea-tablets-for-small-dogs&#34;&gt;Details: Capstar Flea Tablets For Small Dogs&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Cops are tablets that are effective and fast in killing fleas on small dogs such that you&amp;rsquo;ll actually see the pests falling off from your pet.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spraying Yard with Dawn for Fleas</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/spraying-yard-with-dawn-for-fleas/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 04:12:17 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/spraying-yard-with-dawn-for-fleas/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We may earn a commission when you click and buy from Amazon.com.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;My brother and I are neighbors and we have lawns that are green and well-manicured. So we are always worried about the idea of pests like fleas taking over the yards.
So, on the question of spraying the yard with dawn for fleas, I note that spraying
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pestpolicy.com/dawn-dish-soap-for-fleas/&#34;&gt;dawn dish soap&lt;/a&gt;
might be all thats required to eliminate those fleas from your yard. So just mix dish soap (1 ounce) with water in a garden sprayer and spray.
*I recommend that you repeat the spraying using a similar dawn dish soap solution every 10 to 12 days so that we exterminate all the fluids that could have survived and arents hatched yet. *
Despite that dish soap is an effective technique for controlling fleas there are other effective methods you can use to remove the bugs from your yard.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What Do Baby Lizards Eat? 7 Lizard Diets</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/what-do-baby-lizards-eat/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 04:06:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/what-do-baby-lizards-eat/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We may earn a commission when you click and buy from Amazon.com.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;What do baby lizards eat? What do lizards feed their young ones (also know as
&lt;a href=&#34;https://nhm.org/stories/tis-season-baby-lizards&#34;&gt;hatchlings&lt;/a&gt;
)? How do they do it and how long before they can go get their food?
Well, this article piece is all about lizard baby food -just like noted that
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pestpolicy.com/what-does-a-garden-lizard-eat/&#34;&gt;garden lizard eats caterpillars, insects, small crickets, and some greens and fruits&lt;/a&gt;
.
*But what do baby lizards eat?  *
*Baby lizards eat what their parents eat. Yes, they eat insects, roaches, plants, or even both. The only difference is the food ratio. Baby lizards only eat baby portions. For example, if they are eating an insect, the insect should be smaller than them. *
*Baby lizards eat by themselves. Nobody mashes up the prey for them. Its like a natural instinct in their DNA. They get the prey or plant and eat it up. You should note that a baby lizard will eat what its line of species eats. The other element that forms a baby lizards diet is the kind of environment it dwells in. *
[amazon bestseller=&amp;ldquo;Best Food for Baby Lizards&amp;rdquo; items=&amp;ldquo;2&amp;rdquo; template=&amp;ldquo;table&amp;rdquo;]
*A lizard can be carnivorous, insectivorous, herbivorous, or omnivorous.  A carnivorous lizard will eat insects or even small rodents and worms. The herbivores are vegetarians while the omnivores are on a balanced diet of vegetation and meat. Well, a pet lizard does not have very many options as the wild one but you need to know what to feed them and their young ones so that their dietary requirements are met. *&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>7 Best Flea Combs for Dogs 2025 Reviewed</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/best-flea-combs-for-dogs/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 04:04:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/best-flea-combs-for-dogs/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We may earn a commission when you click and buy from Amazon.com.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So, which is the best flea combs for dogs? Flea combs provide one of the safest means of controlling fleas in pets such as dogs.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;But first, you must learn&lt;a href=&#34;https://pestpolicy.com/how-to-use-a-flea-comb/&#34;&gt;how to correctly use a flea comb&lt;/a&gt;and know the&lt;a href=&#34;https://pestpolicy.com/how-to-tell-if-you-have-fleas/&#34;&gt;signs of a flea infestation&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;They also help remove other parasites, flea eggs, and unwanted stuff like dirt, loose fur, and flaky skin.
When used alongside other treatments, its possible to eradicate
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pestpolicy.com/can-dog-fleas-transfer-to-humans/&#34;&gt;fleas from your dogs&lt;/a&gt;
completely. Read Also:
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pestpolicy.com/best-electronic-flea-comb/&#34;&gt;What&amp;rsquo;s the best electronic flea comb?&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;in-a-hurry-view-these-cat-flea-shampoos&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;In a Hurry? View these Cat Flea Shampoos&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;[amazon bestseller=&amp;ldquo;Best Flea Combs for Dogs&amp;rdquo; items=&amp;ldquo;2&amp;rdquo; template=&amp;ldquo;table&amp;rdquo;]&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Do Fleas Drown in Water? Floated or Submerged?</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/do-fleas-drown-in-water/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 03:44:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/do-fleas-drown-in-water/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We may earn a commission when you click and buy from Amazon.com.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Do you have fleas in your home, or on pets like cats and dogs, and have been trying to kill them by drowning? Well, fleas flourish in dusty conditions but is water a risk to the bug&amp;rsquo;s survival?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;**So, do fleas drown in water? Yes, ****fleas will drown within 24 hours ****when submerged in water and may float alive for up to 7 days when drop fleas on the water surface - floating. **&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;**But if you add some dish soap to the water, it breaks down the surface tension making the fleas sink. **
[amazon bestseller=&amp;ldquo;Best Killer for Fleas&amp;rdquo; items=&amp;ldquo;2&amp;rdquo; template=&amp;ldquo;table&amp;rdquo;]
Related:
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pestpolicy.com/best-fogger-for-fleas/&#34;&gt;Flea Bombs that work&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;details-do-fleas-drown-in-water&#34;&gt;Details: Do Fleas Drown In Water?&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For the fleas to drown in water, it will depend on the surface tension of the water that you are subjecting them to. Further, it also matters whether you float or submerge the fleas.
In water with normal surface tension, fleas will just float and even jump away from danger. But if they submerge the fleas in normal water, they&amp;rsquo;ll drown within 24 hours - you may also use
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pestpolicy.com/best-flea-trap/&#34;&gt;flea traps&lt;/a&gt;
.
But if you put fleas in dish soap water, they will drown in a matter of seconds. Next time you consider drowning as a means of eliminating fleas from your area, you are wrong.
&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=UJeDI9vw6eA&#34;&gt;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=UJeDI9vw6eA&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cat Fleas Vs Dog Fleas - A Deep Comparison</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/cat-fleas-vs-dog-fleas/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 03:37:49 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/cat-fleas-vs-dog-fleas/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We may earn a commission when you click and buy from Amazon.com.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There are two main types of fleas that live on cats and dogs - cat fleas and dog fleas. If you want to know the difference between cat fleas vs dog fleas, read on!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;*When our vet informed us that we needed to start treating our dog for cat fleas, I was confused. We don&amp;rsquo;t have a cat and haven&amp;rsquo;t had any in our yard that I know of. *
&lt;em&gt;Let me surprise you!&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;One of the most frequent questions that pet owners ask is this: do cat fleas (&lt;em&gt;Ctenocephalides felis&lt;/em&gt;) exclusively attack cats, while dog fleas (&lt;em&gt;Ctenocephalides canis&lt;/em&gt;) live only off dogs?
**So, how do **
**cat fleas compare to dog fleas? While they&amp;rsquo;re different species (only differentiable under a **
&lt;strong&gt;microscope&lt;/strong&gt;
**), dog and cat fleas can infest either cats or dogs. But **
&lt;strong&gt;cat fleas (&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Ctenocephalides felis&lt;/strong&gt;
**) are more common in North America than dog fleas. **
Let&amp;rsquo;s check the details!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;[amazon bestseller=&amp;ldquo;Cat Fleas Vs Dog Fleas&amp;rdquo; items=&amp;ldquo;2&amp;rdquo; template=&amp;ldquo;table&amp;rdquo;]&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Check for Fleas? 7 Steps (with Pictures)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/how-to-check-for-fleas/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 03:34:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/how-to-check-for-fleas/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We may earn a commission when you click and buy from Amazon.com.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;dl&gt;
&lt;dt&gt;Below I&amp;rsquo;ve outlined how to check for fleas. Sadly, this thought triggers an&lt;/dt&gt;
&lt;dt&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://pestpolicy.com/do-fleas-stay-on-humans/&#34;&gt;itching feeling in me&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/dt&gt;
&lt;dd&gt;does my dog have fleas? Or is it just unfounded fear?
Since I acquired my dog pet: my fluffy king, I have had numerous challenges. Some of them include feed selection,
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pestpolicy.com/best-flea-treatment-for-dogs/&#34;&gt;flea medication selection&lt;/a&gt;
, and safety.
However, none of the above challenges with my dog has been
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pestpolicy.com/can-dog-fleas-transfer-to-humans/&#34;&gt;disturbing as seeing fleas&lt;/a&gt;
running on my pet. I tried numerous flea treatments, but the fleas always came back.
[amazon bestseller=&amp;ldquo;Best Killer for Fleas&amp;rdquo; items=&amp;ldquo;2&amp;rdquo; template=&amp;ldquo;table&amp;rdquo;]&lt;/dd&gt;
&lt;/dl&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;how-to-check-for-fleas-7-steps-with-pictures&#34;&gt;How to Check for Fleas? 7 Steps (with Pictures)&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To check for dog fleas on your pet, you will require the following tools; a
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pestpolicy.com/best-electronic-flea-comb/&#34;&gt;flea comb&lt;/a&gt;
,
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pestpolicy.com/dawn-dish-soap-for-fleas/&#34;&gt;soaped water&lt;/a&gt;
, and a white kitchen paper.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Can Cats Get Fleas in the Winter?</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/can-cats-get-fleas-in-the-winter/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 03:32:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/can-cats-get-fleas-in-the-winter/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We may earn a commission when you click and buy from Amazon.com.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The drier regions of the Midwest and Southwest have a &amp;ldquo;flea season&amp;rdquo; in some months of the year. But in balmy states such as Florida, fleas are highly active and reproduce throughout the year.
So, its no brainer that one reader asked: Can cats get fleas in the winter regardless of my region?
&lt;strong&gt;The simple answer is YES&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Best Flea Spray for Carpets</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/best-flea-spray-for-carpets/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 03:29:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/best-flea-spray-for-carpets/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We may earn a commission when you click and buy from Amazon.com.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Keeping your carpets free from fleas is essential for maintaining a healthy and comfortable home environment. Fleas can quickly infest carpets, causing discomfort to pets and family members. Choosing the best flea spray for carpets can effectively eliminate these pests and prevent reinfestations. Lets explore the top-rated options available on Amazon to help you make an informed decision.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Kill Flea Eggs (4 Easy Methods)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/how-to-kill-flea-eggs/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 03:03:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/how-to-kill-flea-eggs/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We may earn a commission when you click and buy from Amazon.com.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Let&amp;rsquo;s discuss what kills flea eggs in your yard or in
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pestpolicy.com/best-indoor-flea-killer/&#34;&gt;indoor spaces&lt;/a&gt;
. Honestly, there aren&amp;rsquo;t many things that&amp;rsquo;ll kill flea eggs  - they&amp;rsquo;re supper hardy.
Fleas will jump off from the cats and dogs to lays their eggs on pet bedding or even house carpeting. Any unattended fleas eggs will hatch to a major flea infestation within a month.
*In summary, here&amp;rsquo;s how to kill flea eggs; vacuuming carpets, rugs and floors will remove the flea eggs dropped by your cats or dogs. Vacuuming will clean up flea larvae and their food (flea dirt). In addition, vacuuming makes the fleas to emerge from the insecticide-resistant cocoons - exposing them to treatment.  *&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>7 Best Flea Treatment for Kittens 2025 Reviewed</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/best-flea-treatment-for-kittens/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 02:40:53 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/best-flea-treatment-for-kittens/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We may earn a commission when you click and buy from Amazon.com.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Your
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pestpolicy.com/&#34;&gt;kitten&amp;rsquo;s health&lt;/a&gt;
is paramount. The flea-infested kittens may suffer from Bartonella, Anemia, Flea Allergy Dermatitis, or tapeworm.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proper medical treatment and prevention are essential if you desire to keep your kitten free from diseases.
So, what are the best treatment for kittens available? Well, that&amp;rsquo;s the topic of discussion in this post.
So, lets get started.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;in-a-hurry-check-these-cat-flea-shampoos&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;In a Hurry? Check these Cat Flea Shampoos&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;[amazon bestseller=&amp;ldquo;Best Flea Treatment for Kittens&amp;rdquo; items=&amp;ldquo;2&amp;rdquo; template=&amp;ldquo;table&amp;rdquo;]&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Getting Rid of Fleas in the Carpet</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/getting-rid-of-fleas-in-the-carpet/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 02:39:30 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/getting-rid-of-fleas-in-the-carpet/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We may earn a commission when you click and buy from Amazon.com.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It&amp;rsquo;s hard to spot fleas in the carpet fibers, and many treatments
&lt;a href=&#34;https://entomology.ca.uky.edu/ef602&#34;&gt;can&amp;rsquo;t reach deep down&lt;/a&gt;
where they hide.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So, if you&amp;rsquo;re looking for effective ways of getting rid of fleas in the carpet - we&amp;rsquo;ve got lots of ideas! Maybe it&amp;rsquo;s through vacuuming or steam cleaning?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In this PestPolicy guide, this is what I&amp;rsquo;ll be exploring:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;How do fleas end up in your carpet?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;How long do fleas live in carpets?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;What Should I Do with Flea-Infested Furniture and Carpet?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;3 steps to getting rid of fleas in the carpet - fastest way&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;What Can I Use for Fleas on my Furniture?
[amazon bestseller=&amp;ldquo;Best Flea Killers for Carpets&amp;rdquo; items=&amp;ldquo;2&amp;rdquo; template=&amp;ldquo;table&amp;rdquo;]&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;how-do-fleas-end-up-in-your-carpet&#34;&gt;How do fleas end up in your carpet?&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The simplest explanation for how fleas (and flea eggs) end up on your carpet is that they jump from one dog or cat to another, or even worse, from the outdoors into a home.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Do Flea Collars Work?</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/do-flea-collars-work/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 02:35:37 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/do-flea-collars-work/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We may earn a commission when you click and buy from Amazon.com.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Current flea collars are more comfortable, adjustable, non-greasy with flexible designs. Manufactures claim flea collars will offer more extended flea protection (up to months). But
*do flea collars work?  *
&lt;strong&gt;In Summary&lt;/strong&gt;
*, YES, fleas collars will kill fleas on pets, including cats and dogs. But flea collars are different - some will repel fleas, others will kill, some kill baby fleas but other target adult fleas. *
*But go for flea collars whose technology is adequately tested and designed - consult a veterinarian, check the product&amp;rsquo;s label claims or the manufacturers website. *&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Can Humans Carry Fleas from One Home to Another?</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/can-humans-carry-fleas-from-one-home-to-another/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 02:21:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/can-humans-carry-fleas-from-one-home-to-another/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We may earn a commission when you click and buy from Amazon.com.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Fleas are tiny pests that primarily infest dogs and cats, feeding on their blood and causing itching, allergies, and even diseases. But what about humans?
&lt;strong&gt;Can we carry fleas from one house to another?&lt;/strong&gt;
The answer is
&lt;strong&gt;yes - but its uncommon&lt;/strong&gt;
. Unlike bed bugs or ticks, fleas dont prefer human hosts. However, they can
&lt;strong&gt;hitchhike on clothing, shoes, or skin&lt;/strong&gt;
, especially after contact with infested pets or environments.
This guide covers:&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>At What Temperature Do Fleas Die?</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/at-what-temperature-do-fleas-die/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 02:08:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/at-what-temperature-do-fleas-die/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We may earn a commission when you click and buy from Amazon.com.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Using heat is one of the many ways of
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pestpolicy.com/home-remedies-for-fleas/&#34;&gt;getting rid of fleas in your home&lt;/a&gt;
. But what temperatures do fleas die? Well, this is the right place to find your answers.
**Fleas die if exposed to a temperature above 35 C (95F) and temperatures below 8C (46.4F). If it is the immature adults, they die from temperatures as low as 13C (55.4F). Fleas cannot also survive the frozen winter temperatures. Those that do so hide under the fur of warm-blooded animals. **
[amazon bestseller=&amp;ldquo;Best Killer for Fleas&amp;rdquo; items=&amp;ldquo;2&amp;rdquo; template=&amp;ldquo;table&amp;rdquo;]
There are lots of things to know when
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pestpolicy.com/what-kills-fleas-on-contact/&#34;&gt;controlling fleas with temperature&lt;/a&gt;
. Join me in this article as we discuss them and the various options you can apply.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>7 Best Fogger for Fleas 2025 - Flea Bombs</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/best-fogger-for-fleas/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 01:58:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/best-fogger-for-fleas/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We may earn a commission when you click and buy from Amazon.com.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When selecting the best flea fogger, key considerations include effectiveness, coverage area, safety, ease of use, and duration of protection. Effective products like
&lt;strong&gt;Hot Shot HG-20177&lt;/strong&gt;
and
&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B001JTADUI?th=1&amp;amp;linkCode=ll1&amp;amp;tag=p-policy-20&amp;amp;linkId=fedb25230bdd71b590ab0c6ed52e2a1e&amp;amp;language=en_US&amp;amp;ref_=as_li_ss_tl&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Raid Max Fogger&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;
eliminate fleas and their eggs, with options like Black Flag designed for larger spaces and TAT Fogger for smaller areas.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Safety is crucial, especially for households with pets or children, with options like Zoecon Precor Plus offering safer formulations for
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pestpolicy.com/where-do-fleas-hide/&#34;&gt;your home&lt;/a&gt;
. Easy-to-use foggers, such as Hartz UltraGuard Plus, simplify the application process. For long-lasting results, consider products like Spectracide Bug Stop, which provides up to 7 months of protection.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What Kills Fleas on Contact?</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/what-kills-fleas-on-contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 01:47:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/what-kills-fleas-on-contact/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We may earn a commission when you click and buy from Amazon.com.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The question is; what kills fleas on contact? Will the remedy be safe for me and my pets? What product will
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pestpolicy.com/how-to-get-rid-of-fleas/&#34;&gt;tackle the flea infestation effectively&lt;/a&gt;
?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In this article, I&amp;rsquo;ve detailed the answer to this question. There are many flea-killing products like medicated drops, shampoos, repellents, and sprays - but they take time to work.
&lt;strong&gt;But what kills fleas on contact? Well, rubbing alcohol (isopropyl alcohol) will kill adult fleas on contact - it&amp;rsquo;s best applied on flea-infested bedding or yard. Also,&lt;/strong&gt;
** dawn dish soap kills flea eggs (via suffocation); thus, they won&amp;rsquo;t reproduce, infest, or hatch. **&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Can Bearded Dragons Eat Tomatoes? 7 Secrets</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/can-bearded-dragons-eat-tomatoes/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 01:25:39 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/can-bearded-dragons-eat-tomatoes/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We may earn a commission when you click and buy from Amazon.com.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Tomatoes are delicious and
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pestpolicy.com/what-do-bearded-dragons-eat/&#34;&gt;healthy veggie-like fruits&lt;/a&gt;
on taco or salad. But, can bearded dragons eat tomatoes? Well, the aim when feeding the bearded dragons (omnivores) must be safety first and getting a balanced diet to maintain a healthy living.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;C&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;*an bearded dragons eat tomatoes? As with most fruits, the ****short answer is affirmative. Well, Yes and NO; bearded dragons can eat just 1/4 a tomato each meoht ***
***without causing harm to their health. ***
***Tomatoes are a good source of vitamin A, for bearded dragons. But as with any other fruits, bearded dragons must not eat tomatoes as the main diet. Bearded dragons require only a small amount of vitamin A, and the acidic content in tomatoes can harm your smart beard. ***
[amazon bestseller=&amp;ldquo;Food for Bearded Dragons&amp;rdquo; items=&amp;ldquo;2&amp;rdquo; template=&amp;ldquo;table&amp;rdquo;]&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Can You Use Human Shampoo on Cats?</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/can-you-use-human-shampoo-on-cats/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 01:25:39 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/can-you-use-human-shampoo-on-cats/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We may earn a commission when you click and buy from Amazon.com.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Cats love that clean life, they&amp;rsquo;ll grom their skin regularly removing any dirt, dead skin, or loose fur. But, if you&amp;rsquo;re to clean off piles of mud from the pet, can you use human shampoo on cats?
**Simple answer, NO, don&amp;rsquo;t use human shampoo on cats - human shampoo&amp;rsquo;s pH imbalance makes it aggressive and will make the pet&amp;rsquo;s skin dry out. **
**Also, human shampoo may cause painful irritation and flakiness on the cat. So, talk to the cat&amp;rsquo;s veterinarian about mild shampoos that will be great for your cat. **&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Do Squirrels Carry Fleas?</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/do-squirrels-carry-fleas/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 01:17:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/do-squirrels-carry-fleas/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We may earn a commission when you click and buy from Amazon.com.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Well, it is hard to
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pestpolicy.com/how-to-get-rid-of-fleas-in-the-house-fast/&#34;&gt;get rid of fleas at your home&lt;/a&gt;
if you don&amp;rsquo;t know where they are coming from. So, really, do squirrels carry fleas?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Wildlife, particularly rodents can easily deposit
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pestpolicy.com/best-flea-spray-for-yard/&#34;&gt;eggs or larvae around your yard&lt;/a&gt;
which brings a host of challenges for humans.
&lt;strong&gt;To answer this question, YES - squirrels carry fleas. The pests and their eggs can be dropped from the squirrel&amp;rsquo;s fur and fall off on your garden&lt;/strong&gt;
**, lawn, or yard as the rodent walks through. **
**Fleas jump and attach themselves to their hosts, humans, and animals alike including squirrels. The fleas&amp;rsquo; eggs or larvae that fall off can infest your property when they hatch into adulthood. **
[amazon bestseller=&amp;ldquo;Best Fleas Killers&amp;rdquo; items=&amp;ldquo;2&amp;rdquo; template=&amp;ldquo;table&amp;rdquo;]&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Long Does It Take For Steam to Kill Fleas</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/how-long-does-it-take-for-steam-to-kill-fleas/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 01:16:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/how-long-does-it-take-for-steam-to-kill-fleas/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We may earn a commission when you click and buy from Amazon.com.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Fleas will attack your
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pestpolicy.com/can-humans-carry-fleas-from-one-home-to-another/&#34;&gt;carpets, furniture, and clothing&lt;/a&gt;
in your home - quickly growing into a major problem. Many homeowners turn to pesticides to remove fleas, but some may be harmful to humans and pets. However, hot &amp;amp; pressurized steam is a suitable, non-chemical method to kill fleas.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;But on the question of how long that steam will take to kill the fleas depends on different factors such as the duration of exposure and the steam temperature - you may still need to vacuum.
So, in this post, I&amp;rsquo;ll outline the time steam requires to kill these fleas. Further, I&amp;rsquo;ll recommend the most
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pestpolicy.com/best-steam-cleaner-for-fleas/&#34;&gt;suitable steam cleaner&lt;/a&gt;
that I&amp;rsquo;ve found so far for removing fleas and cleaning.
**Typically, exposing fleas to steam at a temperature of 203F (95C) for a minimum of 30 seconds can kill both adult fleas and their eggs. But positing the steam hose for a long time such as 2 minutes on an area that has fleas will kill all these bugs. **&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;review-how-long-does-it-take-for-steam-to-kill-fleas&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Review: How Long Does It Take For Steam to Kill Fleas&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Steam at 203F (95C) will kill both adult fleas and fleas eggs in about 30 seconds.  However, exterminators recommend that you vacuum the spaces to be steamed - this should be done prior to and after the flea steaming process.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Does White Vinegar Kill Fleas?</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/does-white-vinegar-kill-fleas/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 01:09:51 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/does-white-vinegar-kill-fleas/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We may earn a commission when you click and buy from Amazon.com.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Vinegar is a common household ingredient that you will find around the kitchen but it can also have varied applications around the house.
Flea bites are painful and they may cause the transmission of diseases. Further, removing fleas from your house and pets is challenging and expensive but you can use some home remedies.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;**So, does white vinegar (acetic acid) kill fleas? In summary, no, spraying the cider vinegar on the dog bed or rugs wouldn&amp;rsquo;t kill fleas but it will help repel the pests from your house and pets. **&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;**The reason is that the vinegar acid is relatively weak to break through the shells of flea larvae and free eggs. **
**However, adult fleas tend to avoid pets such as cats and dogs that are sprayed with white vinegar. But the vinegar solution won&amp;rsquo;t kill the adult fleas. **&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;details-is-white-vinegar-a-good-diy-flea-spray&#34;&gt;Details: is white vinegar a good DIY flea spray?&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Control or prevention of fleas requires that you kill or sterilize the flea
**larvae **
and flea eggs.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What Kills Fleas in the Yard Naturally?</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/what-kills-fleas-in-the-yard-naturally/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 01:03:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/what-kills-fleas-in-the-yard-naturally/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We may earn a commission when you click and buy from Amazon.com.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Using pesticide sprays, among other
&lt;a href=&#34;https://extension.tennessee.edu/publications/Documents/PB1596.pdf&#34;&gt;chemical flea control methods&lt;/a&gt;
, is considered the best way to control fleas in every Yard.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;But other home remedies are equally effective for someone who would like to try a DIY approach.
So,
what kills fleas in the yard naturally?
So, check the below home remedies:
[amazon bestseller=&amp;ldquo;Best Flea Spray for Yard&amp;rdquo; items=&amp;ldquo;2&amp;rdquo; template=&amp;ldquo;table&amp;rdquo;]&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;1-diatomaceous-earth&#34;&gt;1. Diatomaceous earth&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://pestpolicy.com/diatomaceous-earth-for-fleas/&#34;&gt;Diatomaceous Earth (DE) for fleas&lt;/a&gt;
has silica shards that&amp;rsquo;ll cut through the fleas&amp;rsquo; waxy exoskeleton causing dehydration and eventual death of the bugs and the flea larvae.
Luckily, the Food-grade DE will be safe to use around human beings and animals. Avoid the DE that&amp;rsquo;s used in charcoal filters or swimming pools.
The razor-sharp edges of the crushed Diatomaceous Earth will kill the fleas through dehydration. However, ensure to wear kitchen or garden gloves to avoid drying the hands.
The next step will be sprinkling DE on soft furniture, dog beds, and carpet. Allow DE to settle and do its magic for about three days.
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pestpolicy.com/best-vacuum-for-fleas/&#34;&gt;Vacuum the surfaces thoroughly to kill fleas&lt;/a&gt;
, their eggs, and also larvae.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>7 Home Remedies for Fleas - Natural Treatment</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/home-remedies-for-fleas/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 01:01:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/home-remedies-for-fleas/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We may earn a commission when you click and buy from Amazon.com.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For most home and pet owners,
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pestpolicy.com/what-do-fleas-look-like/&#34;&gt;a flea infestation (see images)&lt;/a&gt;
can cause panic. Below I&amp;rsquo;ve discussed the 7 top home remedies for fleas - they&amp;rsquo;re useful, convenient, and budget-friendly.
Fleas bite humans and pets to suck blood, leading to anemia and
&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.petmd.com/dog/parasites/4-surprising-flea-diseases-you-need-know&#34;&gt;transmission of diseases&lt;/a&gt;
such as Tularemia, Tungiansis, Murine typhus, and Bubonic plague.
&lt;em&gt;In summary, you can keep your cats, dogs (including dips, flea combs&lt;/em&gt;
*), and home being flea-free using simple home remedies that are effective and safe equally - control on the carpet and furniture - including killing flea eggs. *&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Are Leopard Geckos Nocturnal?</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/are-leopard-geckos-nocturnal/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 00:50:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/are-leopard-geckos-nocturnal/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We may earn a commission when you click and buy from Amazon.com.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Leopard geckos are terrestrial animals that mostly live on the ground and under rocks. Naturally, you will find them in the Middle East and Asia in countries like Iran, Afghanistan and India. So,
*are leopard geckos nocturnal? *
**In summary, contrary to popular belief Leopard geckos **are crepuscular and not nocturnal. They are not active the whole night, but you&amp;rsquo;ll only enjoy them at fading light at dusk and dawn during twilight. ****
****Leopard geckos difference from the rest of nocturnal gecko is they have large eyes and ears so they can see and hear clearly at night. ****&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>7 Best Shark Vacuum for Pet Hair 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/best-shark-vacuum-for-pet-hair/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 00:42:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/best-shark-vacuum-for-pet-hair/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We may earn a commission when you click and buy from Amazon.com.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Pet hair gets into our homes and almost goes unnoticeable. Conventional cleaning methods may not effectively remove pet hair from the floor, carpets, and upholstery.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fortunately, Shark makes some of the best vacuum cleaners for pet hair - such as this&lt;a href=&#34;https://patents.google.com/patent/US9374982B2/en&#34;&gt;Pet groomer and vacuum cleaner&lt;/a&gt;.
So, which is the best shark vacuum for pet hair? In this guide, I have reviewed the seven best shark
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pestpolicy.com/best-cordless-vacuum-for-pet-hair/&#34;&gt;vacuum cleaners ideal for pet hair&lt;/a&gt;
removal.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;in-a-rush-see-my-top-chipmunk-repellents&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;In a Rush? See my Top Chipmunk Repellents&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;[amazon bestseller=&amp;ldquo;Best Shark Vacuum for Pet Hair&amp;rdquo; items=&amp;ldquo;2&amp;rdquo; template=&amp;ldquo;table&amp;rdquo;]&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What Can I Eat or Drink to Keep Fleas from Biting Me?</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/what-can-i-eat-or-drink-to-keep-fleas-from-biting-me/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 00:34:33 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/what-can-i-eat-or-drink-to-keep-fleas-from-biting-me/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We may earn a commission when you click and buy from Amazon.com.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Fleas can be an irritating problem, especially if youve got pets or spend time outdoors. While there are plenty of
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pestpolicy.com/flea-repellent-for-humans/&#34;&gt;repellents, sprays&lt;/a&gt;
and treatments out there, did you know that what you eat and drink could also make a difference in keeping fleas away?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Heres a down-to-earth guide on how some simple dietary changes might help you avoid those pesky flea bites.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Keep Fleas off Me While I Sleep</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/how-to-keep-fleas-off-me-while-i-sleep/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 00:08:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/how-to-keep-fleas-off-me-while-i-sleep/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We may earn a commission when you click and buy from Amazon.com.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When fleas jump onto your bed they&amp;rsquo;ll make your sleep comfortable and queen inflict flea bites that are painful.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So, you ask, how to keep fleas off me while I sleep? In brief, cover your skin with long-sleeve and clothing (pants and socks), and treat the gear and clothing with 0.5% permethrin-containing flea control products.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Other precautions you may take include&lt;a href=&#34;https://pestpolicy.com/how-did-my-dog-get-fleas/&#34;&gt;vacuuming the carpets&lt;/a&gt;and upholstered furniture, laundering the bedding and clothing
Lets dig in!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;details-how-to-keep-fleas-off-me-while-i-sleep&#34;&gt;Details: How to Keep Fleas off Me While I Sleep&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It can be challenging to control the biting tendencies of fleas and they&amp;rsquo;re spread in the house especially when they get onto bedding or bed.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NEAT™ Steam Cleaner by Dupray - Best Steam Cleaner</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/neat-steam-cleaner-by-dupray-best-steam-cleaner/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 00:08:33 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/neat-steam-cleaner-by-dupray-best-steam-cleaner/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We may earn a commission when you click and buy from Amazon.com.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In our daily lives, maintaining a clean and hygienic environment has become more critical than ever.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As we spend more time at home, the accumulation of dirt, grime, and germs necessitates a smarter, more effective approach to cleaning. Enter the
&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07C44DM6D?ref=t_ac_view_request_product_image&amp;amp;campaignId=amzn1.campaign.25TY7YR61EF6R&amp;amp;linkCode=tr1&amp;amp;tag=1563-20&amp;amp;linkId=amzn1.campaign.25TY7YR61EF6R_1701354325039&#34;&gt;NEAT Steam Cleaner by Dupray&lt;/a&gt;
a game-changing solution designed to simplify and elevate the cleaning experience.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;unveiling-the-neat-steam-cleaner&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Unveiling the NEAT Steam Cleaner&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;At first glance, the NEAT Steam Cleaner by Dupray stands out with its sleek and modern design. However, its true essence lies in its superior functionality.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Top 7 Best Flea Trap Reviewed</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/best-flea-trap/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 00:07:37 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/best-flea-trap/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We may earn a commission when you click and buy from Amazon.com.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When choosing the best flea trap, you can consider things like effectiveness, ease of use, safety, and durability. Flea traps are essential tools for controlling flea infestations in your home, offering a non-toxic and convenient way to keep these pests under control.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This guide will help you understand the key factors to consider when selecting a flea trap and provide you with top product recommendations such as
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pestpolicy.com/flea-life-cycle/&#34;&gt;adult fleas in the life cycle&lt;/a&gt;
!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
