<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Recording on Insights</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/categories/recording/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Recording on Insights</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- 0.147.3</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 07 May 2025 12:21:29 +0300</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/categories/recording/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Jordan Bartee at the CalArts Machine Lab</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jordan-bartee-at-the-calarts-machine-lab/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 21:53:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jordan-bartee-at-the-calarts-machine-lab/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We may earn a commission when you click and buy from Amazon.com.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Jordan Bartee is a renowned innovator and creative force in the field of digital arts and design. His work at the CalArts Machine Lab highlights his dedication to merging technology with artistic expression, creating groundbreaking projects that challenge conventional boundaries.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;who-is-jordan-bartee&#34;&gt;Who is Jordan Bartee?&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Jordan Bartee is a digital artist, educator, and technologist whose expertise spans interactive design, machine learning, and experimental music. His association with the California Institute of the Arts (CalArts) Machine Lab underscores his commitment to fostering creativity through technology.
Bartees work explores the intersection of art and technology, often utilizing advanced tools and techniques such as programming, robotics, and artificial intelligence to produce innovative projects.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>7 Best Belt Sander for Deck 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/best-belt-sander-for-deck/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 21:46:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/best-belt-sander-for-deck/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We may earn a commission when you click and buy from Amazon.com.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Whats the best
&lt;a href=&#34;http://web.mit.edu/course/other/machineshop/BeltSander/&#34;&gt;belt sander&lt;/a&gt;
for the deck? Choosing the right sander is essential when you are dealing with a large volume of wood. Additionally, although bridges are built out of highly durable woods, they need to be sanded diligently.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you are a DIYer looking to refinish that aging deck in the backyard, you need the sander to achieve a clean look.
What about the length and width of the sanding platform? If you are looking for more precision, the ideal pick should feature a shorter and narrower belt.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>English horn vs Oboe</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/english-horn-vs-oboe/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 17:22:39 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/english-horn-vs-oboe/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We may earn a commission when you click and buy from Amazon.com.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I was not always a woodwind player but I was thinking of the difference &amp;amp; similarities between English Horn (Cor Anglais) and
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pestpolicy.com/what-is-an-oboe/&#34;&gt;Oboe&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;English horn vs Oboe.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Sadly, all I could think of was that they are both in the woodwind family, can found in the orchestra, and are all played using reeds.
Well, I thought they were lame answers too! And so I got down to business researching. Read Also:
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pestpolicy.com/best-laptop-for-music-production/&#34;&gt;Laptop for Music Production&lt;/a&gt;
.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What is Piccolo?</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/what-is-piccolo/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 07:36:45 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/what-is-piccolo/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We may earn a commission when you click and buy from Amazon.com.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;What is Piccolo? Ive been a flutist for 5 years, but I also play the piccolo. In comparison to the flute, the
&lt;a href=&#34;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Piccolo&#34;&gt;piccolo has a higher tone&lt;/a&gt;
.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;However, the piccolo is much smaller than the flute: being smaller and shorter thus considered a lower instrument.
To play piccolo, youll need to add or subtract through lifting our fingers and thats what changes the length of the tube inside and hence alter the notes.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What is an oboe?</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/what-is-an-oboe/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 07:34:23 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/what-is-an-oboe/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We may earn a commission when you click and buy from Amazon.com.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The World Guinness Records documents oboe and French horn are the hardest instruments of all to play. But, what is an oboe? How will it fit into your solo work on the orchestra?
Well, I have to state that the French horn is difficult to play but the oboe - woodwind instrument - is the hardest. By definition, the Oboe  the treble instrument - (pronounced as
&lt;em&gt;OH-boh&lt;/em&gt;
) is a
&lt;a href=&#34;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Woodwind_instrument&#34;&gt;woodwind instruments&lt;/a&gt;
, double-reed mouthpiece to be specific.
Well, the regular oboe would play the soprano or treble range. Notably, Oboes can be made from synthetic materials but mainly wood is the main material. Read Also:
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pestpolicy.com/best-sd-card-for-raspberry-pi-3/&#34;&gt;SD Card for Raspberry Pi 3&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>7 Free Autotune vst Plugins 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/free-autotune-vst-plugins/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 01:23:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/free-autotune-vst-plugins/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We may earn a commission when you click and buy from Amazon.com.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Here&amp;rsquo;s a comparison guide between free Autotune vst plugins. In an attempt to get the best vocal and musical instrumental sound output, producers creatively use the autotune plugins to fine-tune the sounds.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;These plugins also allow you to fix certain imperfections in the sound so as to improve the overall performance of the vocalist.
So, which free autotune
&lt;a href=&#34;http://cseweb.ucsd.edu/~little/vst-plugins/&#34;&gt;VST plugins&lt;/a&gt;
can give you the best fine-tuning results.
Below is a detailed review of the best free autotune plugins commonly used by top-notch producers. Read Also: Check these
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pestpolicy.com/best-mac-for-music-production/&#34;&gt;music production macs&lt;/a&gt;
.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
