<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Lizard on Insights</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/categories/lizard/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Lizard on Insights</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- 0.147.1</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 07 May 2025 12:21:29 +0300</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/categories/lizard/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>What&#39;s the House Lizards&#39; Lifespan?</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/house-lizard-lifespan/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 23:24:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/house-lizard-lifespan/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We may earn a commission when you click and buy from Amazon.com.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;House Lizard Lifespan - Probably you have come across the house lizard (commonly known as house gecko) in your house, yard, compound or zoo and wonder how long
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pestpolicy.com/are-lizards-vertebrates-or-invertebrates/&#34;&gt;these vertebrate&lt;/a&gt;
s live. Could House Lizards live just like human beings or survive for a couple of weeks?
*So, whats the house lizards lifespan? *
**The simple answer is, house lizard live for 4 to 6 years on average. However, this lifespan is subject to factors such as the care given, environment/climate and availability of basic needs for the house lizard. **
**Some house lizards may even live slightly longer than 6 years if the above factors are maintained. On the other hand, skin shedding problems and wounding occurrences may lower the lifespan of the house lizards. **
[amazon bestseller=&amp;ldquo;Best Food for House Lizards&amp;rdquo; items=&amp;ldquo;2&amp;rdquo; template=&amp;ldquo;table&amp;rdquo;]&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Are Mushrooms Safe for Bearded Dragons? Risks &amp; Alternatives</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/can-bearded-dragons-eat-mushrooms/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 23:23:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/can-bearded-dragons-eat-mushrooms/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We may earn a commission when you click and buy from Amazon.com.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Bearded dragons enjoy a diverse and balanced diet that includes leafy greens such as collard greens and
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pestpolicy.com/can-bearded-dragons-eat-cabbage/&#34;&gt;cabbage&lt;/a&gt;
, as well as vegetables like bell peppers,
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pestpolicy.com/can-bearded-dragons-eat-tomatoes/&#34;&gt;tomatoes&lt;/a&gt;
, and
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pestpolicy.com/can-bearded-dragons-eat-carrots/&#34;&gt;carrots&lt;/a&gt;
.
However, it is crucial to carefully assess the food you offer to these unique and docile reptiles, as some foods may be unsafe for their consumption.
So, mushrooms: are they safe for Bearded Dragons?
*In summary, it&amp;rsquo;s generally unsafe to feed mushrooms to bearded dragons - despite these bites having essential nutrients. Although mushrooms have essential nutrients, many varieties, including wild mushrooms, are toxic to reptiles, including bearded dragons. *&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Do Cats Eat Lizards?</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/do-cats-eat-lizards/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 23:06:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/do-cats-eat-lizards/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We may earn a commission when you click and buy from Amazon.com.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Do Cats Eat Lizards? Have you ever met lizards and cats together in your home, yard or compound? Can your lizard and cat pet live together? It is interesting to find how cats go along with lizards in your place? So, do cats eat lizards?
*The direct answer is YES! Cats will eat lizards. Cats are great lizard predators. They will hunt, kill and eat lizard either by cutting it into pieces or swallow it whole (for the small sized cats). *
*Cats prefer eating smaller lizards such as geckos, skins and Savannah lizards. However, depending on the species, cats may not be safe after eating lizards. Some species such as salamanders and juvenile blue-tailed skinks secrets poison in their skin, which may kill your cat if eaten. *
[amazon bestseller=&amp;ldquo;Best Food for Lizards&amp;rdquo; items=&amp;ldquo;2&amp;rdquo; template=&amp;ldquo;table&amp;rdquo;]
&lt;em&gt;Though house lizards (gecko) may not have venom or poison, they carry parasites (liver flukes), pathogens and bacteria (salmonella) which affect adversely on the health of your cat when eaten.&lt;/em&gt;
Related:
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pestpolicy.com/is-wall-gecko-poisonous-if-eaten/&#34;&gt;Is Wall Gecko Poisonous If Eaten?&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Can Lizards Swim? Can they Drown?</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/can-lizards-swim/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 21:41:37 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/can-lizards-swim/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We may earn a commission when you click and buy from Amazon.com.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Could be you have come across lizards in a pond, river, sea, ocean, or stagnant water at your home and wonder how they move about. How do they cross water bodies? So,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;can lizard Swim? *
**The direct answer is, YES! Lizards can swim in water bodies including rivers, seas, oceans, or pods. These reptiles use their tail to propel themselves forward when swimming plus use front limbs for vertical movement. **
**Some lizards like Gecko can even walk on water. Lizard, they&amp;rsquo;re vertebrates, such as Marine Iguanas can swim in deep seas or oceans down to the floor in search of food while holding their breath for 45 minutes. **
[amazon bestseller=&amp;ldquo;Best Food for Lizards&amp;rdquo; items=&amp;ldquo;2&amp;rdquo; template=&amp;ldquo;table&amp;rdquo;]&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;details-can-lizards-swim-can-they-drown-movement&#34;&gt;Details: Can Lizards Swim? Can they Drown? Movement&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Lizards can swim. The swimming capability varies from one species to another and is determined by body size, shape and length of the tail. Some lizard species such as Gecko and skinks can walk or run on the water bodies.
Marine Iguana lizards are known to swim in deep waters and can hold its breath for over 45 minutes while feeding on its prey at the floor of sea or ocean. Lizard such as sandfish or
&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.nytimes.com/2009/07/21/science/21obsand.html&#34;&gt;saharan lizard&lt;/a&gt;
can swim even on sand instead of walking.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Can Bearded Dragons Eat Apples? 7 Secrets</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/can-bearded-dragons-eat-apples/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 21:34:43 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/can-bearded-dragons-eat-apples/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We may earn a commission when you click and buy from Amazon.com.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Can bearded dragons eat apples? Well, your bearded dragon deserve the right food and diet to maintain great health. Maybe some
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pestpolicy.com/can-bearded-dragons-eat-cucumbers/&#34;&gt;cucumbers,&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pestpolicy.com/can-bearded-dragons-eat-cabbage/&#34;&gt;cabbage&lt;/a&gt;
, or
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pestpolicy.com/can-bearded-dragons-eat-mango/&#34;&gt;mango&lt;/a&gt;
.
But most of us wonder; which food or snacks should your avoid or give to beardies? Well,
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pestpolicy.com/what-do-bearded-dragons-eat/&#34;&gt;bearded dragons eat a variety of foods&lt;/a&gt;
like fruits, vegetables or commercial foods.
*But can bearded dragons eat apple? Yes, bearded dragons will eat apples. However, for a healthy diet, peel the apple&amp;rsquo;s skin and cut the fruit into small pieces. *
**Ensure the Caution - only feed apples like a treat because excessive apples will lead to runny stools. **
**Apples are a source of nutrients including vitamin C, proteins, fiber and so on. Apples also contain a lot of water which helps in hydrating your beardies. **
[amazon bestseller=&amp;ldquo;Food for Bearded Dragons&amp;rdquo; items=&amp;ldquo;2&amp;rdquo; template=&amp;ldquo;table&amp;rdquo;]&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Do Lizards Mate and Reproduce?</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/how-do-lizards-mate/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 20:59:04 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/how-do-lizards-mate/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We may earn a commission when you click and buy from Amazon.com.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;How Do Lizards Mate? Maybe you have pet lizards at home or have seen one and wishes to know how they mate. Do they court like human being before mating? Well, in this article we shall answer the question, How Do Lizards Mate?
*During Mating, the male lizard (vertebrates) clings on the females back and support itself by biting the females neck. Then, the male lizards connects is hemipenes/male organ to the females cloaca (female organ) and pours its sperms that move up the oviduct to fertilize the ova (female egg). *
*However, before mating, the male and female may have 1 to 2 months of courtship during the mating season (spring). After fertilization, the lizard (Savannah, monitor, iguana, or Komodo dragon) lays eggs, which hatch into baby lizards in 4 to 8 weeks. *
[amazon bestseller=&amp;ldquo;Best food for Lizards&amp;rdquo; items=&amp;ldquo;2&amp;rdquo; template=&amp;ldquo;table&amp;rdquo;]
Related:
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pestpolicy.com/do-cats-eat-lizards/&#34;&gt;Do Cats Eat Lizards?&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>7 Best Substrate for Leopard Gecko Reviewed</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/best-substrate-for-leopard-gecko/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 20:03:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/best-substrate-for-leopard-gecko/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We may earn a commission when you click and buy from Amazon.com.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When choosing the best substrate for
&lt;a href=&#34;https://animaldiversity.org/accounts/Eublepharis_macularius/&#34;&gt;leopard geckos&lt;/a&gt;
, you can consider things like safety, ease of cleaning, and comfort for your pet.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The substrate is crucial as it forms the bedding of the gecko&amp;rsquo;s enclosure, directly affecting their health and well-being.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;key-factors-to-consider&#34;&gt;Key Factors to Consider&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;1-safety-&#34;&gt;**1. Safety **&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Some products, like
&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B09W7KQHCS/?tag=p-policy-20&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;GECKOPIA Premium Reptile Liner&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;
, are popular because they are safe and free from small particles that could cause impaction if ingested. Safety is paramount when selecting a substrate for Leopard Geckos.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What Do Chameleon Colors Mean?</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/what-do-chameleon-colors-mean/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 19:57:08 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/what-do-chameleon-colors-mean/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We may earn a commission when you click and buy from Amazon.com.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Chameleons are famous for changing colors. A coat of many colors is a story about a little girl who had a coat that was not just one color. She takes it to church with her and everyone admires the colors.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;That&amp;rsquo;s a chameleon! Just like peacocks, a chameleon will change color depending on its mood changes, temperature, or body language.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Can Bearded Dragons Eat Bananas?? 7 Secrets</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/can-bearded-dragons-eat-bananas/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 19:07:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/can-bearded-dragons-eat-bananas/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We may earn a commission when you click and buy from Amazon.com.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://hort.ufl.edu/trees/MUSSPPA.pdf&#34;&gt;Bananas (&lt;em&gt;musa spp)&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;
are widely eaten at homes in cooked form or as snacks when ripe. It concerns many whether
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pestpolicy.com/what-do-bearded-dragons-eat/&#34;&gt;bearded dragons can feed&lt;/a&gt;
on bananas, whether ripe or raw. May be you even wonders if banana peels, leaves or stems can be used to feed these lizards.
*So, can bearded dragon eat bananas? The direct answer is YES!  Bearded dragons will comfortably feed on bananas whether ripe or unripe. Bananas have rich vitamin composition (needed to boost immunity), high dietary fibers (specially unripe bananas  which prevents constipation), high potassium content (needed to regulate blood pressure and kidney stones). *
*Bananas have strong antioxidants (dopamine, catechins  reduces heart diseases), low salt and sugar content (especially unripe bananas- which reduces diabetes and teeth decay), low water level (that reduce over hydration) as well as rich mineral components such as folate, iron, niacin, riboflavin, magnesium, manganese &amp;amp; calcium, which improves growth and development of bones, tissues and organs. *
[amazon bestseller=&amp;ldquo;Food for Bearded Dragons&amp;rdquo; items=&amp;ldquo;2&amp;rdquo; template=&amp;ldquo;table&amp;rdquo;]&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Are Blue Tailed Lizards Poisonous?</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/are-blue-tailed-lizards-poisonous/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 18:32:17 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/are-blue-tailed-lizards-poisonous/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We may earn a commission when you click and buy from Amazon.com.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Could be you have come across Blue Tailed Lizards in your home, yard or zoo and wonder whether they could be
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pestpolicy.com/are-lizards-poisonous/&#34;&gt;poisonous&lt;/a&gt;
. Can these reptiles really harm your children, dogs, cats or other home occupants? May be you are even worried how dangerous their saliva or bite could be.
**Well, the question here is, are Blue Tailed Lizards Poisonous? The direct answer is NO. Blue Tailed Lizards are humble, non- poisonous reptiles that will present no threat to your children, humans or pets such as dogs and cats since their bite do not contain venom. **
**According to Savannah River Ecology Laboratory, there is no scientific record that shows a long lasting effect of a bite from a Blue Tailed Lizard on human or pet. Nevertheless, some sources claim that when eaten by cats or dogs, Blue Tailed Lizards may cause sickness and lead to death. **
[amazon bestseller=&amp;ldquo;Best Lizard Cages&amp;rdquo; items=&amp;ldquo;2&amp;rdquo; template=&amp;ldquo;table&amp;rdquo;]&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Is Wall Gecko Poisonous If Eaten?</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/is-wall-gecko-poisonous-if-eaten/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 16:34:44 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/is-wall-gecko-poisonous-if-eaten/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We may earn a commission when you click and buy from Amazon.com.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Probably your home, yard, field, or zoo is full of
&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.insidescience.org/news/how-geckos-run-water&#34;&gt;wall geckos&lt;/a&gt;
and you wonder whether these reptiles are a source of food. Can they be eaten?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Can Wall Geckos cause food poisoning or be poisonous when eaten by humans or carnivores? So,
*is wall gecko poisonous if eaten? *
**The simple answer is NO! Wall Gecko is not poisonous to humans or other animals when eaten. The meat from the Wall Gecko is non-toxic (has no toxins) and is safe for human consumption. **
**However, there are some parts of Wall Gecko that should not be eaten e.g. skin and mouth-part. These sections are known to house pathogens and bacteria such as salmonella, which multiply rapidly and cause food poisoning when eaten. **
[amazon bestseller=&amp;ldquo;Best Food for Geckos&amp;rdquo; items=&amp;ldquo;2&amp;rdquo; template=&amp;ldquo;table&amp;rdquo;]&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Can Bearded Dragons Eat Eggs?</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/can-bearded-dragons-eat-eggs/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 16:24:53 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/can-bearded-dragons-eat-eggs/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We may earn a commission when you click and buy from Amazon.com.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Eggs constitute a major part of the human diet - most of us love them just like
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pestpolicy.com/can-bearded-dragons-eat-cabbage/&#34;&gt;cabbage&lt;/a&gt;
. They are not only delicious but also contain essential vitamins, minerals, and proteins. But can bearded dragons eat eggs?
&lt;strong&gt;The simple answer is YES  Eggs are a healthy diet for your bearded dragons. Feeding the beardie with eggs provides them with proteins and vitamins such as vitamin A, B12, D,&lt;/strong&gt;
and E. However, since eggs contain a lot of proteins, bearded dragons should be given eggs once in a while. This is especially so for adult beardies which require fewer
** proteins in their diet.**
See Also:
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pestpolicy.com/can-bearded-dragons-eat-mango/&#34;&gt;Dragons Eat Mango&lt;/a&gt;
[amazon bestseller=&amp;ldquo;Food for Bearded Dragons&amp;rdquo; items=&amp;ldquo;2&amp;rdquo; template=&amp;ldquo;table&amp;rdquo;]&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Can Bearded Dragons Eat Spinach?</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/can-bearded-dragons-eat-spinach/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 16:13:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/can-bearded-dragons-eat-spinach/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We may earn a commission when you click and buy from Amazon.com.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We&amp;rsquo;ve seen that bearded dragons will eat fruits like peaches, watermelon, strawberries, and even apples. But can bearded dragons eat spinach - the green leafy vegetable?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Can spinach harm the bearded dragons or does it hold some significant nutritional value for them?
**So, technically, YES - bearded dragons will feed on spinach as it&amp;rsquo;s not toxic to these pets and the leafy vegetables have some level of nutritional value. **
But spinach has notable compounds that would make the vegetable unsuitable for feeding to the bearded dragons on a regular basis. So, we generally advise you to avoid spinach in the beardies&amp;rsquo; diet.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Check these
&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.birdsandexotics.com/wp-content/uploads/Bearded-Dragon-ARAV.pdf&#34;&gt;Bearded Dragon Feeding Guide&lt;/a&gt;
.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Can Bearded Dragons Eat Oranges? 7 Tips</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/can-bearded-dragons-eat-oranges/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 15:46:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/can-bearded-dragons-eat-oranges/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We may earn a commission when you click and buy from Amazon.com.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Can bearded dragons eat oranges?&lt;/strong&gt;
Well, previously we&amp;rsquo;ve seen that
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pestpolicy.com/what-do-bearded-dragons-eat/&#34;&gt;beardies feed on selected veggies, insects (bugs), fruits&lt;/a&gt;
.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;**The short answer is NO - bearded dragons don&amp;rsquo;t eat oranges - oranges contain excessive fruit acid and sugar that may irritate the digestive system of the bearded dragon causing dehydration and diarrhea. **
Also, oranges contain more phosphorous than calcium, giving a Ca:P ratio that is incorrect for bearded dragons.
These beardies love supplements that have a ratio of calcium: phosphorus ranging from 2:1 to 3:1. See other foods for bearded dragons.
[amazon bestseller=&amp;ldquo;Food for Bearded Dragons&amp;rdquo; items=&amp;ldquo;2&amp;rdquo; template=&amp;ldquo;table&amp;rdquo;]&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;details-can-bearded-dragons-eat-oranges&#34;&gt;**Details: Can Bearded Dragons Eat oranges? **&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Don&amp;rsquo;t feed
&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.sciencedirect.com/topics/agricultural-and-biological-sciences/central-bearded-dragon&#34;&gt;bearded dragons&lt;/a&gt;
(or other lizards) with oranges. Oranges have excessive fruit acid and sugar that&amp;rsquo;ll irritate the digestive system of your bearded dragon.
Like other citrus fruits, oranges are very acidic. When ingested by beardies, they can cause severe diarrhea plus dehydration.
Also, the consumption of oranges interferes with the pets Ca:P ratio. Oranges contain large amounts of phosphorus compared to calcium.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What Does a Garden Lizard Eat?</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/what-does-a-garden-lizard-eat/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 14:57:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/what-does-a-garden-lizard-eat/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We may earn a commission when you click and buy from Amazon.com.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;What Does a Garden Lizard Eat? A garden lizard is a great reptile pet for homeowners. These reptiles  (Calotes Veriscolor ) also known as oriental garden lizards reside in warm areas like Asia.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You&amp;rsquo;ll find these lizards in grass, trees, and bushes. They are always behind the scenes observing their environment quietly.
*But the question is, what does a garden lizard feast on? *&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What Do Bearded Dragons Eat? 7 Tips</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/what-do-bearded-dragons-eat/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 13:17:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/what-do-bearded-dragons-eat/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We may earn a commission when you click and buy from Amazon.com.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;What do bearded dragons eat? For a healthy life, it is important to feed your bearded dragon with a proper balanced diet. As a
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pestpolicy.com/how-smart-are-bearded-dragons/&#34;&gt;smart omnivore&lt;/a&gt;
, this dragon either eats fruits, plant or animal products/ supplements.
Maybe you have come across a bearded dragon in the fields, zoo or probably own one and wonders what this reptile eats.
*So, what do Bearded Dragons Eat? Well, these reptiles feed on fruits such as tomatoes, apples, guavas, bananas, berries, figs, watermelons, mangoes, papayas, grapes, kiwi, apricots, pears or plums. *
*Bearded Dragons can also feed on vegetables/greens such as cabbages, celery, sweet potatoes, peas, green beans, courgette, butternut squash, okra, bell pepper, clover, turnip green, mustard green, coriander or collard/ kales. *
[amazon bestseller=&amp;ldquo;Best Food for Bearded Dragons&amp;rdquo; items=&amp;ldquo;2&amp;rdquo; template=&amp;ldquo;table&amp;rdquo;]&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What Does Lizard Poop Look Like??</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/what-does-lizard-poop-look-like/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 12:29:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/what-does-lizard-poop-look-like/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We may earn a commission when you click and buy from Amazon.com.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;What does lizard poop look like? Reptiles such as salamanders lizards and geckos love to hang around the house. You will find their poop on any surface including your bed, sofa set, and wardrobe among other places.
Certainly, these fecal droppings can create a disgusting mess in the house - particularly after a
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pestpolicy.com/what-do-baby-lizards-eat/&#34;&gt;heavy meal&lt;/a&gt;
. Sometimes, it difficult to differentiate lizard poop from that of rodents and birds.
*So, how does lizard poop look like? Lizard poop appears as black droppings with a white substance on one end. The white matter shows the presence of uric acid and its excreted together with the solid waste. *
&lt;em&gt;This is because lizards use one opening (cloaca) to excrete solid waste and urine. The size of the droppings vary according to the size and species of the lizard. Related: What Does Leopard Gecko Eat?&lt;/em&gt;
[amazon bestseller=&amp;ldquo;Best Food for Lizards&amp;rdquo; items=&amp;ldquo;2&amp;rdquo; template=&amp;ldquo;table&amp;rdquo;]&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>7 Best Cages for Bearded Dragons Reviewed</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/best-cages-for-bearded-dragons/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 11:31:47 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/best-cages-for-bearded-dragons/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We may earn a commission when you click and buy from Amazon.com.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When choosing the best cages for bearded dragons, you can consider factors like size, ventilation, material, ease of cleaning, and additional features.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A well-chosen cage ensures the health and comfort of your bearded dragon, providing them with a suitable habitat that mimics their natural environment. Related:
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pestpolicy.com/can-bearded-dragons-eat-mushrooms/&#34;&gt;Do bearded dragons eat mushrooms?&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;key-factors-to-consider&#34;&gt;Key Factors to Consider&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;1-size&#34;&gt;1. Size&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Some products, like the
&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B000OAYXTK/?tag=p-policy-20&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Exo Terra Allglass Terrarium&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;
, offer ample space, which is crucial for bearded dragons as they need room to move, climb, and bask. A cage that is too small can lead to stress and health issues.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Can Bearded Dragons Eat Cabbage?</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/can-bearded-dragons-eat-cabbage/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 11:01:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/can-bearded-dragons-eat-cabbage/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We may earn a commission when you click and buy from Amazon.com.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Cabbages, whether red, green, or variegated, are vegetables that are often eaten together with course meals across the world.
Previously we checked
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pestpolicy.com/what-do-bearded-dragons-eat/&#34;&gt;what bearded dragons eat&lt;/a&gt;
. It may even concern you if these lizards can eat all cabbage species or not.
*So, can bearded dragons eat cabbages? The simple answer is YES! The bearded dragon will feed on all varieties of cabbages without any problems. Actually, cabbages have rich vitamin composition (needed to boost beardies immune system), and high calcium: phosphorous ratio (that prevents metabolic bone disease). *
*Cabbages have high dietary fiber (which prevents constipation), large mineral contents (needed for growth and development of tissues), contain powerful antioxidants and anti-inflammatory, low-fat content (thus preventing obesity) as well as relatively low sugar level that help reduce cases of diabetes and high blood pressure on your bearded dragon. *
[amazon bestseller=&amp;ldquo;Food for Bearded Dragons&amp;rdquo; items=&amp;ldquo;2&amp;rdquo; template=&amp;ldquo;table&amp;rdquo;]&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>5 Pet Lizards That Look Like Dragons</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/pet-lizards-that-look-like-dragons/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 09:14:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/pet-lizards-that-look-like-dragons/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We may earn a commission when you click and buy from Amazon.com.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Pet lizards that look like
&lt;strong&gt;dragons&lt;/strong&gt;
**? **
&lt;strong&gt;May&lt;/strong&gt;
be you have ever heard of dragon or seen them in movies. These eminent creatures depict great power and they are viewed differently from one community to another.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Perhaps you may even desire to see a dragon live. Can you imagine having your own pet dragon at home? So,
*what pet lizards that look like Dragon? *
**In summary, **
&lt;em&gt;pet lizards that look like dragons include Chinese Water Dragons, Bearded Dragons, Red-Eyed Crocodile Skinks, Plumed Basilisks, Crested Geckos, Draco Lizards, Green Iguanas, Armadillo Lizards, Horned Lizards, Sailfin Dragons and Frilled Dragons among others.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Do Geckos Eat Bed Bugs?</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/do-geckos-eat-bed-bugs/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 08:58:23 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/do-geckos-eat-bed-bugs/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We may earn a commission when you click and buy from Amazon.com.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Below I answer this question - do geckos eat bed bugs or what can you use to exterminate the bugs. So, will lizards help exterminate the bed bugs?
*In summary, do lizards eat bed bugs? Yes, lizards (particularly geckos or house lizards) will kill bed bugs - but won&amp;rsquo;t be an effective pest control remedy. *
*However, Bed bugs are fast reproducers and hence lizards won&amp;rsquo;t keep up to feed on the bugs with their quick multiplication just like with other house pests. *
See Also:
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pestpolicy.com/baby-bed-bugs/&#34;&gt;Baby bed bugs&lt;/a&gt;
.
[amazon bestseller=&amp;ldquo;Best Geckos Killers&amp;rdquo; items=&amp;ldquo;2&amp;rdquo; template=&amp;ldquo;table&amp;rdquo;]&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Smart are Bearded Dragons? 9 Secrets</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/how-smart-are-bearded-dragons/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 08:43:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/how-smart-are-bearded-dragons/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We may earn a commission when you click and buy from Amazon.com.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Bearded dragons are often hailed as one of the most intelligent reptiles, just behind some lizards.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Do bearded dragons behave like mammals? Do they respond to training? It is possible to train them?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This article will look at the intelligence of
&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.petmd.com/reptile/care/10-things-you-didnt-know-about-bearded-dragons&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;bearded dragons&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;
and answer these questions.
**How smart are bearded dragons? **
*Bearded dragons may be less intelligent than some lizards, but these reptiles are equally smart. *&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Can Bearded Dragons Eat Mango? 7 Secrets</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/can-bearded-dragons-eat-mango/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 06:48:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/can-bearded-dragons-eat-mango/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We may earn a commission when you click and buy from Amazon.com.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Can bearded dragons eat mango? Mango (
&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pmc/articles/PMC3249901/&#34;&gt;&lt;em&gt;Mangifera indica&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;
) is a delicious drupe that grows mainly in tropical climate and is often used as dessert by many people or chewed while unripe.
Could be you have come across a number of them at market place or you grow various mango species and wonders if
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pestpolicy.com/what-do-bearded-dragons-eat/&#34;&gt;bearded dragons can eat them&lt;/a&gt;
. It may also concern you if beardies can eat mango peels, leaves or stems/backs.
**So, the question here is, can Bearded Dragons Eat Mangoes? The direct answer is YES! Beardies feed on mangoes without any problems. Actually, mangoes are rich in minerals and Vitamins (needed for growth and immune boost). **
[amazon bestseller=&amp;ldquo;Food for Bearded Dragons&amp;rdquo; items=&amp;ldquo;2&amp;rdquo; template=&amp;ldquo;table&amp;rdquo;]&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Are Monitor Lizards Poisonous?</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/are-monitor-lizards-poisonous/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 06:30:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/are-monitor-lizards-poisonous/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We may earn a commission when you click and buy from Amazon.com.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Probably you have come across monitor lizards in your field, yard, compound or zoo and wonder if they could be poisonous. You may even have seen them feed on rats, snakes or rodents. But are Monitor Lizards Poisonous?
**The direct answer is YES. Monitor lizards (such as Komodo Dragon, Asian Water Monitor, and Tree Crocodile Monitor) can bite and cause poisonous infections since they are venomous. **
**The venom contains crotamine, which prevents blood clotting leading to a drop in blood pressure and cause death at the long run. On the other hand, Monitor Lizards such as Bengal Monitor and Savana Monitor are believed to be harmless and defenseless. However, these species are few. **
[amazon bestseller=&amp;ldquo;Monitor Lizards harness&amp;rdquo; items=&amp;ldquo;2&amp;rdquo; template=&amp;ldquo;table&amp;rdquo;]&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Top 7 Best Substrate for Bearded Dragons</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/best-substrate-for-bearded-dragons/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 06:26:23 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/best-substrate-for-bearded-dragons/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We may earn a commission when you click and buy from Amazon.com.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When choosing the best substrate for bearded dragons, you can consider things like safety, ease of cleaning, and the natural feel that mimics their
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pestpolicy.com/&#34;&gt;environment&lt;/a&gt;
.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;key-factors-to-consider&#34;&gt;Key Factors to Consider&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;1-safety-&#34;&gt;**1. Safety **&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Some products, like
&lt;strong&gt;Reptile Carpet such as Zoo Med Eco Cage&lt;/strong&gt;
, are designed to minimize the risk of impaction, a common concern with loose substrates.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Are Lizards Vertebrates or Invertebrates?</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/are-lizards-vertebrates-or-invertebrates/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 06:11:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/are-lizards-vertebrates-or-invertebrates/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We may earn a commission when you click and buy from Amazon.com.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;May be you have come across various species of lizards in your home, park or zoo and wonder whether they have backbones or not. How could their internal organs be protected or supported? Could they be having similar anatomy as mammals or other animals?
**So, Are Lizards Vertebrates or Invertebrates? The simple answer is, all species of Lizard are vertebrates (they have backbone also called the vertebral column/spinal column). **
**The lizards spinal column is divided into cervical, dorsal, caudal regions and sacral apart from legless lizards whose backbone is divided into caudal and precaudal. **
**The main function of the backbone is to offer protection to the spinal cord. It also provides an option for attachment of body muscles. **
[amazon bestseller=&amp;ldquo;Best Food for Lizards&amp;rdquo; items=&amp;ldquo;2&amp;rdquo; template=&amp;ldquo;table&amp;rdquo;]&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Do Lizards Eat Snails?</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/do-lizards-eat-snails/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 06:09:51 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/do-lizards-eat-snails/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We may earn a commission when you click and buy from Amazon.com.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Lizards are fascinating creatures, and their diverse dietary preferences reflect their adaptability to different environments.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The question of whether lizards eat snails can be answered with a resounding &amp;ldquo;yes,&amp;rdquo; though the specifics of this feeding behavior depend on various factors, including the species of
&lt;a href=&#34;https://ucanr.edu/sites/MarinMG/files/116745.pdf&#34;&gt;lizards&lt;/a&gt;
, their natural habitat, and the availability of other food sources.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In this article, we will explore the dietary habits of lizards, their relationship with snails as prey, and the broader ecological role both animals play.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Can Bearded Dragons Eat Broccoli? 7 Tips</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/can-bearded-dragons-eat-broccoli/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 05:54:44 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/can-bearded-dragons-eat-broccoli/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We may earn a commission when you click and buy from Amazon.com.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Can bearded dragons eat broccoli? Vegetables are part of the
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pestpolicy.com/what-do-bearded-dragons-eat/&#34;&gt;recommended diet&lt;/a&gt;
for bearded dragons. Broccoli is a source of essential minerals and vitamins. However, not all vegetables are
&lt;a href=&#34;https://cvm.ncsu.edu/documents/caring-for-your-bearded-dragon/&#34;&gt;good for your bearded dragon&lt;/a&gt;
.
*So, can bearded dragons eat broccoli? A simple answer is YES. A little broccoli wont do harm to your beardie. However, you should only feed your beardie with small amounts of broccoli once in a while. Thats because broccoli contains high contents of oxalic acid which may cause kidney failure in reptiles. *
&lt;em&gt;[amazon bestseller=&amp;ldquo;Food for Bearded Dragons&amp;rdquo; items=&amp;ldquo;2&amp;rdquo; template=&amp;ldquo;table&amp;rdquo;]&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What Should I Feed My Bearded Dragon?</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/what-should-i-feed-my-bearded-dragon/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 05:26:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/what-should-i-feed-my-bearded-dragon/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We may earn a commission when you click and buy from Amazon.com.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So, what should I feed my bearded dragon? Well, bearded dragons are pets that are feed on several vegetables, fruits, and insects.
*So, feed the bearded dragons with fruits (tomatoes, mangoes, bananas or grapes, etc.), vegetables (cabbages, broccoli, greens, pepper, sweet potato, or cucumber, etc.), insects (king-worms, meal-worms, crickets, etc.), or substrates for bearded dragons. *
Thus, its evident
&lt;a href=&#34;https://cvm.ncsu.edu/documents/caring-for-your-bearded-dragon/&#34;&gt;bearded dragons&lt;/a&gt;
will feed on various foods, including fruits, vegetables, insects, and equally the commercially available substrates.
[amazon bestseller=&amp;ldquo;Food for Bearded Dragons&amp;rdquo; items=&amp;ldquo;2&amp;rdquo; template=&amp;ldquo;table&amp;rdquo;]&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Can Bearded Dragons Eat Cucumbers? 7 Secrets</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/can-bearded-dragons-eat-cucumbers/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 05:21:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/can-bearded-dragons-eat-cucumbers/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We may earn a commission when you click and buy from Amazon.com.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Cucumbers are commonly used by humans in their culinary dishes as a source of vitamins, minerals, and fiber.
They are usually preferred because of their low-calorie level and high water content -
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pestpolicy.com/what-do-bearded-dragons-eat/&#34;&gt;bearded dragons eat different foods&lt;/a&gt;
.
But can bearded dragons eat cucumber?
**A simple answer is YES. Cucumber gives you a means of hydrating and nourishing your bearded dragon since it contains some minerals and vitamins. **
**But since cucumbers are not very nutritious, they should not constitute the main diet for your bearded dragon. **
[amazon bestseller=&amp;ldquo;Food for Bearded Dragons&amp;rdquo; items=&amp;ldquo;2&amp;rdquo; template=&amp;ldquo;table&amp;rdquo;]&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Do Lizards Have Bones?</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/do-lizards-have-bones/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 05:21:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/do-lizards-have-bones/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We may earn a commission when you click and buy from Amazon.com.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Probably you have come across various species of lizards in your home, compound, fields, yards, or zoo and wonder if they have bones. How then are their body muscles supported?  So,
*do lizards have bones? *
**The direct answer is, YES, all **
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pestpolicy.com/are-lizards-vertebrates-or-invertebrates/&#34;&gt;lizards are vertebrates&lt;/a&gt;
** that have bones that are interconnected together to help them in locomotion. **
**The bones of lizards are classified under either appendicular skeleton or axial skeleton. These bones offer support, protection of internal organs, and options for attachment of body muscles and cells. The number of each bone varies according to size and species of lizard. **
[amazon bestseller=&amp;ldquo;Best Food for Lizards&amp;rdquo; items=&amp;ldquo;2&amp;rdquo; template=&amp;ldquo;table&amp;rdquo;]&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Can Bearded Dragons Eat Cantaloupe? 7 Tips</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/can-bearded-dragons-eat-cantaloupe/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 04:32:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/can-bearded-dragons-eat-cantaloupe/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We may earn a commission when you click and buy from Amazon.com.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;So, can Bearded Dragon eat cantaloupe?Quick answer is No! Cantaloupes are over sugary (causing teeth decay), very acidic (cause indigestion problems). Also, cantaloupe have excess water content (which cause runny poo), Low calcium: phosphorous ratio as well as low quantities of minerals.&lt;/strong&gt;
*Though most Bearded Dragon owners tend to feed their pet beardies with cantaloupe, this act may endanger the animals health at long run. *
*Some vet recommends occasional feeding of bearded dragon with little bit of cantaloupe, but I suggest you avoid them completely due to the above named problems. *&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Can Bearded Dragons Eat Grapes? 7 Secrets</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/can-bearded-dragons-eat-grapes/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 04:29:08 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/can-bearded-dragons-eat-grapes/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We may earn a commission when you click and buy from Amazon.com.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In this article I&amp;rsquo;ve answered this question - can bearded dragon eat grapes? Grapes, whether red, green, yellow, pink or black, are either seedless or seeded clustered fruits that grow in temperate climate across the world.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;**Answer; Yes - bearded dragon can eat grapes - just like other fruits and vegetables! Most species of bearded dragon eat grapes comfortably without any challenge  they actually like them. **&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;**Grapes contains strong fiber content (needed to prevent constipation), relative water content (needed for osmoregulation), high potassium content (necessary for blood pressure control), low acid content as well as rich minerals and vitamin composition. **&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;**Read Also: Can Bearded Dragons Eat Apples? See the bearded draons food. **
[amazon bestseller=&amp;ldquo;Food for Bearded Dragons&amp;rdquo; items=&amp;ldquo;2&amp;rdquo; template=&amp;ldquo;table&amp;rdquo;]&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;can-bearded-dragons-eat-grapes-7-secrets&#34;&gt;Can Bearded Dragons Eat Grapes? 7 Secrets&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;1-richstrong-fiber-content&#34;&gt;1. Rich/strong Fiber Content&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Grapes have rich and strong fiber content that is necessary for digestion process of your bearded dragon. For every 150g of grapes, there is 1.5g to 2.8g fiber content  this is quite high value as compared to other fruits and vegetables.
Maybe you have vineyard or have seen some grapes in groceries and wonders whether your
&lt;a href=&#34;https://vcahospitals.com/know-your-pet/bearded-dragons-feeding&#34;&gt;bearded dragon can feed&lt;/a&gt;
on them. Would it be okay if you feed it with grapes leaves or vines?
Fiber acts as roughage and binds the food being digested within the alimentary canal. Normally, grapes fiber network will help prevent constipation (inability to release bowels) in your bearded dragon.
Moreover, the grapes fibers are strong, long and coiled (especially for seedless grapes) thus providing a strong grip on food being digested without breaking. This improves the peristalsis process too  the smooth flow of chyme within the digestive track of your bearded dragon.
NB: It is important to note that the fibers are never digested and are highly need in every diet that you feed your beardie.
&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=_nCXF8WhW9o&#34;&gt;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=_nCXF8WhW9o&lt;/a&gt;
Related:
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pestpolicy.com/can-bearded-dragons-eat-cantaloupe/&#34;&gt;Can Bearded Dragons Eat Cantaloupe? 7 Tips&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Do Lizards Have Teeth? - Reptile Dentition</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/do-lizards-have-teeth/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 04:21:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/do-lizards-have-teeth/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We may earn a commission when you click and buy from Amazon.com.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Probably youve seen a lizard running around your house or yard. So, youre wondering whether these reptiles can bite you, other humans, in your residence, or even pets.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Further, how do these lizards even feed  with or without teeth? So, do lizards have teeth?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The short answer is, YES! Lizards have teeth that are well adapted to the type of food they eat. The dentition of lizards varies from one species to another within the taxonomic family where some have pleurodont teeth formation while others have acrodont teeth.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;**The shape of their teeth is either conical, pointed, or serrated to help them grip the prey and push it into the digestive tract. Lizards do not have alveoli or tooth sockets in their dentition. Some lizard species have venom ducts connected to their tooth roots to help paralyzed their prey. **
[amazon bestseller=&amp;ldquo;Best Lizards Food&amp;rdquo; items=&amp;ldquo;2&amp;rdquo; template=&amp;ldquo;table&amp;rdquo;]&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Related:
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pestpolicy.com/can-bearded-dragons-eat-tomatoes/&#34;&gt;Can Bearded Dragons Eat Tomatoes?&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Can Bearded Dragons Eat Onions?</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/can-bearded-dragons-eat-onions/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 03:41:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/can-bearded-dragons-eat-onions/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We may earn a commission when you click and buy from Amazon.com.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Do you own one of these
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pestpolicy.com/how-smart-are-bearded-dragons/&#34;&gt;smart bearded dragon&lt;/a&gt;
or have you seen one at you field or zoo and even wonder what they actually eat?
But when it comes to other foods such as onions, you may need to pay a little bit of attention.
*So, can bearded Dragon Eat Onions? *
**The simple answer is No. Never feed bearded dragon with (cooked or raw). Onions are laced with high levels of acids and have high calcium to phosphorous ratio. These components cause indigestion problems along the delicate alimentary canal of Bearded Dragon. **&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Red Eyed Crocodile Skink Care - 7 Deep Facts</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/red-eyed-crocodile-skink-care/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 02:13:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/red-eyed-crocodile-skink-care/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We may earn a commission when you click and buy from Amazon.com.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There are many &amp;ldquo;expert&amp;rdquo; ideas on how to take care of your Red-Eyed Crocodile Skink - but in this article, I outline my red-eyed crocodile skink care guide - the 5 -years of experience of caring for and breeding for these reptile species.
The
&lt;a href=&#34;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Tribolonotus_gracilis&#34;&gt;red-eyed crocodile skink&lt;/a&gt;
is a shy crepuscular lizard. This means that it is a type of lizard that is most active at dawn and dusk. This shy reptile simply enjoys its own privacy but what if you find them irresistible and simply want to be a good host?&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Are Lizards Poisonous? (Secrets Revealed)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/are-lizards-poisonous/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 01:08:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/are-lizards-poisonous/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We may earn a commission when you click and buy from Amazon.com.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;House lizards eat a great deal of insects in the house and some are kept as pets. But you might be worried about their possibility of harming you or contaminating your food, milk or drinking water - but
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pestpolicy.com/are-lizards-vertebrates-or-invertebrates/&#34;&gt;Lizards are vertebrates&lt;/a&gt;
.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Lizards will bite you when they feel threatened. But are lizards poisonous?
**Short answer is NO. Most house lizards are not poisonous. But they have viruses and bacteria on their skin which can cause serious illness when consumed by humans. **
**Only the Blue-tailed lizard has poison on the skin. A few lizards are known to have venomous bites. These include the Mexican Bearded Lizards, Iguanas and the Gila. **
[amazon bestseller=&amp;ldquo;Best Food for Lizards&amp;rdquo; items=&amp;ldquo;2&amp;rdquo; template=&amp;ldquo;table&amp;rdquo;]&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Can Bearded Dragons Eat Carrots? 7 Secrets</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/can-bearded-dragons-eat-carrots/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 00:54:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/can-bearded-dragons-eat-carrots/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We may earn a commission when you click and buy from Amazon.com.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Can
&lt;a href=&#34;http://avianexotichospital.com/bearded-dragon.html&#34;&gt;bearded dragons&lt;/a&gt;
eat carrots? You know that bearded dragons love eating a variety of vegetables. Vegetables are a good source of minerals, vitamins, and water. So, we recently analyzed this -
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pestpolicy.com/what-do-bearded-dragons-eat/&#34;&gt;what do bearded dragons eat?&lt;/a&gt;
But, can bearded dragons eat carrots?
**Short answer is YES  Bearded dragons love eating carrots. Carrots are rich in Beta-carotene and vitamin A which are essential requirements in a bearded dragons diet. However, carrots should be avoided if the bearded dragon is presently on vitamin A supplements. **
Thats because feeding the bearded dragon on carrots while it is receiving vitamin A supplements might lead excess vitamin A. This condition is known as vitamin A toxicity or hypervitaminosis A.
[amazon bestseller=&amp;ldquo;Food for Bearded Dragons&amp;rdquo; items=&amp;ldquo;2&amp;rdquo; template=&amp;ldquo;table&amp;rdquo;]&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Big are Bearded Dragons?</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/how-big-are-bearded-dragons/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 00:02:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/how-big-are-bearded-dragons/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We may earn a commission when you click and buy from Amazon.com.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The bearded dragons are docile and beautiful reptiles that you&amp;rsquo;ll love for their low maintenance. In this article, I will let you know how big bearded dragons (Beardies) can grow while in captivity.
**In brief, an adult (and fully-grown) bearded dragon will have a length of 16 - 24 inches and have a weight of between 380 - 510 grams. However, this reptile will be classified as unhealthy (suffering stunted growth) when it&amp;rsquo;s under 300 grams all under 16 inches after one year - mainly due to cognitive or physical sickness. **&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
