<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Raspberry Pi 3 on Pest Control &amp; Home Improvement Guides</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/categories/raspberry-pi-3/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Raspberry Pi 3 on Pest Control &amp; Home Improvement Guides</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- 0.147.3</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 07 May 2025 12:21:28 +0300</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/categories/raspberry-pi-3/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>7 Best Heatsink for Raspberry Pi 3 2025 Reviewed</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/best-heatsink-for-raspberry-pi-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 20:47:32 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/best-heatsink-for-raspberry-pi-3/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We may earn a commission when you click and buy from Amazon.com.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Is the raspberry pi three overheating? Choose one of the Best Heatsink for Raspberry Pi 3.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The pi 3&amp;rsquo;s SoC (system-on-chip) overheats while under a load, and prolonged load exposure could reduce its lifespan and needs the Best Heatsink for Raspberry Pi 3.
However, getting a quality heat sink for
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pestpolicy.com/best-sd-card-for-raspberry-pi-3/&#34;&gt;Raspberry Pi 3 micro-SD cards&lt;/a&gt;
with a case can help you keep your pi 3 cool.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;reviews-top-7-best-heatsink-for-raspberry-pi-3-2025&#34;&gt;Reviews: Top 7 Best Heatsink for Raspberry Pi 3 2025&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;1-mudder-8-piece-black-aluminum-heatsink---1-pick&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B01GE7Q060/?tag=p-policy-20&#34;&gt;1. Mudder 8 Piece Black Aluminum Heatsink - #1 Pick&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Mudder 8 Piece Black Aluminum Heatsink is perfect for Raspberry Pi 3 but also Pi 2 and Pi Model B+.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Build a Raspberry Pi Retro Game Console</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/how-to-build-a-raspberry-pi-retro-game-console/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 19:07:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/how-to-build-a-raspberry-pi-retro-game-console/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We may earn a commission when you click and buy from Amazon.com.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It&amp;rsquo;s no brainier that retro gamers have always desired to create their &amp;ldquo;general game console,&amp;rdquo; which would enable them to play games from various systems.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The critical considerations for this seemingly &amp;ldquo;idea build&amp;rdquo; have been excellent connectivity to the Television set, comfortable for gaming using a&lt;a href=&#34;https://pestpolicy.com/best-controller-for-retropie/&#34;&gt;Retropie Controller&lt;/a&gt;, and average price.
However, with the
&lt;a href=&#34;https://retropie.org.uk/&#34;&gt;RetroPie&lt;/a&gt;
software and Raspberry Pi 3, the &amp;ldquo;idea build&amp;rdquo; is now achievable. You can now play many retro games in PlayStation, Game Boy, and the Super NES all at a low cost of building the emulation system.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;how-to-build-a-raspberry-pi-retro-game-console&#34;&gt;How to Build a Raspberry Pi Retro Game Console&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;1-install-the-raspberry-pi-to-the-raspberry-case&#34;&gt;1. Install the Raspberry Pi to the Raspberry case&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Your Raspberry Pi will not come with a case unless you go for the bundled offer. However, to protect your Raspberry Pi, it is vital that you install a case for your Raspberry Pi.
Factors to consider while selecting the Raspberry Pi case are design, easy access for your board, port access, and durability.
Please choose a case that Raspberry Pi that has a heat sink. Notably, I will select the Raspberry Pi case that will not require screws and screwdriver to safeguard.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Best Way to Apply Thermal Paste to CPU?</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/best-way-to-apply-thermal-paste-to-cpu/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 16:05:31 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/best-way-to-apply-thermal-paste-to-cpu/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We may earn a commission when you click and buy from Amazon.com.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The right choice of thermal paste is critical for optimal CPU temperatures.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;But, the thermal paste application leads to different outcomes, which could include damage to your CPU and motherboard.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Therefore, in this article, I discuss the best way to apply thermal paste to the CPU.
Youll need to apply the Thermal Interface Material (thermal paste) either when upgrading your CPU or building a new PC.
But why so? The thermal paste helps in heat dissipation from the PC heat sink and the CPU die. I would recommend the
&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B0087X728K/?tag=p-policy-20&#34;&gt;Arctic Silver 5 AS5-3.5G Thermal Paste&lt;/a&gt;
on Amazon and I will be using it in this case study.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Notably, I recently upgraded the
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pestpolicy.com/best-motherboard-i5-6600k-cpu/&#34;&gt;motherboard for my i5 6600k CPU&lt;/a&gt;
and thus I expect optimal gaming experience: Wolfenstein II: The New Colossus, Observer, and Call of Duty: WWII.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>7 Best Power Supply for Raspberry Pi 3 2025 Reviewed</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/best-power-supply-raspberry-pi-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 13:04:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/best-power-supply-raspberry-pi-3/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We may earn a commission when you click and buy from Amazon.com.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You should know that many problems you experience with your
&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.raspberrypi.org/magpi/raspberry-pi-3-specs-benchmarks/&#34;&gt;raspberry pi 3&lt;/a&gt;
are mainly due to using underpowered and low-quality supplies.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You&amp;rsquo;d thus require the Best power supply for raspberry pi 3.
Many power supplies in the market lie about the specification and they experience a significant voltage drop. Read Also:
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pestpolicy.com/best-laptop-tablet-combo/&#34;&gt;Best Laptop Tablet Combo&lt;/a&gt;
.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;reviews-7-best-power-supply-for-raspberry-pi-3-in-2025&#34;&gt;Reviews: 7 Best Power Supply for Raspberry Pi 3 in 2025&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;1-canakit-5v-25a-raspberry-pi-3-power-supply-adapter&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B00MARDJZ4/?tag=p-policy-20&#34;&gt;1. CanaKit 5V 2.5A Raspberry Pi 3 Power Supply Adapter&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The amazing CanaKit 5V 2.5A power supply is uniquely designed for your Raspberry Pi 3.  Notably, the unit has an inline noise filter to achieve ultimate reliability and stability.
This power supply differs from the normal 5V USB power supply. This power supply will enable you to power your Raspberry Pi 3 to its full 2.5A load and a 1.2A on its 4 USB ports.
Sturdy design
CanaKit power supply has been designed to withstand harsh normal use conditions. For example, the unit has isolated and individually insulated cables that will not break in normal use.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>7 Best Wifi Extender for Fios Verizon 2025 Reviewed</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/best-wifi-extender-for-fios-verizon/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 11:22:43 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/best-wifi-extender-for-fios-verizon/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We may earn a commission when you click and buy from Amazon.com.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Best WiFi Extender for Verizon Fios will be critical in extending the signal reach or range in your house or office.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You most probably have a large house, and you&amp;rsquo;ve placed all your routers in one of the rooms.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;But the wireless signal cannot reach your backyard or other rooms in the house (creating dead WiFi zones).
You&amp;rsquo;ll only need the Best WiFi Extender for Fios Verizon to extend the WiFi signal. With their proprietary system, you are compelled only to use the brand&amp;rsquo;s hardware. Read Also:
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pestpolicy.com/best-sd-card-for-raspberry-pi-3/&#34;&gt;SD card for Raspberry Pi 3&lt;/a&gt;
.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;reviews-top-7-best-wifi-extender-for-fios-verizon&#34;&gt;Reviews: Top 7 Best Wifi Extender for Fios Verizon&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;1-netgear-ac1900-wifi-range-extender---1-pick&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B01D6JEMXC/?tag=p-policy-20&#34;&gt;1. NETGEAR AC1900 WiFi Range Extender - #1 Pick&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Why is the AC1900- EX6400 WiFi-Range-Extender out the best choice among the Best WiFi Extender for Verizon Fios?
Well, if it can boost the internet speed up to 1.9Gbps, why not? The wireless AC technology device supports both Wireless and Ethernet.
The Dual Band (2.4 GHz &amp;amp; 5 GHz - FastLane Technology), 802.11a/b/g/n/ac supported WiFi extender for Verizon FiOS, will boost your current WiFi speed and range to attain up to 1900 Mbps.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Raspberry Pi 3 B Review &#43; Performance</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/raspberry-pi-3-b-review/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 11:06:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/raspberry-pi-3-b-review/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We may earn a commission when you click and buy from Amazon.com.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There is so much fun in DIY Raspberry Pi projects, such as security cameras and digital weather stations.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.raspberrypi.org/products/raspberry-pi-3-model-b-plus/&#34;&gt;Raspberry Pi model 3 B+&lt;/a&gt;is the newest upgrade, being more flexible and powerful, but still low priced. I recently run a test for the&lt;a href=&#34;https://pestpolicy.com/best-sd-card-for-raspberry-pi-3/&#34;&gt;micro-SD card for Raspberry Pi 3&lt;/a&gt;.
The upgrade brings superior WiFi performance, wired LAN performance, CPU frequency (200MHz faster), and other significant modifications but still maintained the 1GB memory.
Below are the first impressions and benchmarks after a brief but thorough experience with the new Raspberry Pi model 3 B+. Read Also:
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pestpolicy.com/raspberry-pi-3-vs-2/&#34;&gt;Raspberry Pi 3 vs. two vs. Zero&lt;/a&gt;
.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;raspberry-pi-3-b-review--performance&#34;&gt;Raspberry Pi 3 B Review + Performance&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;hardware&#34;&gt;Hardware&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Pi 3 Model 3 B+ has two key features that stand out compared to earlier Pi models: a metal shield that covers the Bluetooth and WiFi circuitry (assist in RF emissions containment) and the SoC&amp;rsquo;s metal cover (for dissipating heat).
*But, what are the favorable hardware modifications? *&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>7 Best Nintendo Switch SD Card 2025 Reviewed</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/nintendo-switch-sd-card/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 10:45:04 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/nintendo-switch-sd-card/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We may earn a commission when you click and buy from Amazon.com.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Nintendo Switch Devices on Amazon bundles their device with only a 32GB storage space on the purchase, which is inadequate for additional eShop games, game and system updates, and game patches.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;These will take up more storage space, which is why you need the Best Nintendo Switch SD Card.
Most gamers like their Nintendo Switch Video games on Amazon installed on their device, which eats up their storage space.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;reviews-7-best-nintendo-switch-sd-card-in-2025&#34;&gt;Reviews: 7 Best Nintendo Switch SD Card in 2025&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;1-sandisk-ultra--200gb&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B00V62XBQQ/?tag=p-policy-20&#34;&gt;1. SanDisk Ultra  200GB&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The microSDXC UHS-I by SanDisk is the first microSDXC 200GB card that will allow you to expand the capacity of your Nintendo Switch.
With its speed hitting about 90MB/s in reading speeds, youll easily move any da from the SD card to another data storage device. Read Also:
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pestpolicy.com/best-sd-card-for-raspberry-pi-3/&#34;&gt;SD card for Raspberry Pi 3&lt;/a&gt;
.
As we had discussed above, a class 10 SD card  like this microSDXC UHS-I  will help you achieve optimum operation speeds and efficiency.
The SD card has a durable design that will allow it not to operate effectively even in harsh surroundings such as the magnetic field, X-ray field, and high-temperature areas.
Luckily, your Nintendo Switch is now designed to support Micro SD cards of up to 2 Terabytes (TB) of files and data. You can easily expand your memory by purchasing a compatible Switch SD Card to hold your data and files in a safe way.
Nintendo Switch has developed into both a mobile and living room entertainment device. Just like PS4 and Xbox One, Nintendo Switch can pair with your TV set with only a remote control grip and a dock.
However, the Nintendo Switch is not compatible with external storage, i.e. does not support a hard drive. Now, I dive into an analysis of the Best Nintendo Switch SD Card.
Here&amp;rsquo;s how to
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pestpolicy.com/nintendo-switch-sd-card-slot/&#34;&gt;Install Micro SD Card in the Nintendo switch SD card slot&lt;/a&gt;
.
Unique Features&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>7 Best SD card for Raspberry Pi 3 in 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/best-sd-card-for-raspberry-pi-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 06:52:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/best-sd-card-for-raspberry-pi-3/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We may earn a commission when you click and buy from Amazon.com.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;After using different
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pestpolicy.com/raspberry-pi-models/&#34;&gt;Raspberry Pi&lt;/a&gt;
SD cards, I have to say that the Best SD card for Raspberry Pi 3 must have excellent 4K random read and 4K random write, and
&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.delkin.com/blog/learning-the-basics-about-ssd-wear-leveling-algorithms/&#34;&gt;wear-leveling algorithms&lt;/a&gt;
.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I recommend the&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B00WR4IJBE/?tag=p-policy-20&#34;&gt;Samsung Evo+ 32 GB&lt;/a&gt;(with&lt;a href=&#34;http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Wear_leveling&#34;&gt;&lt;em&gt;wear-leveling&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;)for their high 4K random read (8.58 MB/sec) and 4K random write (3.12 MB/sec), and excellent wear leveling.
With excellent wear leveling and
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pestpolicy.com/how-to-format-sd-card-to-fat32/&#34;&gt;proper SD card formatting&lt;/a&gt;
, writing on your Raspberry Pi SD card will be distributed and hence last longer.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;7-best-sd-card-for-raspberry-pi-3&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;7 Best SD card for Raspberry Pi 3&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;1-sandisk-extreme-pro-32gb&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.amazon.com/gp/product/B00NUB3530/?tag=p-policy-20&#34;&gt;1. SanDisk Extreme-PRO 32GB&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Second and Third places on raspberry pi sd card (based on 4K random read and write) go to SanDisk Extreme MicroSD card &amp;amp; Samsung Pro+, respectively, but will cost you more than the Samsung Evo+.
S
anDisk Extreme Pro 64GB UHS-I i
s approved by the microSD cards Benchmarks
for your Raspberry Pi. With the SanDisk Extreme-PRO, you will get reliability and excellent performance in your Raspberry Pi3.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>7 Best Raspberry Pi 3 Starter Kits 2025 Reviewed</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/best-raspberry-pi-3-starter-kits/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 05:26:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/best-raspberry-pi-3-starter-kits/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We may earn a commission when you click and buy from Amazon.com.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://pestpolicy.com/raspberry-pi-3-b-review/&#34;&gt;Raspberry Pi 3&lt;/a&gt;
is the most powerful single-board credit-card-sized computer.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ill review the Best Raspberry Pi 3 Starter Kits you can purchase.
It&amp;rsquo;s suitable for a retro-gaming console or a media-center computer with its standard HDMI port,
*4 *
USB ports, and Micro-SD slot.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;reviews-top-7-best-raspberry-pi-3-starter-kits-in-2025&#34;&gt;Reviews: Top 7 Best Raspberry Pi 3 Starter Kits in 2025&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;1-canakit-raspberry-pi-3-b-starter-kit---1-pick&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07BCC8PK7/?tag=p-policy-20&#34;&gt;1. CanaKit Raspberry Pi 3 B+ Starter Kit - #1 Pick&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;CanaKits Starter Kit tops the list of the best Raspberry Pi 3 Starter Kits, justifiably so, for its superior features.
Luckily, the starter kit will come with the newest Raspberry Pi 3 B+, USB power supply, pre-loaded
NOOBS
, GPIO reference card, HDMI cable, and a Micro-SD card (32GB), accessories that would even complete a DIY robotics project.
In addition, it includes a free step-by-step usage guide. Further, it comes with an amazing Raspberry Pi 3 case to safeguard your board.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Format SD Card to FAT32 from exFAT</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/how-to-format-sd-card-to-fat32/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 04:39:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/how-to-format-sd-card-to-fat32/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We may earn a commission when you click and buy from Amazon.com.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Formatting the
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pestpolicy.com/best-sd-card-for-raspberry-pi-3/&#34;&gt;Raspberry Pi 3 SD card&lt;/a&gt;
, particularly SDXC (64GB and above), to fat32 is usually the first step while using the tiny computing system for
&lt;strong&gt;Pi 3 projects&lt;/strong&gt;
. Back up all the important data or files on your computer or on an external device.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Previously, I was using DISKPART but now I have found better ways. But under what circumstances would you need to format the Raspberry Pi SD card?
(1) To increase storage capacity because of pre-partition (2) To remove a preloaded Operating System and install another one (3) To clean any corrupt software and files from the card.
Read Also:
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pestpolicy.com/best-recliner-for-tall-people/&#34;&gt;Recliner for Tall People Reviewed&lt;/a&gt;
.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;1-how-to-format-sd-card-fat32-in-windows-10&#34;&gt;1. How to Format SD card FAT32 in Windows 10&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;First, maybe you already know that Windows with an inbuilt format utility. However, this format utility will not format any FAT32 (USB drive or SD card), which is usually bigger than 32GB.
Notably, if you need to format the FAT32 partition and right-click the SD card in windows on file system format, it only shows just the exFAT and NTFS options.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>7 Best Raspberry Pi Models 2025 Reviewed</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/raspberry-pi-models/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 03:22:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/raspberry-pi-models/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We may earn a commission when you click and buy from Amazon.com.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Raspberry Pi Models are popular among single-board super-computing enthusiasts and is described as a small Linux-based computer on a single small board.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Raspberry Pi 1, released in 2012, may be used with the PC monitor or Television and with your standard mouse or keyboard.
The credit-card-sized board (computer) allows you to undertake essential computer functions such as playing games and videos, processing word and excel documents using Python programs, and a fantastic
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pestpolicy.com/best-sd-card-for-raspberry-pi-3/&#34;&gt;micro-SD card&lt;/a&gt;
.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;reviews-top-7-best-raspberry-pi-models-for-2025&#34;&gt;Reviews: Top 7 Best Raspberry Pi Models for 2025&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;1-raspberry-pi-2-model-b-desktop---1-pick&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;1. Raspberry Pi 2 Model B Desktop - #1 Pick&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Raspberry Pi 2 Model B came to replace the Pi Model B+. Notably, Pi 2 Model B is about 6 times faster than Pi Model B+.
It has 40 pins extended GPIO and is total HAT compatible and has a 3.5mm audio jack, HDMI port, and 4 x USB ports.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Samsung EVO Plus Review for Your Raspberry Pi</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/samsung-evo-plus-review-for-your-raspberry-pi/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 03:15:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/samsung-evo-plus-review-for-your-raspberry-pi/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We may earn a commission when you click and buy from Amazon.com.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B00WR4IJBE/?tag=p-policy-20&#34;&gt;Samsung Evo+ 32 GB&lt;/a&gt;
is Samsungs innovative and top-performing MicroSD Memory Card that is suitable for your Raspberry Pi.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Samsung Evo+ is uniquely created to satisfy your content generation needs and deliver a larger storage capacity than their predecessor in the Samsung EVO line.
Right off, let borrow from the
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pestpolicy.com/best-sd-card-for-raspberry-pi-3/&#34;&gt;previous Raspberry Pi Micro-SD tests&lt;/a&gt;
we conducted on the Raspberry Pi 3 Micro-SD card.
Samsung Evo+ topped the list of the best SD card tested. Here is its performance parameter:&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;4K random read (8.58 MB/sec)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;4K random write (3.12 MB/sec)
Read Also:
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pestpolicy.com/how-to-format-sd-card-to-fat32/&#34;&gt;Format SD Card to FAT32 from exFAT&lt;/a&gt;
In comparison to the runners up, the
&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.amazon.com/gp/product/B06XWMQ81P/?tag=p-policy-20&#34;&gt;SanDisk Extreme MicroSD card&lt;/a&gt;
, in the benchmark test whose parameters were:&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;4K random read (14 MB/sec)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;4K random write (17 MB/sec)
&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=bufrpvKAbfw&#34;&gt;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=bufrpvKAbfw&lt;/a&gt;
The performance improvements in the all-new Samsung EVO Plus, Philippines manufactured, include increased storage capacity and attaining the U3 (Grade 3) speed class for the 64GB and over storage.
With its characteristic white edge, the micro-SD card is awesome for people working in high-resolution videos &amp;amp; photography and in top-end smartphones.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The card printing is done in English and removes the symbol + while incorporating the Plus.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Further, the micro-SD is a UHS-3 as opposed to the previous UHS-1. It gives you high-performance levels for its low price.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Checking the read and write speeds, Samsung EVO Plus comes with superior 100MB/s and 90MB/s write and read speeds respectively.
Samsung EVO Plus is NAND powered and will thus easily attain the 100MB/s for the UHS-I read speed.
Read Also:
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pestpolicy.com/best-heatsink-for-raspberry-pi-3/&#34;&gt;Heatsink for Raspberry Pi 3&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;conclusion&#34;&gt;Conclusion&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Samsung EVO Plus is an awesome selection for your Raspberry Pi, digital camera, and media recording. This is mainly due to its superior sequential write and read speeds.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>7 Best Bullet Journal Notebook 2025 Reviewed</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/best-bullet-journal-notebook/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 02:28:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/best-bullet-journal-notebook/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We may earn a commission when you click and buy from Amazon.com.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Journalists, writers, and productivity enthusiasts swear by
&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.huffingtonpost.com.au/2025/02/07/what-the-hell-is-a-bullet-journal-and-why-are-people-using-the_a_21709186/&#34;&gt;bullet journal notebooks&lt;/a&gt;
as powerful tools for self-organization. But with countless options available - varying in shades, textures, layouts, and featureschoosing the right one can be overwhelming.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In this guide, Ill walk you through how to find a simple yet exceptional bullet journal notebookone that perfectly balances functionality, durability, and style.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>7 Best OS for Raspberry Pi 3 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/best-os-for-raspberry-pi-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 00:57:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/best-os-for-raspberry-pi-3/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We may earn a commission when you click and buy from Amazon.com.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Did you order a Raspberry Pi 3 without a ready installed Operating System? If Not, you might need to install the Best OS for Raspberry Pi 3.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;If yes, then you&amp;rsquo;ll need to install the operating system manually.
Luckily you have operating systems options such as
&lt;a href=&#34;https://osmc.tv&#34;&gt;OSMC&lt;/a&gt;
or
&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.raspberrypi.org/downloads/raspbian/&#34;&gt;Raspbian&lt;/a&gt;
to enable media streaming. Read Also:
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pestpolicy.com/nintendo-switch-sd-card/&#34;&gt;Nintendo Switch SD Card&lt;/a&gt;
.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;reviews-top-7-best-os-for-raspberry-pi-3-2025&#34;&gt;Reviews: Top 7 Best OS for raspberry pi 3 2025&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;1-raspbian-os---best-raspberry-pi-3&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.raspberrypi.org/downloads/raspbian/&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;1. Raspbian OS - Best Raspberry Pi 3&lt;/strong&gt;** OS **&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As always, the official release is always better in any class of products, and the
&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.raspberrypi.org/downloads/raspbian/&#34;&gt;Raspbian OS&lt;/a&gt;
is no exception, and hence many papers will always start with it.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>7 Best PCIE Wireless Card for Gaming 2025 Reviewed</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/best-pcie-wireless-card-for-gaming/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 00:50:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/best-pcie-wireless-card-for-gaming/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We may earn a commission when you click and buy from Amazon.com.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To achieve better signal ranges and increased transmission speeds for your gaming, you&amp;rsquo;ll need the Best PCIE Wireless Card for Gaming.
There are two kinds of Wi-Fi adapter technologies: PCI-E Wireless Adapters and
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pestpolicy.com/best-usb-bluetooth-adapter-for-windows-10/&#34;&gt;USB Windows 10 Compatible WiFi Adapters&lt;/a&gt;
.
PCI-E has reduced physical footprint, allows
&lt;a href=&#34;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/I/O_virtualization&#34;&gt;Input-output virtualization&lt;/a&gt;
, and an extensive error detection system (AER).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;reviews-best-pcie-wireless-card-for-gaming-2025&#34;&gt;Reviews: Best PCIE Wireless Card for Gaming 2025&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;1-asus-4x4---pce-ac88-wireless-ac3100-pci-e-adapter&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B01H9QMOMY/?tag=p-policy-20&#34;&gt;1. ASUS 4x4 - PCE-AC88 Wireless-AC3100 PCI-E Adapter&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;With this Dual-band 4x4 AC3100 PCI-E adapter, youll easily achieve 1000Mbps (2.4GHz) and 2100Mbps (5GHz band).
Further, you can individually attach an antenna to the PCI-E card to achieve a more compact connection.
To achieve optimal signal connection with your adapter, the device has a magnetized external antenna for the best coverage.
Also, the adapter has an R-SMA antenna connector that will allow you to easily connect to the antennae available in the market.
To avoid overheating, the PCI-E adapter has a heat sink to dispel excessive heat from your motherboard.
&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=KA6lg1YczrM&#34;&gt;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=KA6lg1YczrM&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
