<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Roaches on Insights</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/categories/roaches/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Roaches on Insights</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- 0.147.1</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 07 May 2025 12:21:29 +0300</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/categories/roaches/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>How to Avoid Pests in Apartments</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/how-to-avoid-pests-in-apartments/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 21:46:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/how-to-avoid-pests-in-apartments/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We may earn a commission when you click and buy from Amazon.com.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Avoiding pests in apartments requires a combination of good hygiene, preventive measures, and prompt action if pests are spotted. Here are some effective strategies to keep your apartment pest-free:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;1-maintain-cleanliness&#34;&gt;1. Maintain Cleanliness&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Regular Cleaning&lt;/strong&gt;: Clean your apartment regularly, focusing on areas like the kitchen and bathroom where pests are more likely to be attracted.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Food Storage&lt;/strong&gt;: Store food in&lt;a href=&#34;https://pestpolicy.com/how-to-get-rid-of-cockroaches-in-apartments/&#34;&gt;airtight containers&lt;/a&gt;and keep countertops, floors, and tables free of crumbs and spills.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Proper Waste Management&lt;/strong&gt;: Dispose of garbage regularly and use trash cans with tight-fitting lids. Recycle and compost properly to minimize waste.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;2-seal-entry-points&#34;&gt;2. Seal Entry Points&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Seal Cracks and Gaps&lt;/strong&gt;: Inspect your apartment for cracks, holes, or gaps around windows, doors, and pipes, and seal them with caulk or weather stripping. This prevents pests from finding their way inside.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Screens&lt;/strong&gt;: Ensure that window and door screens are in good condition and fit tightly to keep pests out.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;3-control-moisture&#34;&gt;3. Control Moisture&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Fix Leaks&lt;/strong&gt;: Repair any leaks in plumbing to prevent damp areas that can attract pests like cockroaches and ants.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Proper Ventilation&lt;/strong&gt;: Use exhaust fans in the bathroom and kitchen to reduce humidity levels.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;4-eliminate-clutter&#34;&gt;4. Eliminate Clutter&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Declutter&lt;/strong&gt;: Reduce clutter in your apartment, as it provides hiding places for pests.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Storage&lt;/strong&gt;: Store items in plastic bins rather than cardboard boxes, which can attract pests.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;5-natural-repellents&#34;&gt;5. Natural Repellents&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Essential Oils&lt;/strong&gt;: Use essential oils like peppermint,&lt;a href=&#34;https://pestpolicy.com/how-to-use-eucalyptus-oil-for-bed-bugs/&#34;&gt;eucalyptus&lt;/a&gt;, or tea tree oil as natural repellents. Mix with water and spray around entry points and other areas where pests may enter.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Herbs&lt;/strong&gt;: Plant herbs such as basil, mint, or bay leaves in pots around your apartment to repel pests.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;6-regular-inspections&#34;&gt;6. Regular Inspections&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Routine Checks&lt;/strong&gt;: Regularly inspect your apartment for signs of pests, such as droppings, nests, or damage to food packaging - including&lt;a href=&#34;https://pestpolicy.com/best-steam-cleaner-for-fleas/&#34;&gt;steam cleaning&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Professional Help&lt;/strong&gt;: If you notice any signs of infestation, contact a professional pest control service promptly.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;7-collaborate-with-neighbors&#34;&gt;7. Collaborate with Neighbors&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Awareness&lt;/strong&gt;: Stay informed about common pests in your area and their habits.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Communication&lt;/strong&gt;: Work with your neighbors to ensure the entire building is taking preventive measures. Pests can easily move from one apartment to another, so a coordinated effort is more effective.
By following these steps and collaborating with your neighbors, you can create an environment that is less attractive to pests and quickly address any issues that arise.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why Do Cockroaches Come Out at Night?</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/why-do-cockroaches-come-out-at-night/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 18:56:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/why-do-cockroaches-come-out-at-night/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We may earn a commission when you click and buy from Amazon.com.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Waking up at the midnight hour for nature&amp;rsquo;s call or a midnight craving and finding a big roach challenging your way with even bigger tentacles, could send chills down the spine!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Is this your every night story? Did you know that having roaches at home could pose a serious threat to your health? You need to get rid of them in no time. But! Why Do Cockroaches Come Out At Night?&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I Saw One Cockroach Should I Be Worried?</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/i-saw-one-cockroach-should-i-be-worried/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 18:05:32 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/i-saw-one-cockroach-should-i-be-worried/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We may earn a commission when you click and buy from Amazon.com.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Whenever you spot a cockroach in your house, the first thing that might come to your mind is whether you might have a roach infestation. Well, roaches bring a host of negative effects to our homes and may cost hundreds of dollars to eradicate.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So, I understand the cause of panic when homeowners spot a single cockroach in their house. But should you be worried about the one roach you have spotted?
&lt;strong&gt;A short answer is NO&lt;/strong&gt;
. The sight of one roach is not a single indicator that you have a roach infestation to deal with. These pesky creatures are attracted to our homes as they search for water, food, shelter and warmth. So, the one roach that you spot, could have just moved in search of conditions to survive. However, you should treat this one roach seriously to ensure that it doesnt develop into an infestation.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Can I Freeze Roaches to Death? Cold Treatment?</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/freeze-roaches-to-death/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 17:07:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/freeze-roaches-to-death/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We may earn a commission when you click and buy from Amazon.com.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Cockroach&#34;&gt;Cockroaches&lt;/a&gt;
are unwelcome visitors in our homes - these
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pestpolicy.com/can-humans-get-ear-mites-from-dogs/&#34;&gt;ear mites will even attack humans&lt;/a&gt;
. Majority of roaches hibernate during winter to maintain their warmth. But, some remain active and get into our homes.
**But can I freeze roaches to death? Yes. While this may sound like a lame suggestion, its a low-risk control tactic that wont cost you a dime. Why? Cockroaches die when temperatures fall to a certain level.  **&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Get Rid of Palmetto Bugs</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/how-to-get-rid-of-palmetto-bugs/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 15:49:33 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/how-to-get-rid-of-palmetto-bugs/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We may earn a commission when you click and buy from Amazon.com.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The sight of
&lt;a href=&#34;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Florida_woods_cockroach&#34;&gt;palmetto bugs&lt;/a&gt;
crawling around your house is simply disgusting. In case youre wondering how to get rid of it, you dont need to worry. Weve already done the research for you.
**Carry out these 5 simple tips to get rid of these palmetto bugs without making direct contact. **&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Place roach glue traps around the place in strategic positions.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Use boric acid to make homemade roach baits.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Spread out food-grade diatomaceous earth over the entire place.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ensure every crack; gap and hole along the walls are sealed.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Natural predators such as beneficial bugs and geckos should be encouraged.&lt;/strong&gt;
Palmetto bugs are terrifying and can give you the creeps when they appear in front of you out of nowhere. You certainly dont want these bugs swarming your kitchen or bathrooms.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thats why its important that you learn how to get rid of them immediately.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Do Cockroaches Eat Bed Bugs? Predators</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/do-cockroaches-eat-bed-bugs/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 14:10:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/do-cockroaches-eat-bed-bugs/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We may earn a commission when you click and buy from Amazon.com.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Below I&amp;rsquo;ve tackled this questions - &amp;ldquo;do cockroaches eat bed bugs?&amp;rdquo; Most people dread from the disgusting sight of domestic cockroaches.
&lt;img loading=&#34;lazy&#34; src=&#34;http://localhost:1313/assets/img/img/&#34;&gt;
Natural/biological pest control remedies like
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pestpolicy.com/what-eats-bed-bugs/&#34;&gt;Bed Bug Predators&lt;/a&gt;
have now become popular. So, do roaches eat bed bugs?
**Simple answer, YES  Cockroaches are known predators of bed bugs, which wreak havoc in millions of homes. However, only some species of cockroaches eat bed bugs. **
**Particularly the American and the German cockroaches are very fond of feasting on bed bugs. Others cockroaches that eat bed bugs include the oriental and the brown-banded cockroaches. **&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>7 Best Roach Killer for 2025 Reviewed</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/best-roach-killer/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 13:33:52 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/best-roach-killer/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We may earn a commission when you click and buy from Amazon.com.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Are you searching for the best cockroach killer? The search is over. In this pest policy guide, youll get to know: my #1 rated cockroach killer, factors to consider when buying a cockroach killer, and the top 7 cockroach killers.
&lt;img loading=&#34;lazy&#34; src=&#34;http://localhost:1313/assets/img/img/&#34;&gt;
But are cockroaches that hard to eradicate? Well, some are tough and opposed to some pesticides.
But there are potent pesticides designed for the different species of roaches in our houses. Read Also:
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pestpolicy.com/best-roach-spray/&#34;&gt;Roach Sprays Reviewed&lt;/a&gt;
.
Whenever you spot a roach in your house, the chances are that there might be a whole colony of these creatures. Thats why you must make haste to find the best cockroach remedies for the infestation.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What Do Roaches Smell Like? - Infestation Smell</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/what-do-roaches-smell-like/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 11:15:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/what-do-roaches-smell-like/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We may earn a commission when you click and buy from Amazon.com.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So, what do roaches smell like?
&lt;a href=&#34;http://npic.orst.edu/pest/roach.html&#34;&gt;Roaches&lt;/a&gt;
are one of the most annoying pests you can find in your house. However, sometimes you might be anxious about what type of pest is roaming your home at night. Maybe smell can help?
**What is even more annoying about these insects is the smell they cause in a place. The smell is unpleasant, and it poses a health risk to human beings. So, what do roaches smell like? **
**The short answer is; roach smell is a pungent, oily, musty, and nasty odor. The scent can also be defined as healthy and stinky too. Many words can describe the smells, but we can all agree that the smell is terrible to have in your house. **
[amazon bestseller=&amp;ldquo;Best Roach Killer&amp;rdquo; items=&amp;ldquo;2&amp;rdquo; template=&amp;ldquo;table&amp;rdquo;]&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>9 Best Fire Ant Killer for 2025 Reviewed</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/best-fire-ant-killer/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 10:44:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/best-fire-ant-killer/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We may earn a commission when you click and buy from Amazon.com.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://entnemdept.ufl.edu/creatures/urban/ants/red_imported_fire_ant.htm&#34;&gt;Fire ants&lt;/a&gt;
invade homes, cars, and yards - and their painful stings make them a serious problem. Using the wrong treatment can split colonies, spreading the infestation.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The key? A targeted fire ant killer that eliminates the colony fast. (
&lt;em&gt;For more ant control tips, see&lt;/em&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pestpolicy.com/best-ant-killer-for-yard/&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ant killers for yard&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;
).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;top-9-best-fire-ant-killer&#34;&gt;Top 9 Best Fire Ant Killer&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;1-best-for-lawns-ortho-orthene-fire-ant-killer&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B000A0UCRG/?tag=p-policy-20&#34;&gt;1. Best for Lawns: Ortho Orthene Fire Ant Killer&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you love gardening, you probably know how it feels like to see fire ants ruining the ornamental plants in your garden.
S
ave yourself and
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pestpolicy.com/best-ant-killer-for-yard/&#34;&gt;your garden or yard&lt;/a&gt;
by getting the Ortho Orthene fire ant killer that will not only kill the existing ants but also prevent re-infestation in the future.
&lt;img loading=&#34;lazy&#34; src=&#34;http://localhost:1313/assets/img/03/Best-Fire-Ant-Killer-300x200.jpg&#34;&gt;
This contact killer consists of 50% acephate that only takes a few minutes to treat around 162 ant mounds and has a residual effect that lasts up to 6 months.
It is very easy to use for garden owners who just have to pour one tablespoon of Ortho Orthene over the fire ant mound without the need to dissolve it in water. Its deep-reaching formula allows it to reach ants that are packed inside the mound and kills them too.
Pros:&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>7 Best Roach Sprays for 2025 Reviewed</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/best-roach-spray/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 08:01:21 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/best-roach-spray/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We may earn a commission when you click and buy from Amazon.com.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In this article, I will review the best roach sprays.
&lt;a href=&#34;https://extension.umn.edu/insects-infest-homes/cockroaches&#34;&gt;Cockroach&lt;/a&gt;
infestation in
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pestpolicy.com/i-saw-one-cockroach-should-i-be-worried/&#34;&gt;your house or compound&lt;/a&gt;
can really be problematic if not attended.
&lt;img loading=&#34;lazy&#34; src=&#34;http://localhost:1313/assets/img/img/&#34;&gt;
Cockroaches contaminate foodstuff by biting and feeding on them. They even defecate on your kitchen wear, furniture, and bedding, thus messing them.
What Attracts cockroaches in your home? Cockroaches may be attracted in your Home by some of the following things:&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Do Geckos Eat Roaches?</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/do-geckos-eat-roaches/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 06:52:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/do-geckos-eat-roaches/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We may earn a commission when you click and buy from Amazon.com.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Have you been disturbed by colonies of roaches in your place and wonder which animal can eliminate them naturally? You may even be compelled to find out if some of your pets can eat cockroaches.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Do you own a pet Gecko (house lizard) or have you spotted one in your house, yard or zoo? Well, in this article, we shall delve into close predation of gecko on roaches.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>7 Best Fogger for Roaches 2025 Reviewed</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/best-fogger-for-roaches/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 05:04:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/best-fogger-for-roaches/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We may earn a commission when you click and buy from Amazon.com.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When choosing the best fogger for roaches, you can consider things like effectiveness, safety, coverage area, ease of use, and cost. Selecting the right fogger can significantly impact your ability to control and eliminate a roach infestation in
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pestpolicy.com/best-roach-killer-for-apartments/&#34;&gt;your spaces such as apartments&lt;/a&gt;
.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;top-7-best-fogger-for-roaches-reviewed&#34;&gt;Top 7 Best Fogger for Roaches Reviewed&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;1-hot-shot-no-mess-fogger&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B00P7MZZAG/?tag=p-policy-20&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;1. Hot Shot No-Mess! Fogger&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Hot Shot No-Mess! Fogger is a popular choice for those seeking a reliable and convenient solution to roach infestations. This fogger is formulated to kill roaches on contact, delivering immediate results.
Beyond its initial impact, it provides residual killing action for up to two months, helping to keep roaches at bay long after the treatment.
&lt;img loading=&#34;lazy&#34; src=&#34;http://localhost:1313/assets/img/03/Best-Fogger-for-Roaches-300x206.jpg&#34;&gt;
One of its standout features is its dry fog technology, which disperses a fine mist that penetrates into cracks, crevices, and other hard-to-reach areas without leaving a wet, sticky residue behind. This makes it an excellent option for apartments or smaller spaces where cleanup needs to be minimal.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
