<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Squirrels on Insights</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/categories/squirrels/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Squirrels on Insights</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- 0.147.1</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 07 May 2025 12:21:27 +0300</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/categories/squirrels/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>How To Get Rid of Squirrels in the Yard</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/how-to-get-rid-of-squirrels-in-the-yard/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 21:22:44 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/how-to-get-rid-of-squirrels-in-the-yard/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We may earn a commission when you click and buy from Amazon.com.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Below I&amp;rsquo;ve outlined h&lt;/em&gt;
ow to get rid of squirrels in the yard.
*Are you tired from squirrels and want to get rid of them? We will help you with this. *
*With the passage of time and need of the hour, various methods have emerged to tackle this specieshome remedies to eliminate squirrels. *
Squirrels are an animal that looks quite funny, being small in size, and extremely active and elusive. With the
restless nature and extreme swift movements, they are tough to catch and potentially can cause a lot of damage to your property and holdings.
**See Squirrel solutions. **
[amazon bestseller=&amp;ldquo;How To Get Rid of Squirrels in the Yard&amp;rdquo; items=&amp;ldquo;2&amp;rdquo; template=&amp;ldquo;table&amp;rdquo;]
Squirrels dont leave anything unharmed, from woods to vegetables; all are vulnerable to their potential of harmful instincts.
They can cause fleas and even tick to your pets.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>7 Best Bug Bombs for Spiders 2025 - Crawlies!</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/bug-bomb-for-spiders/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 20:16:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/bug-bomb-for-spiders/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We may earn a commission when you click and buy from Amazon.com.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Spiders can be a real nuisance, especially when they start multiplying and hiding in every corner of your home. Regular sprays and traps might not cut it for a full-blown infestation.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Thats where&lt;strong&gt;bug bombs for spiders&lt;/strong&gt;come in. These foggers release a mist that reaches even the tiniest cracks, killing spiders, their eggs, and other pests.
In this guide, Ill walk you through the
&lt;strong&gt;best bug bombs for spiders&lt;/strong&gt;
on the market. Whether youre dealing with a few unwanted guests or a full-on spider invasion, these products can help you reclaim your space.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;top-6-bug-bombs-for-spiders&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Top 6 Bug Bombs for Spiders&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;1kinzua-commercial-grade-100-spider-killer-fogger&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;1. Kinzua Commercial-Grade 100% Spider Killer Fogger&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If youre dealing with a serious spider problem, the Kinzua Spider Killer Fogger is a powerhouse. Its designed for large spaces like basements, attics, and garages, and it keeps working for weeks after you use it.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Do Squirrels Carry Ticks? 7 Control Tips</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/do-squirrels-carry-ticks/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 19:26:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/do-squirrels-carry-ticks/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We may earn a commission when you click and buy from Amazon.com.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Squirrels are part of the
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pestpolicy.com/&#34;&gt;bigger rodents family&lt;/a&gt;
. They are prone to pests and parasites but do squirrels carry ticks?
**Do Squirrels Carry Ticks? Yes, squirrels can carry ticks, and they also carry other parasites like fleas and spread them to pets and also humans. **&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;**Among the most common ticks are the squirrel ticks. They are also likely to host ticks that cause Lyme disease. **
**Squirrels are known for their long fluffy tail as they invade cereals, nuts, and other foods from our homes. They bring harm by spreading diseases that are caused by ticks and fleas and other parasites.
**
[amazon bestseller=&amp;ldquo;Best Squirrels Repellent&amp;rdquo; items=&amp;ldquo;2&amp;rdquo; template=&amp;ldquo;table&amp;rdquo;]
Well, if you like
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pestpolicy.com/how-long-do-squirrels-live/&#34;&gt;squirrels as a pet&lt;/a&gt;
or you have wild squirrels invading your home, they are all likely to spread pests, parasites, and diseases in your home.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;details-do-squirrels-carry-ticks&#34;&gt;Details: Do Squirrels Carry Ticks?&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Squirrels carry ticks and are a host of many other parasites like fleas. They can spread them to humans if you have a squirrel as a pet.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Long Do Squirrels Live? Life Expectancy?</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/how-long-do-squirrels-live/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 15:33:49 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/how-long-do-squirrels-live/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We may earn a commission when you click and buy from Amazon.com.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Have you come across squirrels in your garden? But do you ever ask yourself how long do squirrels live? Did you know that there are different species of squirrels (
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pestpolicy.com/best-chipmunk-repellents/&#34;&gt;just like with chipmunks&lt;/a&gt;
) and they have a different life span and
Well, I was in the same situation as you a few years back when I had squirrels all over my garden. This prompted me into finding out more about squirrels. Here is what I found.
Related:
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pestpolicy.com/best-poison-for-squirrels/&#34;&gt;Squirrels Poison&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Best Chipmunk Repellents for Home and Garden</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/best-chipmunk-repellents/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 15:29:37 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/best-chipmunk-repellents/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We may earn a commission when you click and buy from Amazon.com.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Are you searching for the best chipmunk repellents? Chipmunks can cause significant damage around your home, from gardens to garage spaces.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Discover the best chipmunk repellents to protect your property effectively.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&#34;understanding-chipmunk-damage&#34;&gt;Understanding Chipmunk Damage&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Before diving into the best
&lt;a href=&#34;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Chipmunk&#34;&gt;chipmunks&lt;/a&gt;
repellents, it&amp;rsquo;s essential to understand the kind of damage chipmunks can cause.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;These small but persistent rodents can dig up plants, chew on wires, and even find their way into homes.
Their burrowing can undermine foundations and damage lawns, leading to costly repairs. By using effective repellents, you can prevent these issues and maintain a safe, chipmunk-free environment.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;1-bonide-868-outdoor-chipmunk-repellent&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07JYFFMV1/?tag=p-policy-20&#34;&gt;1. Bonide 868 Outdoor Chipmunk Repellent&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Bonide 868 Chipmunk, Squirrel &amp;amp; Rodent Repellent is a ready-to-spray solution designed for outdoor use. It&amp;rsquo;s formulated to deter chipmunks, squirrels, and other rodents from your lawn and garden areas.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Do Squirrels Attack Humans? How Often? Dangerous?</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/do-squirrels-attack-humans/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 07:29:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/do-squirrels-attack-humans/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We may earn a commission when you click and buy from Amazon.com.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Summertime in many parts of the World including the United States such as in Washington, D.C., largely experiences an upsurge of squirrels -
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pestpolicy.com/how-long-do-squirrels-live/&#34;&gt;they live longer too&lt;/a&gt;
.
Well, squirrels are comparatively cute and most of us may get attracted to them. In fact, we argue that squirrels are not like lions, bears, or wolves. But do squirrels attack humans?
*In brief, Yes, squirrels will attack humans whenever they feel threatened - their powerful bites may bring dangerous diseases. So, if you love watching or feeding squirrels in the backyard, you must keep some safe distance. *&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Top 5 Best Squirrel Repellent - Deterrents</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/best-squirrel-repellent/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 07:09:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/best-squirrel-repellent/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We may earn a commission when you click and buy from Amazon.com.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When choosing the best squirrel repellent, you can consider things like effectiveness, safety, ease of use, and cost. Ensuring you select the right product is essential to keeping your property free from these persistent pests without causing harm to them or other animals.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;key-factors-to-consider&#34;&gt;Key Factors to Consider&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;1-effectiveness&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;1. Effectiveness&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Some products, like the
&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B002ITKVKU/?tag=p-policy-20&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Bonide Repels-All repellent&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;
, stand out for their long-lasting effectiveness. This product contains natural ingredients that deter not only squirrels but also other pests like deer,
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pestpolicy.com/best-mole-traps/&#34;&gt;moles&lt;/a&gt;
, rabbits, and skunks.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>7 Best Poison for Squirrels in Home</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/best-poison-for-squirrels/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 04:25:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/best-poison-for-squirrels/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We may earn a commission when you click and buy from Amazon.com.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When choosing the best poison for
&lt;a href=&#34;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Squirrel&#34;&gt;squirrels&lt;/a&gt;
, you can consider factors like effectiveness, safety, ease of use, and environmental impact.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Selecting the right product requires understanding the specific needs of your situation to effectively control the squirrel population without causing undue harm to non-target animals or the environment.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;key-factors-to-consider&#34;&gt;Key Factors to Consider&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;**1. Safety **
Safety is paramount when choosing a poison, especially if you have pets or children. Anticoagulants, such as like
&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B0071D0DAG/?tag=p-policy-20&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Tomcat All-Weather Bait Chunx&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;
contain Warfarin, which is effective against squirrels but has a known antidote, Vitamin K1, making it a safer option for use around pets.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
