<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Moles on Pest Control &amp; Home Improvement Guides</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/categories/moles/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Moles on Pest Control &amp; Home Improvement Guides</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- 0.147.3</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 07 May 2025 12:21:28 +0300</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/categories/moles/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Rodent Control in Tacoma</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/rodent-control-in-tacoma/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 22:49:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/rodent-control-in-tacoma/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We may earn a commission when you click and buy from Amazon.com.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Rodent control is crucial for maintaining a healthy and safe home environment, particularly in Tacoma, WA, where common rodents such as house mice, Norway rats, and roof rats are prevalent.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Here are detailed steps and tips for homeowners in Tacoma to effectively manage rodent issues:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;identifying-rodents&#34;&gt;Identifying Rodents&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Understanding the specific type of rodent you&amp;rsquo;re dealing with is the first step in effective control. House mice are small, usually gray or brown with large ears and eyes.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rodents in the Spring: What You Need To Know</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/rodents-in-the-spring-what-you-need-to-know/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 16:53:49 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/rodents-in-the-spring-what-you-need-to-know/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We may earn a commission when you click and buy from Amazon.com.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Spring marks a period of increased rodent activity due to warmer weather and the availability of food and shelter. This season, rodents become more visible and active, which can lead to infestations if preventive measures are not taken.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;increased-activity&#34;&gt;Increased Activity&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;During spring, many rodent species enter their prime breeding season, resulting in a population surge. The abundance of food sources such as plants and insects supports this growth.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Do Possums Eat Cats?</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/do-possums-eat-cats/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 14:45:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/do-possums-eat-cats/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We may earn a commission when you click and buy from Amazon.com.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The idea that possums eat cats is largely a misconception. Possums, being opportunistic omnivores and scavengers, primarily feed on fruits, insects, and small animals like rodents.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;They do not actively hunt cats, and while they might scavenge the remains of a deceased cat, they do not pose a direct threat to living, healthy ones.
Possums are more likely to compete with cats for food than to attack them. This article explores possum behavior, their dietary preferences, and the nature of their interactions with domestic cats, offering reassurance to pet owners and tips to prevent unwanted encounters.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;possum-diet-what-do-they-eat&#34;&gt;Possum Diet: What Do They Eat?&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Possums are omnivores, which means they eat a
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pestpolicy.com/what-do-opossums-eat/&#34;&gt;variety of plant and animal matter&lt;/a&gt;
. Their diet is highly opportunistic, often dictated by what is easily available in their environment. In the wild, possums typically consume:&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Do Moles Have Eyes? Can Moles See?</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/do-moles-have-eyes/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 11:24:30 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/do-moles-have-eyes/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We may earn a commission when you click and buy from Amazon.com.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;From an outward look, moles appear not to have eyes! But how do they manage to dig tunnels and destroy our gardens?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Moles will do anything that is done by animals that have eyes. They dig tunnels, move around, look for food, mate and also evade enemies. But do they have eyes?
**Short answer is YES  Moles have eyes which are covered by a fur and a thin membrane. These eyes cant see things but can differentiate light and dark. Their eyes help them in knowing time periods and seasons of the year. **&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Effective Rodent Control in Eugene, OR</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/rodent-control-in-eugene/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 07:41:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/rodent-control-in-eugene/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We may earn a commission when you click and buy from Amazon.com.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Rodent infestations can be a serious concern for homeowners in Eugene, OR, where the temperate climate and lush environment provide an ideal habitat for various rodent species.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Common rodents such as Norway rats, roof rats, and house mice can cause significant damage to homes and pose health risks.
Here are effective strategies specifically tailored to Eugenes unique conditions to manage and prevent rodent infestations.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&#34;identifying-common-rodent-species-in-eugene&#34;&gt;Identifying Common Rodent Species in Eugene&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Norway Rats&lt;/strong&gt;: These large, burrowing rats are prevalent in Eugene. They typically nest in basements, crawl spaces, and the ground outside. Norway rats can cause extensive damage to property and are known to contaminate food supplies.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Roof Rats&lt;/strong&gt;: Smaller and more agile than Norway rats, roof rats are excellent climbers and often nest in attics, walls, and trees. They can damage wiring, insulation, and stored items.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;House Mice&lt;/strong&gt;: These small rodents are highly adaptable and can be found in various environments, including urban areas like Eugene. They typically nest in hidden areas such as wall voids, attics, and storage boxes. House mice can contaminate food and spread diseases.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&#34;prevention-tips-for-eugene-homeowners&#34;&gt;Prevention Tips for Eugene Homeowners&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Preventing a rodent infestation is the first step in effective rodent control. Here are some practical tips specifically for homeowners in Eugene:&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What Do Opossums Eat? 9 Diet Facts</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/what-do-opossums-eat/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 03:43:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/what-do-opossums-eat/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We may earn a commission when you click and buy from Amazon.com.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Opossums are omnivores, meaning that they eat both plants and animals - like humans. But really, what do opossums eat? Opossums need a balanced diet of proteins, fats, and carbohydrates to maintain good health.
*A natural diet for an opossum would be lots of insects (insects are high in protein), small mammals (high in fat), and the occasional fruit or nut (high in carbs). They need a very high calcium diet (which can be found in plant products). *
*In captivity, opossums/ possums eat different foods including vegetables and dog food. But in summary, their diet can be leafy greens (like kale &amp;amp; spinach), grains (like oats &amp;amp; rice), and fruits (like oranges &amp;amp; apples). *
[amazon bestseller=&amp;ldquo;Best Opossums Food&amp;rdquo; items=&amp;ldquo;2&amp;rdquo; template=&amp;ldquo;table&amp;rdquo;]
Related:
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pestpolicy.com/do-opossums-carry-rabies/&#34;&gt;Do Opossums Carry Rabies&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Top 9 Best Mole Traps 2025 Reviewed</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/best-mole-traps/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 03:05:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/best-mole-traps/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We may earn a commission when you click and buy from Amazon.com.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Are you searching for the best mole traps? We cover it all in this guide!
But first, what damage have moles caused you? Or have you tried other strategies to eradicate moles but with little results?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Well, these pesky creatures are never useful to anyone.
In this review, I&amp;rsquo;ll show you why mole traps are the best remedies for eradicating moles. Let&amp;rsquo;s get started! Related:
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pestpolicy.com/do-moles-have-eyes/&#34;&gt;Do Moles Have Eyes&lt;/a&gt;
?&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Do Possums Eat Chickens?</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/do-possums-eat-chickens/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 02:51:47 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/do-possums-eat-chickens/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We may earn a commission when you click and buy from Amazon.com.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Maybe some chicken (plus chicks) and their eggs have recently disappeared from their coop. Recently, there have been some native opossums
*(Didelphis Virginiana) and dead chickens *
around - well, these are scavengers.
So, you&amp;rsquo;re wondering really &amp;lsquo;do possums eat chickens?&amp;rsquo; Well, Yes, possums will scavenger and eat chickens (including fully-grown hens) and other easy food sources like chicks and eggs.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Can You Tell If You Have Moles in Your Yard</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/how-can-you-tell-if-you-have-moles-in-your-yard/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 01:15:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/how-can-you-tell-if-you-have-moles-in-your-yard/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We may earn a commission when you click and buy from Amazon.com.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Maybe in your yard, you spotted a mouse or a rat, or its a mole but you can tell the difference. How can you tell if you have moles in your yard?
&lt;strong&gt;Well, here are the signs of moles in the yard; moulding, drying plants and grass, and sighting a mole. You need to deal with them, the moment you spot them before the level of damage can be extensive.&lt;/strong&gt;
In this regard, there are a few questions to answer to help you understand what we are dealing with. Check also the
&lt;a href=&#34;https://pestpolicy.com/best-gopher-traps/&#34;&gt;gopher traps&lt;/a&gt;
. If you want to know you have moles in your yard, here are some commons things you have to look out for.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
